{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19365 * 12534.", "answer": 242720910, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11544 * 10618.", "answer": 122574192, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17542 * 15827.", "answer": 277637234, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12557 * 12267.", "answer": 154036719, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14341 * 16014.", "answer": 229656774, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19538 * 14093.", "answer": 275349034, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13817 * 14198.", "answer": 196173766, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14920 * 11505.", "answer": 171654600, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19346 * 16550.", "answer": 320176300, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19323 * 13562.", "answer": 262058526, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11264 * 15319.", "answer": 172553216, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17905 * 12832.", "answer": 229756960, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17999 * 19440.", "answer": 349900560, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11562 * 19752.", "answer": 228372624, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14921 * 10612.", "answer": 158341652, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19441 * 16251.", "answer": 315935691, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11285 * 10916.", "answer": 123187060, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15478 * 15700.", "answer": 243004600, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17115 * 16824.", "answer": 287942760, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11974 * 13714.", "answer": 164211436, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19868 * 10187.", "answer": 202395316, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16266 * 10886.", "answer": 177071676, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14993 * 18591.", "answer": 278734863, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10674 * 15231.", "answer": 162575694, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18846 * 19255.", "answer": 362879730, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12450 * 15354.", "answer": 191157300, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18231 * 13617.", "answer": 248251527, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12509 * 10827.", "answer": 135434943, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16436 * 17300.", "answer": 284342800, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19750 * 19424.", "answer": 383624000, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18269 * 11475.", "answer": 209636775, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13638 * 17076.", "answer": 232882488, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14747 * 16460.", "answer": 242735620, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12425 * 12165.", "answer": 151150125, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15507 * 11352.", "answer": 176035464, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17796 * 19362.", "answer": 344566152, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10807 * 18980.", "answer": 205116860, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16540 * 14301.", "answer": 236538540, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11393 * 16529.", "answer": 188314897, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18221 * 17118.", "answer": 311907078, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12136 * 12209.", "answer": 148168424, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17879 * 19163.", "answer": 342615277, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13245 * 17993.", "answer": 238317285, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16476 * 19360.", "answer": 318975360, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13212 * 19194.", "answer": 253591128, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18589 * 14034.", "answer": 260878026, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13970 * 11173.", "answer": 156086810, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14362 * 17046.", "answer": 244814652, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15298 * 19437.", "answer": 297347226, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11467 * 11843.", "answer": 135803681, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16776 * 16939.", "answer": 284168664, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15984 * 15706.", "answer": 251044704, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13120 * 15254.", "answer": 200132480, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15644 * 19730.", "answer": 308656120, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10396 * 14994.", "answer": 155877624, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12773 * 15729.", "answer": 200906517, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17245 * 12389.", "answer": 213648305, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17216 * 10735.", "answer": 184813760, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13825 * 13271.", "answer": 183471575, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16124 * 12555.", "answer": 202436820, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11405 * 11841.", "answer": 135046605, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10893 * 13982.", "answer": 152305926, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12419 * 14713.", "answer": 182720747, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10225 * 15624.", "answer": 159755400, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11823 * 14999.", "answer": 177333177, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17373 * 17719.", "answer": 307832187, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10372 * 15437.", "answer": 160112564, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13424 * 18814.", "answer": 252559136, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13471 * 13339.", "answer": 179689669, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18952 * 18573.", "answer": 351995496, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14237 * 18991.", "answer": 270374867, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17913 * 12315.", "answer": 220598595, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10301 * 16170.", "answer": 166567170, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19551 * 18631.", "answer": 364254681, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10712 * 14185.", "answer": 151949720, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12790 * 10984.", "answer": 140485360, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14653 * 13288.", "answer": 194709064, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14444 * 10869.", "answer": 156991836, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17617 * 10136.", "answer": 178565912, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11091 * 16367.", "answer": 181526397, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14445 * 15901.", "answer": 229689945, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11767 * 10312.", "answer": 121341304, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14792 * 16332.", "answer": 241582944, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13787 * 16237.", "answer": 223859519, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18331 * 11631.", "answer": 213207861, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15168 * 17940.", "answer": 272113920, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19782 * 18709.", "answer": 370101438, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11442 * 13054.", "answer": 149363868, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13258 * 18202.", "answer": 241322116, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17503 * 19186.", "answer": 335812558, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10352 * 10651.", "answer": 110259152, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14053 * 18673.", "answer": 262411669, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14995 * 15465.", "answer": 231897675, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18027 * 16445.", "answer": 296454015, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12572 * 10301.", "answer": 129504172, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15681 * 15765.", "answer": 247210965, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15822 * 14953.", "answer": 236586366, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13869 * 18212.", "answer": 252582228, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14519 * 11015.", "answer": 159926785, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14221 * 16343.", "answer": 232413803, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10482 * 19092.", "answer": 200122344, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14590 * 13695.", "answer": 199810050, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12485 * 15599.", "answer": 194753515, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16436 * 12248.", "answer": 201308128, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11438 * 16262.", "answer": 186004756, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18531 * 13726.", "answer": 254356506, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16837 * 13938.", "answer": 234674106, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19386 * 12502.", "answer": 242363772, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16987 * 15118.", "answer": 256809466, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19918 * 15395.", "answer": 306637610, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17359 * 18883.", "answer": 327789997, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12158 * 13387.", "answer": 162759146, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12270 * 19519.", "answer": 239498130, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18869 * 13314.", "answer": 251221866, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12262 * 15062.", "answer": 184690244, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18582 * 12215.", "answer": 226979130, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17046 * 12378.", "answer": 210995388, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19254 * 12589.", "answer": 242388606, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15201 * 11111.", "answer": 168898311, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19131 * 18732.", "answer": 358361892, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11939 * 13016.", "answer": 155398024, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15203 * 12384.", "answer": 188273952, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10483 * 15221.", "answer": 159561743, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16783 * 16737.", "answer": 280897071, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14970 * 17258.", "answer": 258352260, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14485 * 12489.", "answer": 180903165, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13079 * 11749.", "answer": 153665171, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12155 * 13026.", "answer": 158331030, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10429 * 14372.", "answer": 149885588, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19922 * 19290.", "answer": 384295380, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13783 * 19770.", "answer": 272489910, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13804 * 13783.", "answer": 190260532, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10427 * 15886.", "answer": 165643322, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11302 * 17808.", "answer": 201266016, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12196 * 18230.", "answer": 222333080, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19907 * 17680.", "answer": 351955760, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16126 * 13014.", "answer": 209863764, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16348 * 18051.", "answer": 295097748, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17763 * 12253.", "answer": 217650039, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12683 * 13166.", "answer": 166984378, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13707 * 10528.", "answer": 144307296, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16694 * 10245.", "answer": 171030030, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14421 * 16767.", "answer": 241796907, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13646 * 13323.", "answer": 181805658, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13351 * 11083.", "answer": 147969133, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12901 * 17197.", "answer": 221858497, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18027 * 15323.", "answer": 276227721, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17496 * 14043.", "answer": 245696328, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17005 * 16633.", "answer": 282844165, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10685 * 19960.", "answer": 213272600, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16232 * 15126.", "answer": 245525232, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16457 * 19370.", "answer": 318772090, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19728 * 18784.", "answer": 370570752, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18605 * 10630.", "answer": 197771150, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18530 * 11791.", "answer": 218487230, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17399 * 17485.", "answer": 304221515, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10694 * 14025.", "answer": 149983350, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18498 * 18812.", "answer": 347984376, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16481 * 10643.", "answer": 175407283, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19137 * 16347.", "answer": 312832539, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18456 * 10807.", "answer": 199453992, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13110 * 14770.", "answer": 193634700, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17201 * 16521.", "answer": 284177721, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14989 * 14684.", "answer": 220098476, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17558 * 12727.", "answer": 223460666, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16921 * 14823.", "answer": 250819983, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10893 * 18470.", "answer": 201193710, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12330 * 17595.", "answer": 216946350, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17400 * 11481.", "answer": 199769400, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18202 * 11854.", "answer": 215766508, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12945 * 19591.", "answer": 253605495, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18952 * 12216.", "answer": 231517632, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16440 * 16775.", "answer": 275781000, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15299 * 17387.", "answer": 266003713, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10408 * 12930.", "answer": 134575440, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17433 * 19671.", "answer": 342924543, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13308 * 17449.", "answer": 232211292, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11477 * 14097.", "answer": 161791269, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15309 * 12686.", "answer": 194209974, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12024 * 11494.", "answer": 138203856, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11870 * 17362.", "answer": 206086940, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15946 * 11397.", "answer": 181736562, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18582 * 16292.", "answer": 302737944, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18383 * 12619.", "answer": 231975077, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16204 * 19016.", "answer": 308135264, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16235 * 10719.", "answer": 174022965, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12799 * 15491.", "answer": 198269309, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19265 * 12459.", "answer": 240022635, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12656 * 12369.", "answer": 156542064, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12930 * 10840.", "answer": 140161200, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16874 * 15047.", "answer": 253903078, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15071 * 17311.", "answer": 260894081, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14731 * 12960.", "answer": 190913760, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11926 * 12155.", "answer": 144960530, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13323 * 10057.", "answer": 133989411, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14146 * 10200.", "answer": 144289200, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17514 * 18153.", "answer": 317931642, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18169 * 18904.", "answer": 343466776, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10094 * 19961.", "answer": 201486334, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18084 * 13897.", "answer": 251313348, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13553 * 19647.", "answer": 266275791, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17794 * 17434.", "answer": 310220596, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16719 * 17239.", "answer": 288218841, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11300 * 19850.", "answer": 224305000, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19832 * 10107.", "answer": 200442024, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14009 * 18967.", "answer": 265708703, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14556 * 19134.", "answer": 278514504, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13401 * 10801.", "answer": 144744201, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13028 * 12429.", "answer": 161925012, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10902 * 15718.", "answer": 171357636, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10601 * 12381.", "answer": 131250981, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10531 * 19471.", "answer": 205049101, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19884 * 14889.", "answer": 296052876, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15424 * 11436.", "answer": 176388864, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10803 * 11784.", "answer": 127302552, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16831 * 12920.", "answer": 217456520, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12643 * 14659.", "answer": 185333737, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19747 * 19376.", "answer": 382617872, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19210 * 12906.", "answer": 247924260, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17460 * 19485.", "answer": 340208100, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15901 * 10587.", "answer": 168343887, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11525 * 14903.", "answer": 171757075, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15289 * 16038.", "answer": 245204982, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16208 * 11108.", "answer": 180038464, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17001 * 19018.", "answer": 323325018, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11063 * 14797.", "answer": 163699211, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17713 * 12204.", "answer": 216169452, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11999 * 14496.", "answer": 173937504, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15393 * 18635.", "answer": 286848555, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16779 * 18595.", "answer": 312005505, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13438 * 13425.", "answer": 180405150, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10953 * 11790.", "answer": 129135870, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19361 * 18666.", "answer": 361392426, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11436 * 17924.", "answer": 204978864, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19908 * 14705.", "answer": 292747140, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16996 * 19975.", "answer": 339495100, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15185 * 14254.", "answer": 216446990, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18608 * 19423.", "answer": 361423184, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15797 * 12125.", "answer": 191538625, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19218 * 18132.", "answer": 348460776, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18514 * 18154.", "answer": 336103156, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18069 * 12947.", "answer": 233939343, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19984 * 13812.", "answer": 276019008, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14759 * 13171.", "answer": 194390789, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10025 * 11936.", "answer": 119658400, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10392 * 17616.", "answer": 183065472, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11932 * 13396.", "answer": 159841072, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16793 * 16783.", "answer": 281836919, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10745 * 15468.", "answer": 166203660, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15728 * 19181.", "answer": 301678768, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13478 * 10185.", "answer": 137273430, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13296 * 14614.", "answer": 194307744, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14168 * 11111.", "answer": 157420648, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15042 * 14919.", "answer": 224411598, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18301 * 19011.", "answer": 347920311, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15307 * 10100.", "answer": 154600700, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11865 * 15460.", "answer": 183432900, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15592 * 16488.", "answer": 257080896, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19321 * 10477.", "answer": 202426117, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12877 * 13178.", "answer": 169693106, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15415 * 15536.", "answer": 239487440, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17849 * 17774.", "answer": 317248126, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10582 * 12224.", "answer": 129354368, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17888 * 12545.", "answer": 224404960, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17546 * 18797.", "answer": 329812162, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15490 * 17577.", "answer": 272267730, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16782 * 10917.", "answer": 183209094, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18537 * 14904.", "answer": 276275448, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19256 * 15169.", "answer": 292094264, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19096 * 18779.", "answer": 358603784, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10306 * 13412.", "answer": 138224072, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19460 * 15434.", "answer": 300345640, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15793 * 11084.", "answer": 175049612, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12446 * 14595.", "answer": 181649370, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10510 * 15556.", "answer": 163493560, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16147 * 18753.", "answer": 302804691, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12719 * 19354.", "answer": 246163526, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19923 * 16382.", "answer": 326378586, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13070 * 19751.", "answer": 258145570, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11914 * 15050.", "answer": 179305700, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15152 * 10518.", "answer": 159368736, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14448 * 16780.", "answer": 242437440, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11422 * 18143.", "answer": 207229346, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13893 * 16088.", "answer": 223510584, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17404 * 14958.", "answer": 260329032, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13541 * 18603.", "answer": 251903223, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14953 * 12867.", "answer": 192400251, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11838 * 16131.", "answer": 190958778, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10612 * 13311.", "answer": 141256332, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11517 * 17270.", "answer": 198898590, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18290 * 10408.", "answer": 190362320, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17907 * 18192.", "answer": 325764144, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12524 * 13116.", "answer": 164264784, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15572 * 17921.", "answer": 279065812, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18579 * 15084.", "answer": 280245636, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15363 * 12347.", "answer": 189686961, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11609 * 18456.", "answer": 214255704, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12174 * 13361.", "answer": 162656814, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10598 * 17526.", "answer": 185740548, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16350 * 18558.", "answer": 303423300, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11897 * 10067.", "answer": 119767099, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15095 * 10721.", "answer": 161833495, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19736 * 11426.", "answer": 225503536, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15460 * 17649.", "answer": 272853540, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10755 * 11689.", "answer": 125715195, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18529 * 15119.", "answer": 280139951, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10368 * 19462.", "answer": 201782016, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15114 * 13438.", "answer": 203101932, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15257 * 13285.", "answer": 202689245, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13154 * 14695.", "answer": 193298030, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14532 * 18720.", "answer": 272039040, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15228 * 17227.", "answer": 262332756, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11927 * 14467.", "answer": 172547909, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12446 * 12580.", "answer": 156570680, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14483 * 11875.", "answer": 171985625, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10249 * 19168.", "answer": 196452832, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18422 * 11677.", "answer": 215113694, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13384 * 18888.", "answer": 252796992, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15739 * 19000.", "answer": 299041000, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15218 * 14440.", "answer": 219747920, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12319 * 14641.", "answer": 180362479, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19405 * 14011.", "answer": 271883455, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12806 * 11167.", "answer": 143004602, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15101 * 15549.", "answer": 234805449, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18856 * 17268.", "answer": 325605408, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10831 * 12131.", "answer": 131390861, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10475 * 17712.", "answer": 185533200, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10826 * 11735.", "answer": 127043110, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16284 * 10881.", "answer": 177186204, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11410 * 16987.", "answer": 193821670, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16421 * 12932.", "answer": 212356372, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19766 * 19711.", "answer": 389607626, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17304 * 15826.", "answer": 273853104, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15119 * 15444.", "answer": 233497836, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13246 * 18740.", "answer": 248230040, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11286 * 17629.", "answer": 198960894, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19302 * 12159.", "answer": 234693018, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11522 * 17672.", "answer": 203616784, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11593 * 17464.", "answer": 202460152, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15085 * 17625.", "answer": 265873125, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17709 * 13796.", "answer": 244313364, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13666 * 12354.", "answer": 168829764, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14227 * 15954.", "answer": 226977558, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16423 * 13004.", "answer": 213564692, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15412 * 15320.", "answer": 236111840, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17426 * 17987.", "answer": 313441462, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10495 * 11070.", "answer": 116179650, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17787 * 11849.", "answer": 210758163, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15758 * 17842.", "answer": 281154236, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17556 * 12798.", "answer": 224681688, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14624 * 15711.", "answer": 229757664, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19903 * 19415.", "answer": 386416745, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12087 * 18322.", "answer": 221458014, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11686 * 16646.", "answer": 194525156, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11752 * 15339.", "answer": 180263928, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19111 * 11162.", "answer": 213316982, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14949 * 18728.", "answer": 279964872, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17552 * 16566.", "answer": 290766432, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19675 * 16773.", "answer": 330008775, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13908 * 13992.", "answer": 194600736, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18977 * 12605.", "answer": 239205085, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17903 * 16288.", "answer": 291604064, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11082 * 15582.", "answer": 172679724, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13411 * 19682.", "answer": 263955302, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17063 * 17132.", "answer": 292323316, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19293 * 15606.", "answer": 301086558, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18921 * 13869.", "answer": 262415349, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12835 * 11276.", "answer": 144727460, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19407 * 17972.", "answer": 348782604, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11873 * 19702.", "answer": 233921846, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19766 * 17584.", "answer": 347565344, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15330 * 19094.", "answer": 292711020, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11599 * 17294.", "answer": 200593106, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12886 * 15046.", "answer": 193882756, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16648 * 11140.", "answer": 185458720, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19801 * 11781.", "answer": 233275581, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19771 * 16208.", "answer": 320448368, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15364 * 18098.", "answer": 278057672, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11007 * 11483.", "answer": 126393381, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13565 * 12276.", "answer": 166523940, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19515 * 10003.", "answer": 195208545, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12403 * 12444.", "answer": 154342932, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17421 * 18704.", "answer": 325842384, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14775 * 16389.", "answer": 242147475, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19468 * 17326.", "answer": 337302568, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13205 * 13369.", "answer": 176537645, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15187 * 14910.", "answer": 226438170, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19343 * 14989.", "answer": 289932227, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17122 * 15640.", "answer": 267788080, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11462 * 19547.", "answer": 224047714, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10133 * 18362.", "answer": 186062146, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16622 * 12089.", "answer": 200943358, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14819 * 11022.", "answer": 163335018, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16049 * 18992.", "answer": 304802608, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10870 * 10013.", "answer": 108841310, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19175 * 15885.", "answer": 304594875, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11797 * 14623.", "answer": 172507531, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10510 * 13854.", "answer": 145605540, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17073 * 19669.", "answer": 335808837, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16459 * 15212.", "answer": 250374308, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16271 * 16652.", "answer": 270944692, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16251 * 17130.", "answer": 278379630, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18931 * 13460.", "answer": 254811260, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12841 * 17780.", "answer": 228312980, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12278 * 13083.", "answer": 160633074, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19100 * 16301.", "answer": 311349100, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15902 * 16835.", "answer": 267710170, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12527 * 14726.", "answer": 184472602, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12056 * 12200.", "answer": 147083200, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10190 * 11175.", "answer": 113873250, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10257 * 12359.", "answer": 126766263, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17974 * 17155.", "answer": 308343970, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12224 * 11387.", "answer": 139194688, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12248 * 16813.", "answer": 205925624, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17471 * 19902.", "answer": 347707842, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16974 * 12945.", "answer": 219728430, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17444 * 18346.", "answer": 320027624, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16948 * 19044.", "answer": 322757712, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17373 * 16303.", "answer": 283232019, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15821 * 13698.", "answer": 216716058, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13044 * 16959.", "answer": 221213196, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19905 * 10121.", "answer": 201458505, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19468 * 18161.", "answer": 353558348, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13878 * 18220.", "answer": 252857160, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14411 * 16731.", "answer": 241110441, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18948 * 19442.", "answer": 368387016, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16012 * 10548.", "answer": 168894576, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10620 * 19308.", "answer": 205050960, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17917 * 16038.", "answer": 287352846, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11854 * 19507.", "answer": 231235978, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17889 * 11311.", "answer": 202342479, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12327 * 18624.", "answer": 229578048, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14578 * 17617.", "answer": 256820626, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18469 * 11281.", "answer": 208348789, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18574 * 19995.", "answer": 371387130, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11449 * 14017.", "answer": 160480633, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17740 * 11279.", "answer": 200089460, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18834 * 19496.", "answer": 367187664, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15119 * 10864.", "answer": 164252816, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15628 * 18765.", "answer": 293259420, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10176 * 17681.", "answer": 179921856, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17438 * 18399.", "answer": 320841762, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17687 * 19403.", "answer": 343180861, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15431 * 16897.", "answer": 260737607, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15782 * 14827.", "answer": 233999714, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14738 * 12744.", "answer": 187821072, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10578 * 19791.", "answer": 209349198, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14981 * 19235.", "answer": 288159535, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14267 * 11006.", "answer": 157022602, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17752 * 19472.", "answer": 345666944, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12770 * 19385.", "answer": 247546450, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10845 * 14780.", "answer": 160289100, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10447 * 14699.", "answer": 153560453, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17942 * 11351.", "answer": 203659642, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12077 * 18283.", "answer": 220803791, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11259 * 14552.", "answer": 163840968, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14129 * 12171.", "answer": 171964059, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14603 * 14509.", "answer": 211874927, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14209 * 10232.", "answer": 145386488, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11827 * 19893.", "answer": 235274511, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12860 * 19695.", "answer": 253277700, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12476 * 17317.", "answer": 216046892, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16058 * 12873.", "answer": 206714634, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14280 * 13869.", "answer": 198049320, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17944 * 12962.", "answer": 232590128, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18640 * 10542.", "answer": 196502880, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15617 * 11382.", "answer": 177752694, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12376 * 19757.", "answer": 244512632, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12525 * 18125.", "answer": 227015625, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16765 * 16277.", "answer": 272883905, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 13898 * 17211.", "answer": 239198478, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12740 * 13454.", "answer": 171403960, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19465 * 15653.", "answer": 304685645, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10890 * 14331.", "answer": 156064590, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11900 * 10860.", "answer": 129234000, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12745 * 17602.", "answer": 224337490, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16533 * 17802.", "answer": 294320466, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14937 * 17803.", "answer": 265923411, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18724 * 13828.", "answer": 258915472, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16222 * 16390.", "answer": 265878580, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17775 * 14302.", "answer": 254218050, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12378 * 18690.", "answer": 231344820, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17122 * 10194.", "answer": 174541668, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14731 * 17353.", "answer": 255627043, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 16258 * 15172.", "answer": 246666376, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18687 * 10672.", "answer": 199427664, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11595 * 18704.", "answer": 216872880, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 15797 * 17074.", "answer": 269717978, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14466 * 15488.", "answer": 224049408, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 14429 * 14375.", "answer": 207416875, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11610 * 14183.", "answer": 164664630, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19571 * 16408.", "answer": 321120968, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 17554 * 13961.", "answer": 245071394, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 19645 * 13193.", "answer": 259176485, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18518 * 15528.", "answer": 287547504, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 12947 * 15132.", "answer": 195914004, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 18972 * 10173.", "answer": 193002156, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10138 * 11113.", "answer": 112663594, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 10195 * 16737.", "answer": 170633715, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 11600 * 18605.", "answer": 215818000, "range": "[10000, 19999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21702 * 27306.", "answer": 592594812, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25759 * 23594.", "answer": 607757846, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24641 * 24127.", "answer": 594513407, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23163 * 20557.", "answer": 476161791, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20388 * 21506.", "answer": 438464328, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20931 * 29734.", "answer": 622362354, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23552 * 29820.", "answer": 702320640, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21995 * 21965.", "answer": 483120175, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21415 * 29907.", "answer": 640458405, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22128 * 26159.", "answer": 578846352, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29274 * 23027.", "answer": 674092398, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21816 * 23018.", "answer": 502160688, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24150 * 24826.", "answer": 599547900, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27650 * 21240.", "answer": 587286000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27429 * 24528.", "answer": 672778512, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26995 * 25298.", "answer": 682919510, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24216 * 22653.", "answer": 548565048, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21212 * 24543.", "answer": 520606116, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21022 * 26271.", "answer": 552268962, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26366 * 25450.", "answer": 671014700, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20984 * 24230.", "answer": 508442320, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24336 * 22915.", "answer": 557659440, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27218 * 21137.", "answer": 575306866, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28056 * 23287.", "answer": 653340072, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29999 * 26432.", "answer": 792933568, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22923 * 28061.", "answer": 643242303, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21776 * 22357.", "answer": 486846032, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28857 * 27065.", "answer": 781014705, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23578 * 21740.", "answer": 512585720, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27234 * 24243.", "answer": 660233862, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21692 * 20571.", "answer": 446226132, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21194 * 21153.", "answer": 448316682, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29360 * 24105.", "answer": 707722800, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27305 * 20307.", "answer": 554482635, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28154 * 22438.", "answer": 631719452, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20014 * 20619.", "answer": 412668666, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26397 * 24365.", "answer": 643162905, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22483 * 25403.", "answer": 571135649, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26411 * 29414.", "answer": 776853154, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20060 * 28444.", "answer": 570586640, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28039 * 27833.", "answer": 780409487, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27144 * 26617.", "answer": 722491848, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21148 * 28849.", "answer": 610098652, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23700 * 20054.", "answer": 475279800, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26298 * 27898.", "answer": 733661604, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21985 * 29293.", "answer": 644006605, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28770 * 25880.", "answer": 744567600, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25463 * 24961.", "answer": 635581943, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26563 * 20904.", "answer": 555272952, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21485 * 25985.", "answer": 558287725, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28759 * 25571.", "answer": 735396389, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21318 * 27530.", "answer": 586884540, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24750 * 23327.", "answer": 577343250, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22893 * 29084.", "answer": 665820012, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20644 * 26294.", "answer": 542813336, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23129 * 24896.", "answer": 575819584, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26391 * 21749.", "answer": 573977859, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25886 * 27970.", "answer": 724031420, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21390 * 27175.", "answer": 581273250, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23104 * 22292.", "answer": 515034368, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20584 * 23163.", "answer": 476787192, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20415 * 29714.", "answer": 606611310, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23907 * 28015.", "answer": 669754605, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26369 * 21032.", "answer": 554592808, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28856 * 25041.", "answer": 722583096, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28186 * 28748.", "answer": 810291128, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27361 * 20268.", "answer": 554552748, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20606 * 25558.", "answer": 526648148, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20918 * 25533.", "answer": 534099294, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20701 * 26643.", "answer": 551536743, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21936 * 23468.", "answer": 514794048, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28570 * 27509.", "answer": 785932130, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28791 * 22440.", "answer": 646070040, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29492 * 23817.", "answer": 702410964, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21180 * 20604.", "answer": 436392720, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22319 * 28010.", "answer": 625155190, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20312 * 27720.", "answer": 563048640, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20750 * 23976.", "answer": 497502000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22138 * 20235.", "answer": 447962430, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22822 * 20818.", "answer": 475108396, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25035 * 21594.", "answer": 540605790, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27474 * 22796.", "answer": 626297304, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29683 * 21047.", "answer": 624738101, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21742 * 21870.", "answer": 475497540, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28145 * 29748.", "answer": 837257460, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23613 * 21033.", "answer": 496652229, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23320 * 26983.", "answer": 629243560, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25527 * 26586.", "answer": 678660822, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25312 * 21979.", "answer": 556332448, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29436 * 28943.", "answer": 851966148, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22250 * 25268.", "answer": 562213000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23493 * 20746.", "answer": 487385778, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29717 * 22841.", "answer": 678765997, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25496 * 21035.", "answer": 536308360, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21978 * 24487.", "answer": 538175286, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22314 * 26801.", "answer": 598037514, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22753 * 26060.", "answer": 592943180, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29067 * 22703.", "answer": 659908101, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27187 * 23991.", "answer": 652243317, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29535 * 20666.", "answer": 610370310, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22185 * 21637.", "answer": 480016845, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26162 * 22584.", "answer": 590842608, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20256 * 27978.", "answer": 566722368, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21322 * 20104.", "answer": 428657488, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20118 * 22939.", "answer": 461486802, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21460 * 29727.", "answer": 637941420, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24648 * 26819.", "answer": 661034712, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27798 * 22079.", "answer": 613752042, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23377 * 22344.", "answer": 522335688, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24439 * 28570.", "answer": 698222230, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27379 * 26750.", "answer": 732388250, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23919 * 22859.", "answer": 546764421, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20616 * 29769.", "answer": 613717704, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22949 * 28190.", "answer": 646932310, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21442 * 24934.", "answer": 534634828, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25699 * 26861.", "answer": 690300839, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20074 * 29137.", "answer": 584896138, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23860 * 23144.", "answer": 552215840, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21925 * 28686.", "answer": 628940550, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21567 * 25929.", "answer": 559210743, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28842 * 28315.", "answer": 816661230, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23592 * 27605.", "answer": 651257160, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23409 * 24528.", "answer": 574175952, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20869 * 23173.", "answer": 483597337, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21846 * 22444.", "answer": 490311624, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27772 * 28151.", "answer": 781809572, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22888 * 22617.", "answer": 517657896, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20706 * 20885.", "answer": 432444810, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25966 * 24670.", "answer": 640581220, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23433 * 27121.", "answer": 635526393, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24118 * 25477.", "answer": 614454286, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27424 * 20709.", "answer": 567923616, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21710 * 20859.", "answer": 452848890, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28804 * 22881.", "answer": 659064324, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22589 * 20476.", "answer": 462532364, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27947 * 28436.", "answer": 794700892, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21901 * 21160.", "answer": 463425160, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23855 * 27287.", "answer": 650931385, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29710 * 29498.", "answer": 876385580, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25340 * 26865.", "answer": 680759100, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23256 * 25336.", "answer": 589214016, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23769 * 21804.", "answer": 518259276, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25343 * 23731.", "answer": 601414733, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21606 * 23884.", "answer": 516037704, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26759 * 23276.", "answer": 622842484, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26152 * 23615.", "answer": 617579480, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21204 * 27716.", "answer": 587690064, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29586 * 27936.", "answer": 826514496, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20890 * 27141.", "answer": 566975490, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22374 * 23541.", "answer": 526706334, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29984 * 27454.", "answer": 823180736, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22917 * 26346.", "answer": 603771282, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26119 * 22234.", "answer": 580729846, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27499 * 23181.", "answer": 637454319, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25875 * 24418.", "answer": 631815750, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23313 * 25503.", "answer": 594551439, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22084 * 20525.", "answer": 453274100, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29317 * 20977.", "answer": 614982709, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24597 * 22236.", "answer": 546938892, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21820 * 27627.", "answer": 602821140, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27513 * 26852.", "answer": 738779076, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22804 * 25629.", "answer": 584443716, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23602 * 24835.", "answer": 586155670, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29889 * 22568.", "answer": 674534952, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22784 * 29471.", "answer": 671467264, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29056 * 23763.", "answer": 690457728, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21416 * 26745.", "answer": 572770920, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28548 * 28015.", "answer": 799772220, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23546 * 29692.", "answer": 699127832, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27757 * 27581.", "answer": 765565817, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24573 * 20237.", "answer": 497283801, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27014 * 24041.", "answer": 649443574, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24060 * 25362.", "answer": 610209720, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27114 * 29493.", "answer": 799673202, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23643 * 29695.", "answer": 702078885, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22440 * 29399.", "answer": 659713560, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20083 * 26844.", "answer": 539108052, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20724 * 20656.", "answer": 428074944, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27711 * 28261.", "answer": 783140571, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20550 * 26974.", "answer": 554315700, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28701 * 26460.", "answer": 759428460, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27852 * 21605.", "answer": 601742460, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27412 * 28114.", "answer": 770660968, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23940 * 21361.", "answer": 511382340, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29150 * 20203.", "answer": 588917450, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26662 * 23571.", "answer": 628450002, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22174 * 25872.", "answer": 573685728, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24846 * 23916.", "answer": 594216936, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21486 * 20260.", "answer": 435306360, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27860 * 24994.", "answer": 696332840, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22650 * 27524.", "answer": 623418600, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29345 * 29562.", "answer": 867496890, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20399 * 27452.", "answer": 559993348, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27598 * 22271.", "answer": 614635058, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26641 * 23030.", "answer": 613542230, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26068 * 27607.", "answer": 719659276, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20022 * 21158.", "answer": 423625476, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26305 * 25454.", "answer": 669567470, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28698 * 20535.", "answer": 589313430, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24859 * 26977.", "answer": 670621243, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24420 * 28887.", "answer": 705420540, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29424 * 23393.", "answer": 688315632, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21326 * 25500.", "answer": 543813000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20898 * 28433.", "answer": 594192834, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25963 * 20844.", "answer": 541172772, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21818 * 26274.", "answer": 573246132, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25989 * 27624.", "answer": 717920136, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20669 * 25989.", "answer": 537166641, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26003 * 22871.", "answer": 594714613, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29155 * 21097.", "answer": 615083035, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29187 * 23354.", "answer": 681633198, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22267 * 25487.", "answer": 567519029, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23909 * 28841.", "answer": 689559469, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21860 * 27839.", "answer": 608560540, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29504 * 23437.", "answer": 691485248, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23693 * 25250.", "answer": 598248250, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25778 * 24380.", "answer": 628467640, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28250 * 26929.", "answer": 760744250, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24540 * 20892.", "answer": 512689680, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21038 * 26108.", "answer": 549260104, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25656 * 27412.", "answer": 703282272, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27966 * 28215.", "answer": 789060690, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28629 * 22010.", "answer": 630124290, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27703 * 28714.", "answer": 795463942, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28730 * 24788.", "answer": 712159240, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27405 * 26031.", "answer": 713379555, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21075 * 23085.", "answer": 486516375, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27501 * 21430.", "answer": 589346430, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21313 * 26400.", "answer": 562663200, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22929 * 24724.", "answer": 566896596, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21260 * 21791.", "answer": 463276660, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22699 * 24521.", "answer": 556602179, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21835 * 22424.", "answer": 489628040, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28131 * 22465.", "answer": 631962915, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23346 * 28530.", "answer": 666061380, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20371 * 24803.", "answer": 505261913, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26824 * 28870.", "answer": 774408880, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22163 * 27764.", "answer": 615333532, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25680 * 26883.", "answer": 690355440, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27272 * 20351.", "answer": 555012472, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24776 * 23097.", "answer": 572251272, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21031 * 20361.", "answer": 428212191, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23806 * 28513.", "answer": 678780478, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25503 * 26745.", "answer": 682077735, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29481 * 25616.", "answer": 755185296, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25346 * 27965.", "answer": 708800890, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29721 * 28686.", "answer": 852576606, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28986 * 27295.", "answer": 791172870, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27503 * 24982.", "answer": 687079946, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29293 * 22161.", "answer": 649162173, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25021 * 22813.", "answer": 570804073, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24259 * 23715.", "answer": 575302185, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27933 * 26093.", "answer": 728855769, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24720 * 20775.", "answer": 513558000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22430 * 25785.", "answer": 578357550, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24659 * 27469.", "answer": 677358071, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22725 * 22634.", "answer": 514357650, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28770 * 24673.", "answer": 709842210, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22986 * 22873.", "answer": 525758778, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22514 * 22641.", "answer": 509739474, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23897 * 21915.", "answer": 523702755, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20674 * 25187.", "answer": 520716038, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29413 * 22072.", "answer": 649203736, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27223 * 24266.", "answer": 660593318, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26056 * 23022.", "answer": 599861232, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23361 * 29215.", "answer": 682491615, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20568 * 25192.", "answer": 518149056, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25633 * 22423.", "answer": 574768759, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26109 * 27347.", "answer": 714002823, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28845 * 22663.", "answer": 653714235, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28743 * 24940.", "answer": 716850420, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21990 * 20408.", "answer": 448771920, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26628 * 28182.", "answer": 750430296, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22381 * 27504.", "answer": 615567024, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25246 * 22556.", "answer": 569448776, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20070 * 28948.", "answer": 580986360, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28313 * 25427.", "answer": 719914651, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24842 * 27764.", "answer": 689713288, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24748 * 29399.", "answer": 727566452, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22409 * 29260.", "answer": 655687340, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27243 * 25549.", "answer": 696031407, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21840 * 27847.", "answer": 608178480, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20656 * 22284.", "answer": 460298304, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29026 * 21914.", "answer": 636075764, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25047 * 20406.", "answer": 511109082, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26580 * 23610.", "answer": 627553800, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27306 * 25855.", "answer": 705996630, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21515 * 25347.", "answer": 545340705, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20901 * 29963.", "answer": 626256663, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23197 * 29558.", "answer": 685656926, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28625 * 23639.", "answer": 676666375, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24553 * 23206.", "answer": 569776918, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20369 * 21369.", "answer": 435265161, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28821 * 27298.", "answer": 786755658, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21431 * 28385.", "answer": 608318935, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26462 * 23185.", "answer": 613521470, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28035 * 25206.", "answer": 706650210, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29882 * 29913.", "answer": 893860266, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28381 * 20918.", "answer": 593673758, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25915 * 26513.", "answer": 687084395, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22423 * 27006.", "answer": 605555538, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26056 * 26326.", "answer": 685950256, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26108 * 20199.", "answer": 527355492, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24663 * 25651.", "answer": 632630613, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25756 * 25047.", "answer": 645110532, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27300 * 29191.", "answer": 796914300, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21435 * 23533.", "answer": 504429855, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27278 * 26809.", "answer": 731295902, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27249 * 24728.", "answer": 673813272, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22683 * 26944.", "answer": 611170752, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26786 * 22286.", "answer": 596952796, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29620 * 29796.", "answer": 882557520, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21410 * 22353.", "answer": 478577730, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23404 * 24968.", "answer": 584351072, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27776 * 28606.", "answer": 794560256, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25495 * 21083.", "answer": 537511085, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29677 * 26156.", "answer": 776231612, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21449 * 20108.", "answer": 431296492, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26708 * 24478.", "answer": 653758424, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26791 * 22865.", "answer": 612576215, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29106 * 27571.", "answer": 802481526, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29304 * 22243.", "answer": 651808872, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23264 * 23047.", "answer": 536165408, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26254 * 24742.", "answer": 649576468, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29074 * 28037.", "answer": 815147738, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20691 * 24947.", "answer": 516178377, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29588 * 24979.", "answer": 739078652, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28095 * 29163.", "answer": 819334485, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27593 * 23678.", "answer": 653347054, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20439 * 20040.", "answer": 409597560, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22523 * 24303.", "answer": 547376469, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24917 * 27742.", "answer": 691247414, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22034 * 24713.", "answer": 544526242, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26834 * 22938.", "answer": 615518292, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28059 * 24009.", "answer": 673668531, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20466 * 21955.", "answer": 449331030, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24541 * 28078.", "answer": 689062198, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21093 * 29812.", "answer": 628824516, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25927 * 29520.", "answer": 765365040, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27872 * 29266.", "answer": 815701952, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27144 * 24225.", "answer": 657563400, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27799 * 21959.", "answer": 610438241, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26114 * 28397.", "answer": 741559258, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29425 * 20287.", "answer": 596944975, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24252 * 22668.", "answer": 549744336, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29529 * 20958.", "answer": 618868782, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22394 * 25237.", "answer": 565157378, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27553 * 22219.", "answer": 612200107, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25855 * 22675.", "answer": 586262125, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20866 * 24467.", "answer": 510528422, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25917 * 26873.", "answer": 696467541, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25832 * 20798.", "answer": 537253936, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24749 * 24778.", "answer": 613230722, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28677 * 21258.", "answer": 609615666, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28419 * 23175.", "answer": 658610325, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23002 * 21548.", "answer": 495647096, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29810 * 22738.", "answer": 677819780, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28908 * 25285.", "answer": 730938780, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25180 * 24932.", "answer": 627787760, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24447 * 25939.", "answer": 634130733, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21570 * 28755.", "answer": 620245350, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29503 * 25761.", "answer": 760026783, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22354 * 20211.", "answer": 451796694, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22243 * 28489.", "answer": 633680827, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24610 * 26111.", "answer": 642591710, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27944 * 26750.", "answer": 747502000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25575 * 22671.", "answer": 579810825, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21678 * 23569.", "answer": 510928782, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22532 * 28247.", "answer": 636461404, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23622 * 23087.", "answer": 545361114, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29153 * 28612.", "answer": 834125636, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28717 * 29029.", "answer": 833625793, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21867 * 26837.", "answer": 586844679, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27544 * 21251.", "answer": 585337544, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21909 * 22150.", "answer": 485284350, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20284 * 27856.", "answer": 565031104, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25705 * 25104.", "answer": 645298320, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25940 * 22277.", "answer": 577865380, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27240 * 29791.", "answer": 811506840, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28570 * 25604.", "answer": 731506280, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22821 * 24991.", "answer": 570319611, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20471 * 21943.", "answer": 449195153, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23643 * 22108.", "answer": 522699444, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22332 * 23712.", "answer": 529536384, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25036 * 22053.", "answer": 552118908, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23438 * 22133.", "answer": 518753254, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21287 * 26960.", "answer": 573897520, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21830 * 21273.", "answer": 464389590, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20308 * 27934.", "answer": 567283672, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27065 * 20696.", "answer": 560137240, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23217 * 21766.", "answer": 505341222, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20537 * 28412.", "answer": 583497244, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29718 * 20971.", "answer": 623216178, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27685 * 21948.", "answer": 607630380, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24145 * 20709.", "answer": 500018805, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21085 * 24942.", "answer": 525902070, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20168 * 21581.", "answer": 435245608, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22028 * 29859.", "answer": 657734052, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23365 * 29627.", "answer": 692234855, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23277 * 23027.", "answer": 535999479, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25759 * 20479.", "answer": 527518561, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21487 * 22384.", "answer": 480965008, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24544 * 29498.", "answer": 723998912, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25698 * 25770.", "answer": 662237460, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22630 * 28202.", "answer": 638211260, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23962 * 28272.", "answer": 677453664, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29342 * 21119.", "answer": 619673698, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21623 * 29472.", "answer": 637273056, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20229 * 28664.", "answer": 579844056, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23555 * 23138.", "answer": 545015590, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24617 * 22814.", "answer": 561612238, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28800 * 20070.", "answer": 578016000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21616 * 23506.", "answer": 508105696, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28260 * 27777.", "answer": 784978020, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26004 * 29656.", "answer": 771174624, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23033 * 27203.", "answer": 626566699, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21758 * 22963.", "answer": 499628954, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25813 * 26219.", "answer": 676791047, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26948 * 23510.", "answer": 633547480, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28425 * 23728.", "answer": 674468400, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26677 * 21848.", "answer": 582839096, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25149 * 22025.", "answer": 553906725, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27633 * 21807.", "answer": 602592831, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28515 * 22226.", "answer": 633774390, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28123 * 25918.", "answer": 728891914, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24723 * 29128.", "answer": 720131544, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20665 * 21347.", "answer": 441135755, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25375 * 28088.", "answer": 712733000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21895 * 26304.", "answer": 575926080, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24646 * 27486.", "answer": 677419956, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29836 * 25111.", "answer": 749211796, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27273 * 23700.", "answer": 646370100, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29075 * 26672.", "answer": 775488400, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24761 * 27011.", "answer": 668819371, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23093 * 21140.", "answer": 488186020, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27793 * 26020.", "answer": 723173860, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22937 * 20209.", "answer": 463533833, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28055 * 21723.", "answer": 609438765, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26494 * 27177.", "answer": 720027438, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28563 * 21392.", "answer": 611019696, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21953 * 22348.", "answer": 490605644, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26468 * 26563.", "answer": 703069484, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29675 * 21666.", "answer": 642938550, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22764 * 21060.", "answer": 479409840, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25959 * 23261.", "answer": 603832299, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25548 * 23281.", "answer": 594782988, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29747 * 26623.", "answer": 791954381, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22011 * 23815.", "answer": 524191965, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26958 * 28177.", "answer": 759595566, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24563 * 29534.", "answer": 725443642, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29726 * 24472.", "answer": 727454672, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26557 * 25834.", "answer": 686073538, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27795 * 29882.", "answer": 830570190, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26626 * 27938.", "answer": 743877188, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28379 * 24569.", "answer": 697243651, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22414 * 27448.", "answer": 615219472, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21770 * 22001.", "answer": 478961770, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24107 * 28017.", "answer": 675405819, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28147 * 23781.", "answer": 669363807, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22205 * 20486.", "answer": 454891630, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21631 * 20865.", "answer": 451330815, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21117 * 28161.", "answer": 594675837, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20438 * 22934.", "answer": 468725092, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26269 * 29905.", "answer": 785574445, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25356 * 22502.", "answer": 570560712, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24960 * 21578.", "answer": 538586880, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21253 * 28518.", "answer": 606093054, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28064 * 27635.", "answer": 775548640, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 23308 * 24809.", "answer": 578248172, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28157 * 28032.", "answer": 789297024, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28270 * 24287.", "answer": 686593490, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28887 * 25629.", "answer": 740344923, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28856 * 28955.", "answer": 835525480, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20289 * 20517.", "answer": 416269413, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27051 * 21951.", "answer": 593796501, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26285 * 27374.", "answer": 719525590, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25153 * 26165.", "answer": 658128245, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27250 * 27531.", "answer": 750219750, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20589 * 20538.", "answer": 422856882, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22897 * 29120.", "answer": 666760640, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24965 * 22689.", "answer": 566430885, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28052 * 27056.", "answer": 758974912, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22203 * 25119.", "answer": 557717157, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26374 * 27986.", "answer": 738102764, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21792 * 29320.", "answer": 638941440, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28037 * 29073.", "answer": 815119701, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28837 * 29375.", "answer": 847086875, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 27697 * 27797.", "answer": 769893509, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29211 * 22560.", "answer": 659000160, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28301 * 20913.", "answer": 591858813, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26412 * 24315.", "answer": 642207780, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 28105 * 29683.", "answer": 834240715, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26189 * 25779.", "answer": 675126231, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 24660 * 25250.", "answer": 622665000, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 21006 * 20461.", "answer": 429803766, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 29674 * 20739.", "answer": 615409086, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 22100 * 26003.", "answer": 574666300, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 25715 * 29567.", "answer": 760315405, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 20440 * 25591.", "answer": 523080040, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 26235 * 21594.", "answer": 566518590, "range": "[20000, 29999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37014 * 35654.", "answer": 1319697156, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35855 * 36749.", "answer": 1317635395, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35755 * 30924.", "answer": 1105687620, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34001 * 34056.", "answer": 1157938056, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33844 * 35113.", "answer": 1188364372, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39708 * 31391.", "answer": 1246473828, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31073 * 34995.", "answer": 1087399635, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31875 * 35531.", "answer": 1132550625, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32781 * 30322.", "answer": 993985482, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38821 * 35343.", "answer": 1372050603, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30612 * 37551.", "answer": 1149511212, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36921 * 39306.", "answer": 1451216826, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38433 * 36900.", "answer": 1418177700, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34368 * 30334.", "answer": 1042518912, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37695 * 39633.", "answer": 1493965935, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30364 * 35185.", "answer": 1068357340, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36188 * 39344.", "answer": 1423780672, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36394 * 35282.", "answer": 1284053108, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39380 * 31601.", "answer": 1244447380, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38001 * 31639.", "answer": 1202313639, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33373 * 35504.", "answer": 1184874992, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38138 * 38237.", "answer": 1458282706, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35563 * 32730.", "answer": 1163976990, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34907 * 35952.", "answer": 1254976464, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37143 * 33305.", "answer": 1237047615, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38142 * 31234.", "answer": 1191327228, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38779 * 33507.", "answer": 1299367953, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34708 * 34344.", "answer": 1192011552, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30778 * 34871.", "answer": 1073259638, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39396 * 36586.", "answer": 1441342056, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33700 * 31506.", "answer": 1061752200, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39473 * 31552.", "answer": 1245452096, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39697 * 35518.", "answer": 1409958046, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34478 * 31102.", "answer": 1072334756, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39280 * 38700.", "answer": 1520136000, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37786 * 36997.", "answer": 1397968642, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33436 * 35690.", "answer": 1193330840, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31256 * 34945.", "answer": 1092240920, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38268 * 34913.", "answer": 1336050684, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37092 * 38846.", "answer": 1440875832, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35133 * 33278.", "answer": 1169155974, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36788 * 36591.", "answer": 1346109708, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34116 * 38443.", "answer": 1311521388, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37425 * 38971.", "answer": 1458489675, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32958 * 30304.", "answer": 998759232, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38457 * 33056.", "answer": 1271234592, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39451 * 38178.", "answer": 1506160278, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33489 * 37656.", "answer": 1261061784, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34389 * 38728.", "answer": 1331817192, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37106 * 39275.", "answer": 1457338150, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30981 * 38556.", "answer": 1194503436, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33287 * 35968.", "answer": 1197266816, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37577 * 32420.", "answer": 1218246340, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33938 * 32465.", "answer": 1101797170, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34919 * 37133.", "answer": 1296647227, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36721 * 35220.", "answer": 1293313620, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31055 * 33335.", "answer": 1035218425, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36757 * 34373.", "answer": 1263448361, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34702 * 32631.", "answer": 1132360962, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34201 * 39850.", "answer": 1362909850, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33868 * 36649.", "answer": 1241228332, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33907 * 31860.", "answer": 1080277020, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32456 * 33144.", "answer": 1075721664, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30453 * 34023.", "answer": 1036102419, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35087 * 37604.", "answer": 1319411548, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37952 * 39172.", "answer": 1486655744, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37145 * 36914.", "answer": 1371170530, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30606 * 33309.", "answer": 1019455254, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32610 * 34468.", "answer": 1124001480, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32235 * 30477.", "answer": 982426095, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34233 * 34551.", "answer": 1182784383, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39022 * 32883.", "answer": 1283160426, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30691 * 37960.", "answer": 1165030360, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30326 * 30906.", "answer": 937255356, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31375 * 35143.", "answer": 1102611625, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39856 * 34882.", "answer": 1390256992, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31041 * 36668.", "answer": 1138211388, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35954 * 31479.", "answer": 1131795966, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36502 * 32302.", "answer": 1179087604, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33867 * 31833.", "answer": 1078088211, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39354 * 38196.", "answer": 1503165384, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31976 * 38551.", "answer": 1232706776, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39509 * 38605.", "answer": 1525244945, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34125 * 38133.", "answer": 1301288625, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31478 * 33900.", "answer": 1067104200, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39827 * 32003.", "answer": 1274583481, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35134 * 35395.", "answer": 1243567930, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39573 * 36388.", "answer": 1439982324, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33865 * 36928.", "answer": 1250566720, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33571 * 32363.", "answer": 1086458273, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31750 * 32869.", "answer": 1043590750, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33507 * 34498.", "answer": 1155924486, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37200 * 36690.", "answer": 1364868000, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34166 * 39658.", "answer": 1354955228, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30916 * 38034.", "answer": 1175859144, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38740 * 36139.", "answer": 1400024860, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31850 * 35185.", "answer": 1120642250, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38941 * 36943.", "answer": 1438597363, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37780 * 34036.", "answer": 1285880080, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34550 * 32374.", "answer": 1118521700, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35947 * 37786.", "answer": 1358293342, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36025 * 35049.", "answer": 1262640225, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30345 * 39925.", "answer": 1211524125, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30570 * 30895.", "answer": 944460150, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33926 * 34144.", "answer": 1158369344, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39055 * 36302.", "answer": 1417774610, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35067 * 35945.", "answer": 1260483315, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31999 * 38763.", "answer": 1240377237, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33872 * 37248.", "answer": 1261664256, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36364 * 30128.", "answer": 1095574592, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36438 * 34186.", "answer": 1245669468, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34929 * 31478.", "answer": 1099495062, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33857 * 34872.", "answer": 1180661304, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33446 * 32625.", "answer": 1091175750, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37190 * 35196.", "answer": 1308939240, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36656 * 30555.", "answer": 1120024080, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34489 * 31312.", "answer": 1079919568, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38055 * 37718.", "answer": 1435358490, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36765 * 35451.", "answer": 1303356015, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36920 * 31644.", "answer": 1168296480, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32627 * 34275.", "answer": 1118290425, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38295 * 31087.", "answer": 1190476665, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35764 * 36895.", "answer": 1319512780, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39865 * 38973.", "answer": 1553658645, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35353 * 37426.", "answer": 1323121378, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30448 * 30853.", "answer": 939412144, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33010 * 37264.", "answer": 1230084640, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32229 * 30050.", "answer": 968481450, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36564 * 33278.", "answer": 1216776792, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35006 * 35140.", "answer": 1230110840, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39434 * 31347.", "answer": 1236137598, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31815 * 32585.", "answer": 1036691775, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34089 * 38460.", "answer": 1311062940, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32131 * 39732.", "answer": 1276628892, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36722 * 35233.", "answer": 1293826226, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37397 * 37837.", "answer": 1414990289, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32187 * 34270.", "answer": 1103048490, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32842 * 39716.", "answer": 1304352872, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35367 * 34616.", "answer": 1224264072, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33254 * 31382.", "answer": 1043577028, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36791 * 36022.", "answer": 1325285402, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32980 * 36447.", "answer": 1202022060, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36182 * 39345.", "answer": 1423580790, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33677 * 30339.", "answer": 1021726503, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30376 * 39150.", "answer": 1189220400, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33747 * 31457.", "answer": 1061579379, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37576 * 33248.", "answer": 1249326848, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34289 * 32764.", "answer": 1123444796, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30815 * 36570.", "answer": 1126904550, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37027 * 39836.", "answer": 1475007572, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34262 * 32445.", "answer": 1111630590, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31459 * 36028.", "answer": 1133404852, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32787 * 39293.", "answer": 1288299591, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31922 * 30231.", "answer": 965033982, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38615 * 37129.", "answer": 1433736335, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37433 * 38096.", "answer": 1426047568, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31941 * 33677.", "answer": 1075677057, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33328 * 33121.", "answer": 1103856688, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34361 * 34717.", "answer": 1192910837, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38096 * 36259.", "answer": 1381322864, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32133 * 37066.", "answer": 1191041778, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33385 * 39831.", "answer": 1329757935, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33531 * 34636.", "answer": 1161379716, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33102 * 36853.", "answer": 1219908006, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32955 * 36693.", "answer": 1209217815, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32391 * 30471.", "answer": 986986161, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34754 * 34289.", "answer": 1191679906, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33858 * 37388.", "answer": 1265882904, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34068 * 36056.", "answer": 1228355808, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39550 * 37506.", "answer": 1483362300, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31404 * 30169.", "answer": 947427276, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37682 * 32182.", "answer": 1212682124, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35296 * 36513.", "answer": 1288762848, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33476 * 36283.", "answer": 1214609708, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36935 * 39784.", "answer": 1469422040, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34198 * 31196.", "answer": 1066840808, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31561 * 39125.", "answer": 1234824125, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30962 * 30853.", "answer": 955270586, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35453 * 33847.", "answer": 1199977691, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37715 * 35804.", "answer": 1350347860, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39934 * 39801.", "answer": 1589413134, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30745 * 30087.", "answer": 925024815, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34155 * 38266.", "answer": 1306975230, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36241 * 34956.", "answer": 1266840396, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36466 * 36076.", "answer": 1315547416, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32166 * 39167.", "answer": 1259845722, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30673 * 39510.", "answer": 1211890230, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32938 * 34264.", "answer": 1128587632, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32783 * 38253.", "answer": 1254048099, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38074 * 35557.", "answer": 1353797218, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37669 * 32161.", "answer": 1211472709, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31468 * 35198.", "answer": 1107610664, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38690 * 37093.", "answer": 1435128170, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32323 * 34266.", "answer": 1107579918, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31914 * 35132.", "answer": 1121202648, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30723 * 32095.", "answer": 986054685, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38179 * 34603.", "answer": 1321107937, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35907 * 37046.", "answer": 1330210722, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34635 * 34312.", "answer": 1188396120, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34321 * 38470.", "answer": 1320328870, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35128 * 37139.", "answer": 1304618792, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32703 * 35169.", "answer": 1150131807, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38049 * 32478.", "answer": 1235755422, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39104 * 37208.", "answer": 1454981632, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30871 * 33095.", "answer": 1021675745, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32435 * 30894.", "answer": 1002046890, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33766 * 33000.", "answer": 1114278000, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30587 * 37704.", "answer": 1153252248, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34263 * 32679.", "answer": 1119680577, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37653 * 37150.", "answer": 1398808950, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31900 * 38108.", "answer": 1215645200, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30668 * 37233.", "answer": 1141861644, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35841 * 39189.", "answer": 1404572949, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37949 * 37499.", "answer": 1423049551, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38077 * 31843.", "answer": 1212485911, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32425 * 32025.", "answer": 1038410625, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35727 * 31533.", "answer": 1126579491, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33337 * 34654.", "answer": 1155260398, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32959 * 32757.", "answer": 1079637963, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38335 * 34469.", "answer": 1321369115, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39228 * 39595.", "answer": 1553232660, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33479 * 39560.", "answer": 1324429240, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30067 * 38618.", "answer": 1161127406, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39351 * 32958.", "answer": 1296930258, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36822 * 31258.", "answer": 1150982076, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34033 * 38161.", "answer": 1298733313, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31545 * 35384.", "answer": 1116188280, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30425 * 34657.", "answer": 1054439225, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31998 * 36458.", "answer": 1166583084, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36120 * 39672.", "answer": 1432952640, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31737 * 35300.", "answer": 1120316100, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32519 * 30473.", "answer": 990951487, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31328 * 37540.", "answer": 1176053120, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37861 * 37439.", "answer": 1417477979, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34412 * 39735.", "answer": 1367360820, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30095 * 35397.", "answer": 1065272715, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30718 * 37423.", "answer": 1149559714, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35323 * 39325.", "answer": 1389076975, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32118 * 33463.", "answer": 1074764634, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30797 * 34635.", "answer": 1066654095, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35294 * 30909.", "answer": 1090902246, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31158 * 38964.", "answer": 1214040312, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39867 * 36248.", "answer": 1445099016, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31516 * 36534.", "answer": 1151405544, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34180 * 32916.", "answer": 1125068880, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33933 * 36535.", "answer": 1239742155, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31461 * 30336.", "answer": 954400896, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33411 * 32669.", "answer": 1091503959, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36365 * 36592.", "answer": 1330668080, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34668 * 32525.", "answer": 1127576700, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31975 * 34891.", "answer": 1115639725, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38042 * 37083.", "answer": 1410711486, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35080 * 39887.", "answer": 1399235960, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32151 * 35882.", "answer": 1153642182, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31574 * 36020.", "answer": 1137295480, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38399 * 33274.", "answer": 1277688326, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38021 * 37298.", "answer": 1418107258, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36358 * 37805.", "answer": 1374514190, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34398 * 39225.", "answer": 1349261550, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39835 * 36931.", "answer": 1471146385, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31478 * 36922.", "answer": 1162230716, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36033 * 33053.", "answer": 1190998749, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37112 * 36979.", "answer": 1372364648, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31522 * 30662.", "answer": 966527564, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38410 * 35599.", "answer": 1367357590, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37594 * 33673.", "answer": 1265902762, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32540 * 38115.", "answer": 1240262100, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38638 * 38596.", "answer": 1491272248, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31375 * 34762.", "answer": 1090657750, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37671 * 37165.", "answer": 1400042715, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31297 * 37825.", "answer": 1183809025, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34921 * 32434.", "answer": 1132627714, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32093 * 34921.", "answer": 1120719653, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34073 * 38570.", "answer": 1314195610, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37007 * 34841.", "answer": 1289360887, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39314 * 30781.", "answer": 1210124234, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39027 * 31253.", "answer": 1219710831, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30738 * 38411.", "answer": 1180677318, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31763 * 38366.", "answer": 1218619258, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36961 * 36766.", "answer": 1358908126, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31548 * 37612.", "answer": 1186583376, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39313 * 34151.", "answer": 1342578263, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35823 * 34175.", "answer": 1224251025, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39593 * 31339.", "answer": 1240805027, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38248 * 30266.", "answer": 1157613968, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31866 * 37583.", "answer": 1197619878, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32941 * 32985.", "answer": 1086558885, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36438 * 30741.", "answer": 1120140558, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31364 * 36819.", "answer": 1154791116, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34876 * 35143.", "answer": 1225647268, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39620 * 37454.", "answer": 1483927480, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37371 * 34342.", "answer": 1283394882, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35592 * 33066.", "answer": 1176885072, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33458 * 33032.", "answer": 1105184656, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31281 * 39896.", "answer": 1247986776, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34248 * 31742.", "answer": 1087100016, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37107 * 38755.", "answer": 1438081785, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30293 * 30095.", "answer": 911667835, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36470 * 31911.", "answer": 1163794170, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30217 * 32813.", "answer": 991510421, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37817 * 37539.", "answer": 1419612363, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36637 * 39861.", "answer": 1460387457, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37974 * 34961.", "answer": 1327609014, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35910 * 36471.", "answer": 1309673610, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34958 * 31435.", "answer": 1098904730, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32049 * 32213.", "answer": 1032394437, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30227 * 33126.", "answer": 1001299602, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31833 * 30260.", "answer": 963266580, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33083 * 30439.", "answer": 1007013437, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33428 * 37882.", "answer": 1266319496, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32378 * 33961.", "answer": 1099589258, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37139 * 38824.", "answer": 1441884536, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33127 * 31410.", "answer": 1040519070, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34930 * 37592.", "answer": 1313088560, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32427 * 37765.", "answer": 1224605655, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36912 * 30357.", "answer": 1120537584, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31908 * 32721.", "answer": 1044061668, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32497 * 37295.", "answer": 1211975615, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37947 * 37724.", "answer": 1431512628, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30321 * 37364.", "answer": 1132913844, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39588 * 33975.", "answer": 1345002300, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33298 * 34830.", "answer": 1159769340, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39329 * 36418.", "answer": 1432283522, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30834 * 35469.", "answer": 1093651146, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30129 * 31682.", "answer": 954546978, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37074 * 36810.", "answer": 1364693940, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38121 * 39480.", "answer": 1505017080, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39762 * 39081.", "answer": 1553938722, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34764 * 30606.", "answer": 1063986984, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37987 * 36548.", "answer": 1388348876, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37964 * 38410.", "answer": 1458197240, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39683 * 37993.", "answer": 1507676219, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33799 * 30994.", "answer": 1047566206, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38655 * 30311.", "answer": 1171671705, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36914 * 39443.", "answer": 1455998902, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35174 * 39064.", "answer": 1374037136, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31040 * 34388.", "answer": 1067403520, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36834 * 37755.", "answer": 1390667670, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31915 * 38106.", "answer": 1216152990, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35681 * 37345.", "answer": 1332506945, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37147 * 30340.", "answer": 1127039980, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32643 * 34718.", "answer": 1133299674, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33149 * 37688.", "answer": 1249319512, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35633 * 37178.", "answer": 1324763674, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33802 * 38317.", "answer": 1295191234, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33599 * 39628.", "answer": 1331461172, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35556 * 39864.", "answer": 1417404384, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37675 * 32148.", "answer": 1211175900, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34806 * 36395.", "answer": 1266764370, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36829 * 35902.", "answer": 1322234758, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37738 * 32654.", "answer": 1232296652, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33394 * 34627.", "answer": 1156334038, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31412 * 37911.", "answer": 1190860332, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32115 * 32839.", "answer": 1054624485, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33268 * 32561.", "answer": 1083239348, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39924 * 38063.", "answer": 1519627212, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31653 * 36815.", "answer": 1165305195, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38089 * 34975.", "answer": 1332162775, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33845 * 33431.", "answer": 1131472195, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39123 * 30770.", "answer": 1203814710, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30297 * 35878.", "answer": 1086995766, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34273 * 35849.", "answer": 1228652777, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32598 * 32862.", "answer": 1071235476, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38248 * 30523.", "answer": 1167443704, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31043 * 35533.", "answer": 1103050919, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37055 * 31867.", "answer": 1180831685, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33714 * 31977.", "answer": 1078072578, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39207 * 33671.", "answer": 1320138897, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37968 * 34224.", "answer": 1299416832, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35575 * 35820.", "answer": 1274296500, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30764 * 39126.", "answer": 1203672264, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34382 * 32476.", "answer": 1116589832, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38444 * 39900.", "answer": 1533915600, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31706 * 30826.", "answer": 977369156, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37173 * 37489.", "answer": 1393578597, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31817 * 31734.", "answer": 1009680678, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39988 * 31669.", "answer": 1266379972, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39215 * 30687.", "answer": 1203390705, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38311 * 31727.", "answer": 1215493097, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32736 * 31934.", "answer": 1045391424, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33365 * 35925.", "answer": 1198637625, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32572 * 34786.", "answer": 1133049592, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37233 * 38288.", "answer": 1425577104, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38165 * 31626.", "answer": 1207006290, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32527 * 35959.", "answer": 1169638393, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35482 * 32257.", "answer": 1144542874, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32014 * 33307.", "answer": 1066290298, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37194 * 36811.", "answer": 1369148334, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30107 * 34019.", "answer": 1024210033, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37760 * 35592.", "answer": 1343953920, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34698 * 38274.", "answer": 1328031252, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32805 * 31396.", "answer": 1029945780, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34358 * 36101.", "answer": 1240358158, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36799 * 35908.", "answer": 1321378492, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34021 * 32483.", "answer": 1105104143, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38677 * 36909.", "answer": 1427529393, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33738 * 32260.", "answer": 1088387880, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37025 * 36773.", "answer": 1361520325, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36706 * 37516.", "answer": 1377062296, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38456 * 35927.", "answer": 1381608712, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30487 * 37251.", "answer": 1135671237, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32385 * 30162.", "answer": 976796370, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38476 * 31140.", "answer": 1198142640, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31389 * 35542.", "answer": 1115627838, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35157 * 36580.", "answer": 1286043060, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32692 * 37111.", "answer": 1213232812, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31007 * 36443.", "answer": 1129988101, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30607 * 32473.", "answer": 993901111, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39413 * 30947.", "answer": 1219714111, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38516 * 34845.", "answer": 1342090020, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36869 * 36586.", "answer": 1348889234, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39070 * 34986.", "answer": 1366903020, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35139 * 35638.", "answer": 1252283682, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30129 * 34583.", "answer": 1041951207, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38647 * 32406.", "answer": 1252394682, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36618 * 37310.", "answer": 1366217580, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33360 * 38919.", "answer": 1298337840, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37244 * 35656.", "answer": 1327972064, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36627 * 33232.", "answer": 1217188464, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34940 * 31380.", "answer": 1096417200, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30605 * 38805.", "answer": 1187627025, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35480 * 36389.", "answer": 1291081720, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32064 * 38527.", "answer": 1235329728, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38860 * 34651.", "answer": 1346537860, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33501 * 31520.", "answer": 1055951520, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38383 * 39040.", "answer": 1498472320, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35115 * 38541.", "answer": 1353367215, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35582 * 32621.", "answer": 1160720422, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30383 * 30456.", "answer": 925344648, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38846 * 39707.", "answer": 1542458122, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34238 * 33954.", "answer": 1162517052, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34979 * 36926.", "answer": 1291634554, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38278 * 31809.", "answer": 1217584902, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30982 * 36110.", "answer": 1118760020, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34255 * 38314.", "answer": 1312446070, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35807 * 32028.", "answer": 1146826596, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30782 * 32043.", "answer": 986347626, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37352 * 34881.", "answer": 1302875112, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39378 * 30085.", "answer": 1184687130, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37424 * 35553.", "answer": 1330535472, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33868 * 39528.", "answer": 1338734304, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39266 * 38737.", "answer": 1521047042, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39757 * 33831.", "answer": 1345019067, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35739 * 34902.", "answer": 1247362578, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34661 * 39384.", "answer": 1365088824, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32293 * 36187.", "answer": 1168586791, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38514 * 34057.", "answer": 1311671298, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31724 * 35371.", "answer": 1122109604, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38461 * 39541.", "answer": 1520786401, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33154 * 35919.", "answer": 1190858526, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37443 * 31605.", "answer": 1183386015, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32401 * 36974.", "answer": 1197994574, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36751 * 31342.", "answer": 1151849842, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31511 * 31018.", "answer": 977408198, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36961 * 32130.", "answer": 1187556930, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37802 * 33519.", "answer": 1267085238, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37309 * 31279.", "answer": 1166988211, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36050 * 38622.", "answer": 1392323100, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36598 * 39637.", "answer": 1450634926, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39158 * 38502.", "answer": 1507661316, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36468 * 34320.", "answer": 1251581760, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39573 * 38172.", "answer": 1510580556, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36937 * 37210.", "answer": 1374425770, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38020 * 36830.", "answer": 1400276600, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32668 * 32364.", "answer": 1057267152, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38286 * 32082.", "answer": 1228291452, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37942 * 37499.", "answer": 1422787058, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32119 * 38408.", "answer": 1233626552, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38669 * 31934.", "answer": 1234855846, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 33483 * 37461.", "answer": 1254306663, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37755 * 30534.", "answer": 1152811170, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32569 * 39159.", "answer": 1275369471, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36051 * 31945.", "answer": 1151649195, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39856 * 36694.", "answer": 1462476064, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31807 * 31980.", "answer": 1017187860, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36055 * 39367.", "answer": 1419377185, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34744 * 30659.", "answer": 1065216296, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38565 * 32511.", "answer": 1253786715, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31929 * 36086.", "answer": 1152189894, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34995 * 36135.", "answer": 1264544325, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34968 * 34816.", "answer": 1217445888, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37961 * 30458.", "answer": 1156216138, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32340 * 32328.", "answer": 1045487520, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39660 * 36910.", "answer": 1463850600, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30797 * 34999.", "answer": 1077864203, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 34644 * 33532.", "answer": 1161682608, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32999 * 38008.", "answer": 1254225992, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 30034 * 32004.", "answer": 961208136, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38970 * 35712.", "answer": 1391696640, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31106 * 30732.", "answer": 955949592, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 36841 * 37883.", "answer": 1395647603, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39389 * 35074.", "answer": 1381529786, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 39269 * 37411.", "answer": 1469092559, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 35534 * 36181.", "answer": 1285655654, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37786 * 39923.", "answer": 1508530478, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32175 * 32269.", "answer": 1038255075, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 38270 * 37551.", "answer": 1437076770, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 37371 * 37357.", "answer": 1396068447, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 32440 * 35328.", "answer": 1146040320, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 31463 * 36711.", "answer": 1155038193, "range": "[30000, 39999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46344 * 43814.", "answer": 2030516016, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46478 * 45554.", "answer": 2117258812, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48863 * 40750.", "answer": 1991167250, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47259 * 44544.", "answer": 2105104896, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41450 * 42713.", "answer": 1770453850, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40406 * 49371.", "answer": 1994884626, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45060 * 49192.", "answer": 2216591520, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42028 * 49164.", "answer": 2066264592, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41395 * 43152.", "answer": 1786277040, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48877 * 49451.", "answer": 2417016527, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40866 * 49342.", "answer": 2016410172, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48548 * 43103.", "answer": 2092564444, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47796 * 48235.", "answer": 2305440060, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40305 * 41970.", "answer": 1691600850, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48713 * 42944.", "answer": 2091931072, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40310 * 44504.", "answer": 1793956240, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43371 * 44018.", "answer": 1909104678, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49495 * 47278.", "answer": 2340024610, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41386 * 48741.", "answer": 2017195026, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49942 * 45249.", "answer": 2259825558, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46583 * 49648.", "answer": 2312752784, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40737 * 48052.", "answer": 1957494324, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40381 * 45569.", "answer": 1840121789, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47160 * 42957.", "answer": 2025852120, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46798 * 40394.", "answer": 1890358412, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48649 * 45199.", "answer": 2198886151, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46258 * 44213.", "answer": 2045204954, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41491 * 41878.", "answer": 1737560098, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41627 * 48876.", "answer": 2034561252, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42755 * 44675.", "answer": 1910079625, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42359 * 42992.", "answer": 1821098128, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44187 * 41468.", "answer": 1832346516, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42526 * 45026.", "answer": 1914775676, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46672 * 42772.", "answer": 1996254784, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40965 * 45329.", "answer": 1856902485, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42973 * 40445.", "answer": 1738042985, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40958 * 44882.", "answer": 1838276956, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46388 * 41617.", "answer": 1930529396, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45243 * 42334.", "answer": 1915317162, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46763 * 45311.", "answer": 2118878293, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44225 * 46152.", "answer": 2041072200, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41981 * 40849.", "answer": 1714881869, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43318 * 43925.", "answer": 1902743150, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49781 * 49601.", "answer": 2469187381, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43874 * 48076.", "answer": 2109286424, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48333 * 48264.", "answer": 2332743912, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46308 * 41885.", "answer": 1939610580, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44412 * 40993.", "answer": 1820581116, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45215 * 47615.", "answer": 2152912225, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49062 * 46669.", "answer": 2289674478, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41072 * 47932.", "answer": 1968663104, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40473 * 46676.", "answer": 1889117748, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43829 * 40305.", "answer": 1766527845, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44409 * 49077.", "answer": 2179460493, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49603 * 41663.", "answer": 2066609789, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44035 * 49088.", "answer": 2161590080, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42057 * 44990.", "answer": 1892144430, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49310 * 46664.", "answer": 2301001840, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47306 * 41374.", "answer": 1957238444, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48199 * 43333.", "answer": 2088607267, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42332 * 46116.", "answer": 1952182512, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48854 * 42755.", "answer": 2088752770, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44016 * 48806.", "answer": 2148244896, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46942 * 49095.", "answer": 2304617490, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47401 * 40684.", "answer": 1928462284, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40016 * 47612.", "answer": 1905241792, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44739 * 42742.", "answer": 1912234338, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40008 * 40985.", "answer": 1639727880, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47900 * 44477.", "answer": 2130448300, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49795 * 44110.", "answer": 2196457450, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46228 * 45757.", "answer": 2115254596, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43485 * 49587.", "answer": 2156290695, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48361 * 44609.", "answer": 2157335849, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40745 * 42644.", "answer": 1737529780, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48750 * 49225.", "answer": 2399718750, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41145 * 44925.", "answer": 1848439125, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41469 * 46476.", "answer": 1927313244, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42014 * 42288.", "answer": 1776688032, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49117 * 44578.", "answer": 2189537626, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47077 * 43454.", "answer": 2045683958, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48270 * 45215.", "answer": 2182528050, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45613 * 44282.", "answer": 2019834866, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47417 * 44473.", "answer": 2108776241, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44029 * 45269.", "answer": 1993148801, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45597 * 43450.", "answer": 1981189650, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47533 * 49822.", "answer": 2368189126, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45381 * 40260.", "answer": 1827039060, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42190 * 40033.", "answer": 1688992270, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49974 * 47807.", "answer": 2389107018, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40070 * 40156.", "answer": 1609050920, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42843 * 46769.", "answer": 2003724267, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49106 * 48011.", "answer": 2357628166, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46435 * 48816.", "answer": 2266770960, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41329 * 41270.", "answer": 1705647830, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48825 * 40507.", "answer": 1977754275, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47293 * 42022.", "answer": 1987346446, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45783 * 46166.", "answer": 2113617978, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49851 * 45864.", "answer": 2286366264, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46336 * 42903.", "answer": 1987953408, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40138 * 42044.", "answer": 1687562072, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47580 * 46069.", "answer": 2191963020, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43161 * 47283.", "answer": 2040781563, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40153 * 43629.", "answer": 1751835237, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40324 * 44606.", "answer": 1798692344, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45862 * 43137.", "answer": 1978349094, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41474 * 44967.", "answer": 1864961358, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43623 * 43838.", "answer": 1912345074, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48090 * 45947.", "answer": 2209591230, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40602 * 44599.", "answer": 1810808598, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48074 * 49929.", "answer": 2400286746, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43425 * 40116.", "answer": 1742037300, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43212 * 46489.", "answer": 2008882668, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41817 * 44544.", "answer": 1862696448, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49324 * 48197.", "answer": 2377268828, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48093 * 42793.", "answer": 2058043749, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49040 * 43174.", "answer": 2117252960, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49268 * 49879.", "answer": 2457438572, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49259 * 42875.", "answer": 2111979625, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41070 * 49636.", "answer": 2038550520, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42101 * 41065.", "answer": 1728877565, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42087 * 44253.", "answer": 1862476011, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49337 * 43734.", "answer": 2157704358, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48570 * 44494.", "answer": 2161073580, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43143 * 40378.", "answer": 1742028054, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48731 * 44143.", "answer": 2151132533, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49176 * 47437.", "answer": 2332761912, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40032 * 46997.", "answer": 1881383904, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40849 * 45292.", "answer": 1850132908, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47086 * 46666.", "answer": 2197315276, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44489 * 41994.", "answer": 1868271066, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48491 * 47644.", "answer": 2310305204, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48119 * 45922.", "answer": 2209720718, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48474 * 40712.", "answer": 1973473488, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43678 * 40769.", "answer": 1780708382, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44553 * 46882.", "answer": 2088733746, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48723 * 47354.", "answer": 2307228942, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45181 * 40084.", "answer": 1811035204, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46420 * 43188.", "answer": 2004786960, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45483 * 41340.", "answer": 1880267220, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49368 * 40415.", "answer": 1995207720, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43696 * 46943.", "answer": 2051221328, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41219 * 44095.", "answer": 1817551805, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43225 * 42694.", "answer": 1845448150, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45394 * 45092.", "answer": 2046906248, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41029 * 41584.", "answer": 1706149936, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40456 * 47863.", "answer": 1936345528, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47077 * 40393.", "answer": 1901581261, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49708 * 45477.", "answer": 2260570716, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44102 * 44049.", "answer": 1942648998, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41766 * 47759.", "answer": 1994702394, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43905 * 45583.", "answer": 2001321615, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40891 * 45465.", "answer": 1859109315, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48514 * 43878.", "answer": 2128697292, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41194 * 49829.", "answer": 2052655826, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47184 * 41567.", "answer": 1961297328, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47314 * 49485.", "answer": 2341333290, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42045 * 41401.", "answer": 1740705045, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40994 * 40546.", "answer": 1662142724, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46183 * 45132.", "answer": 2084331156, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41065 * 42089.", "answer": 1728384785, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41015 * 47240.", "answer": 1937548600, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40897 * 44939.", "answer": 1837870283, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47075 * 41077.", "answer": 1933699775, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41668 * 40914.", "answer": 1704804552, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49162 * 40855.", "answer": 2008513510, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44831 * 46249.", "answer": 2073388919, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46581 * 41570.", "answer": 1936372170, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46735 * 43819.", "answer": 2047880965, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49823 * 40173.", "answer": 2001539379, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47428 * 46290.", "answer": 2195442120, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47605 * 47014.", "answer": 2238101470, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41659 * 45564.", "answer": 1898150676, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40425 * 47439.", "answer": 1917721575, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48474 * 45377.", "answer": 2199604698, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49630 * 43153.", "answer": 2141683390, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41769 * 41682.", "answer": 1741015458, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40201 * 49751.", "answer": 2000039951, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41106 * 49713.", "answer": 2043502578, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43172 * 49391.", "answer": 2132308252, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42064 * 48337.", "answer": 2033247568, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44198 * 45822.", "answer": 2025240756, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46897 * 47887.", "answer": 2245756639, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47284 * 43046.", "answer": 2035387064, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43983 * 42255.", "answer": 1858501665, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40722 * 40991.", "answer": 1669235502, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42091 * 45106.", "answer": 1898556646, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49576 * 47140.", "answer": 2337012640, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48407 * 45861.", "answer": 2219993427, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45098 * 49562.", "answer": 2235147076, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48866 * 42385.", "answer": 2071185410, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42415 * 47692.", "answer": 2022856180, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45057 * 49884.", "answer": 2247623388, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45618 * 44768.", "answer": 2042226624, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46042 * 40132.", "answer": 1847757544, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48481 * 49608.", "answer": 2405045448, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42369 * 40939.", "answer": 1734544491, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43889 * 48308.", "answer": 2120189812, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49166 * 40894.", "answer": 2010594404, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46915 * 45633.", "answer": 2140872195, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43201 * 43282.", "answer": 1869825682, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43297 * 41120.", "answer": 1780372640, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45595 * 43102.", "answer": 1965235690, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47794 * 47657.", "answer": 2277718658, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49826 * 45425.", "answer": 2263346050, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49476 * 49274.", "answer": 2437880424, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45499 * 44909.", "answer": 2043314591, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46859 * 45384.", "answer": 2126648856, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42658 * 41717.", "answer": 1779563786, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47443 * 40691.", "answer": 1930503113, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48125 * 43594.", "answer": 2097961250, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40060 * 43654.", "answer": 1748779240, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43772 * 47643.", "answer": 2085429396, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43492 * 43916.", "answer": 1909994672, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47876 * 45431.", "answer": 2175054556, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46158 * 43363.", "answer": 2001549354, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46558 * 43018.", "answer": 2002832044, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40110 * 45944.", "answer": 1842813840, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40162 * 41208.", "answer": 1654995696, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45863 * 40491.", "answer": 1857038733, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49088 * 41887.", "answer": 2056149056, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42333 * 44760.", "answer": 1894825080, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47215 * 43185.", "answer": 2038979775, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49595 * 45896.", "answer": 2276212120, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40719 * 40486.", "answer": 1648549434, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43262 * 43241.", "answer": 1870692142, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44654 * 42853.", "answer": 1913557862, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43587 * 44292.", "answer": 1930555404, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42855 * 45567.", "answer": 1952773785, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49085 * 44029.", "answer": 2161163465, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42925 * 43211.", "answer": 1854832175, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40352 * 42884.", "answer": 1730455168, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44289 * 41657.", "answer": 1844946873, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40343 * 42248.", "answer": 1704411064, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46208 * 41818.", "answer": 1932326144, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45544 * 43444.", "answer": 1978613536, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44998 * 47474.", "answer": 2136235052, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43934 * 46056.", "answer": 2023424304, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46100 * 42807.", "answer": 1973402700, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48633 * 47106.", "answer": 2290906098, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41071 * 41941.", "answer": 1722558811, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42366 * 42142.", "answer": 1785387972, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43107 * 43140.", "answer": 1859635980, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48725 * 46196.", "answer": 2250900100, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46131 * 45209.", "answer": 2085536379, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49823 * 47037.", "answer": 2343524451, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44006 * 40756.", "answer": 1793508536, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49622 * 43098.", "answer": 2138608956, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48773 * 44819.", "answer": 2185957087, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42434 * 45368.", "answer": 1925145712, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44049 * 40872.", "answer": 1800370728, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44588 * 42071.", "answer": 1875861748, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48327 * 49569.", "answer": 2395521063, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48011 * 43428.", "answer": 2085021708, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41333 * 47711.", "answer": 1972038763, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41062 * 42743.", "answer": 1755113066, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48333 * 46358.", "answer": 2240621214, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48342 * 46131.", "answer": 2230064802, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48168 * 48501.", "answer": 2336196168, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47606 * 42932.", "answer": 2043820792, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45272 * 46125.", "answer": 2088171000, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48609 * 47918.", "answer": 2329246062, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48106 * 47762.", "answer": 2297638772, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44396 * 49522.", "answer": 2198578712, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46569 * 49567.", "answer": 2308285623, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40599 * 43394.", "answer": 1761753006, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43596 * 43325.", "answer": 1888796700, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47406 * 43840.", "answer": 2078279040, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46486 * 43581.", "answer": 2025906366, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45013 * 46963.", "answer": 2113945519, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46178 * 49361.", "answer": 2279392258, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42575 * 46129.", "answer": 1963942175, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44170 * 49020.", "answer": 2165213400, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41388 * 42200.", "answer": 1746573600, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41376 * 44834.", "answer": 1855051584, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47282 * 48500.", "answer": 2293177000, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45760 * 43771.", "answer": 2002960960, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49567 * 40674.", "answer": 2016088158, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47622 * 48392.", "answer": 2304523824, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45511 * 46981.", "answer": 2138152291, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47391 * 47660.", "answer": 2258655060, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47086 * 46700.", "answer": 2198916200, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46021 * 48151.", "answer": 2215957171, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45194 * 44473.", "answer": 2009912762, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46264 * 40404.", "answer": 1869250656, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42942 * 47236.", "answer": 2028408312, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43830 * 44351.", "answer": 1943904330, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41243 * 45883.", "answer": 1892352569, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41350 * 44825.", "answer": 1853513750, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48220 * 48401.", "answer": 2333896220, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48956 * 41280.", "answer": 2020903680, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44528 * 43731.", "answer": 1947253968, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41612 * 41942.", "answer": 1745290504, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41168 * 45902.", "answer": 1889693536, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40627 * 48946.", "answer": 1988529142, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43281 * 45468.", "answer": 1967900508, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43221 * 45394.", "answer": 1961974074, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44096 * 44959.", "answer": 1982512064, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44496 * 43123.", "answer": 1918801008, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49896 * 42258.", "answer": 2108505168, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48898 * 44278.", "answer": 2165105644, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40139 * 44906.", "answer": 1802481934, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44617 * 45679.", "answer": 2038059943, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46616 * 46647.", "answer": 2174496552, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49501 * 40194.", "answer": 1989643194, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47733 * 48399.", "answer": 2310229467, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42445 * 46512.", "answer": 1974201840, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43728 * 43717.", "answer": 1911656976, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43438 * 47773.", "answer": 2075163574, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43829 * 48451.", "answer": 2123558879, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49617 * 49054.", "answer": 2433912318, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47679 * 47559.", "answer": 2267565561, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45581 * 41406.", "answer": 1887326886, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45129 * 43077.", "answer": 1944021933, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47025 * 46843.", "answer": 2202792075, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43433 * 47187.", "answer": 2049472971, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47372 * 49149.", "answer": 2328286428, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40493 * 46139.", "answer": 1868306527, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42276 * 49461.", "answer": 2091013236, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42102 * 45006.", "answer": 1894842612, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40158 * 48188.", "answer": 1935133704, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45810 * 45567.", "answer": 2087424270, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43694 * 46867.", "answer": 2047806698, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46974 * 46608.", "answer": 2189364192, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48808 * 44909.", "answer": 2191918472, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45342 * 49616.", "answer": 2249688672, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40380 * 49299.", "answer": 1990693620, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40527 * 42279.", "answer": 1713441033, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42518 * 45410.", "answer": 1930742380, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49309 * 49879.", "answer": 2459483611, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49958 * 49402.", "answer": 2468025116, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46404 * 46247.", "answer": 2146045788, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43345 * 46400.", "answer": 2011208000, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41043 * 48757.", "answer": 2001133551, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46331 * 43085.", "answer": 1996171135, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47778 * 41779.", "answer": 1996117062, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45387 * 49330.", "answer": 2238940710, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47397 * 44991.", "answer": 2132438427, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41527 * 42808.", "answer": 1777687816, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41709 * 49058.", "answer": 2046160122, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42910 * 40525.", "answer": 1738927750, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49885 * 48005.", "answer": 2394729425, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40439 * 43058.", "answer": 1741222462, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43260 * 41138.", "answer": 1779629880, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46322 * 44650.", "answer": 2068277300, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43373 * 43818.", "answer": 1900518114, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44769 * 48591.", "answer": 2175370479, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41146 * 47449.", "answer": 1952336554, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40941 * 46039.", "answer": 1884882699, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48495 * 40180.", "answer": 1948529100, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42815 * 45353.", "answer": 1941788695, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46731 * 46407.", "answer": 2168645517, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42572 * 41814.", "answer": 1780105608, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42115 * 48789.", "answer": 2054748735, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46855 * 47835.", "answer": 2241308925, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41126 * 46373.", "answer": 1907135998, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43382 * 42128.", "answer": 1827596896, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43369 * 45075.", "answer": 1954857675, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47081 * 47778.", "answer": 2249436018, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42601 * 49891.", "answer": 2125406491, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49422 * 45084.", "answer": 2228141448, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49625 * 43325.", "answer": 2150003125, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48232 * 47519.", "answer": 2291936408, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44512 * 43304.", "answer": 1927547648, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40121 * 42337.", "answer": 1698602777, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47302 * 41048.", "answer": 1941652496, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46541 * 49909.", "answer": 2322814769, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44044 * 48615.", "answer": 2141199060, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45388 * 49326.", "answer": 2238808488, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48043 * 47539.", "answer": 2283916177, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47580 * 49439.", "answer": 2352307620, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40640 * 41492.", "answer": 1686234880, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44717 * 47476.", "answer": 2122984292, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45681 * 44873.", "answer": 2049843513, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46407 * 42869.", "answer": 1989421683, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46800 * 44081.", "answer": 2062990800, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42942 * 47079.", "answer": 2021666418, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47501 * 46302.", "answer": 2199391302, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43005 * 49316.", "answer": 2120834580, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41565 * 46447.", "answer": 1930569555, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40715 * 43927.", "answer": 1788487805, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42587 * 44485.", "answer": 1894482695, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48810 * 44782.", "answer": 2185809420, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41093 * 43559.", "answer": 1789969987, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48085 * 46738.", "answer": 2247396730, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49057 * 41986.", "answer": 2059707202, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46041 * 41253.", "answer": 1899329373, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41723 * 48264.", "answer": 2013718872, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45341 * 46719.", "answer": 2118286179, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47388 * 42700.", "answer": 2023467600, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44141 * 43397.", "answer": 1915586977, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48291 * 40731.", "answer": 1966940721, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47572 * 40437.", "answer": 1923668964, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41199 * 47567.", "answer": 1959712833, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46244 * 45630.", "answer": 2110113720, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46542 * 43185.", "answer": 2009916270, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46499 * 40618.", "answer": 1888696382, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40175 * 44105.", "answer": 1771918375, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41878 * 42236.", "answer": 1768759208, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45359 * 47606.", "answer": 2159360554, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47942 * 47558.", "answer": 2280025636, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41117 * 41352.", "answer": 1700270184, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48985 * 43969.", "answer": 2153821465, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47171 * 42297.", "answer": 1995191787, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47713 * 44573.", "answer": 2126711549, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42643 * 42794.", "answer": 1824864542, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40295 * 49944.", "answer": 2012493480, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41646 * 42903.", "answer": 1786738338, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44819 * 42034.", "answer": 1883921846, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48759 * 46403.", "answer": 2262563877, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42759 * 41271.", "answer": 1764706689, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40183 * 44476.", "answer": 1787179108, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42514 * 47219.", "answer": 2007468566, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45866 * 42915.", "answer": 1968339390, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43549 * 40564.", "answer": 1766521636, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48721 * 43541.", "answer": 2121361061, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47242 * 40782.", "answer": 1926623244, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48566 * 41684.", "answer": 2024425144, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46399 * 45051.", "answer": 2090321349, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47274 * 40858.", "answer": 1931521092, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49800 * 40076.", "answer": 1995784800, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40797 * 46183.", "answer": 1884127851, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43305 * 44091.", "answer": 1909360755, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46138 * 43908.", "answer": 2025827304, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43276 * 41497.", "answer": 1795824172, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40262 * 46908.", "answer": 1888609896, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40457 * 40238.", "answer": 1627908766, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45523 * 43148.", "answer": 1964226404, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41035 * 43613.", "answer": 1789659455, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41582 * 42750.", "answer": 1777630500, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42736 * 40721.", "answer": 1740252656, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46810 * 48396.", "answer": 2265416760, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41764 * 45359.", "answer": 1894373276, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45286 * 49208.", "answer": 2228433488, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43105 * 43393.", "answer": 1870455265, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48875 * 46472.", "answer": 2271319000, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47010 * 41979.", "answer": 1973432790, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43807 * 43502.", "answer": 1905692114, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41734 * 45842.", "answer": 1913170028, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45298 * 42844.", "answer": 1940747512, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40245 * 46588.", "answer": 1874934060, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45181 * 40196.", "answer": 1816095476, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46376 * 43485.", "answer": 2016660360, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47516 * 43606.", "answer": 2071982696, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41081 * 44562.", "answer": 1830651522, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46045 * 40719.", "answer": 1874906355, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41103 * 43580.", "answer": 1791268740, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46735 * 44940.", "answer": 2100270900, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49811 * 48185.", "answer": 2400143035, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41668 * 48784.", "answer": 2032731712, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49325 * 42809.", "answer": 2111553925, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44127 * 41552.", "answer": 1833565104, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49828 * 45314.", "answer": 2257905992, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46366 * 42177.", "answer": 1955578782, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45440 * 42872.", "answer": 1948103680, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45209 * 47899.", "answer": 2165465891, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41106 * 45490.", "answer": 1869911940, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40289 * 49970.", "answer": 2013241330, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49585 * 47354.", "answer": 2348048090, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46264 * 48372.", "answer": 2237882208, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43808 * 48248.", "answer": 2113648384, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49625 * 40217.", "answer": 1995768625, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43811 * 40347.", "answer": 1767642417, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42032 * 45060.", "answer": 1893961920, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43873 * 47020.", "answer": 2062908460, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43990 * 41300.", "answer": 1816787000, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40981 * 42253.", "answer": 1731570193, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46136 * 48171.", "answer": 2222417256, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44859 * 43309.", "answer": 1942798431, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42484 * 46156.", "answer": 1960891504, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43348 * 40621.", "answer": 1760839108, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43900 * 49798.", "answer": 2186132200, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47270 * 45385.", "answer": 2145348950, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 42199 * 44556.", "answer": 1880218644, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45202 * 40648.", "answer": 1837370896, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48533 * 46797.", "answer": 2271198801, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44726 * 40388.", "answer": 1806393688, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43752 * 45427.", "answer": 1987522104, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45615 * 43969.", "answer": 2005645935, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43372 * 48836.", "answer": 2118114992, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40885 * 44068.", "answer": 1801720180, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43644 * 49962.", "answer": 2180541528, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46250 * 48543.", "answer": 2245113750, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45269 * 43007.", "answer": 1946883883, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 47247 * 40099.", "answer": 1894557453, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41058 * 48055.", "answer": 1973042190, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41146 * 43153.", "answer": 1775573338, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 40853 * 42318.", "answer": 1728817254, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43345 * 42057.", "answer": 1822960665, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 41503 * 42845.", "answer": 1778196035, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49709 * 48992.", "answer": 2435343328, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43348 * 43871.", "answer": 1901720108, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 48313 * 41280.", "answer": 1994360640, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46983 * 47652.", "answer": 2238833916, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 45103 * 42689.", "answer": 1925401967, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43236 * 44012.", "answer": 1902902832, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 46947 * 42890.", "answer": 2013556830, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49926 * 44079.", "answer": 2200688154, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 44966 * 44675.", "answer": 2008856050, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 49444 * 47344.", "answer": 2340876736, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 43299 * 44454.", "answer": 1924813746, "range": "[40000, 49999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57883 * 51310.", "answer": 2969976730, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55891 * 56524.", "answer": 3159182884, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56188 * 52748.", "answer": 2963804624, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57712 * 57231.", "answer": 3302915472, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56925 * 58278.", "answer": 3317475150, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59984 * 57101.", "answer": 3425146384, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52553 * 57897.", "answer": 3042661041, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50324 * 56249.", "answer": 2830674676, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57002 * 51363.", "answer": 2927793726, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54918 * 59751.", "answer": 3281405418, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58801 * 52503.", "answer": 3087228903, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59057 * 52878.", "answer": 3122816046, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54215 * 56233.", "answer": 3048672095, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57596 * 55011.", "answer": 3168413556, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57431 * 54640.", "answer": 3138029840, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56146 * 59210.", "answer": 3324404660, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59929 * 57878.", "answer": 3468570662, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51178 * 55459.", "answer": 2838280702, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52238 * 57688.", "answer": 3013505744, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53206 * 52535.", "answer": 2795177210, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53106 * 50068.", "answer": 2658911208, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50210 * 58203.", "answer": 2922372630, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56131 * 58051.", "answer": 3258460681, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56628 * 56812.", "answer": 3217149936, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56465 * 56113.", "answer": 3168420545, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56292 * 58020.", "answer": 3266061840, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55043 * 59638.", "answer": 3282654434, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51167 * 56697.", "answer": 2901015399, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50636 * 52039.", "answer": 2635046804, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56304 * 59266.", "answer": 3336912864, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52660 * 53182.", "answer": 2800564120, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57148 * 54182.", "answer": 3096392936, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55711 * 58349.", "answer": 3250681139, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58005 * 56032.", "answer": 3250136160, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50945 * 56313.", "answer": 2868865785, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56947 * 54043.", "answer": 3077586721, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53970 * 57827.", "answer": 3120923190, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50565 * 55921.", "answer": 2827645365, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50462 * 52422.", "answer": 2645318964, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54281 * 59919.", "answer": 3252463239, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57462 * 52414.", "answer": 3011813268, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54166 * 54053.", "answer": 2927834798, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59865 * 59475.", "answer": 3560470875, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52644 * 50202.", "answer": 2642834088, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51912 * 51512.", "answer": 2674090944, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56297 * 56515.", "answer": 3181624955, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59603 * 51316.", "answer": 3058587548, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58495 * 53093.", "answer": 3105675035, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56929 * 52716.", "answer": 3001069164, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56993 * 54143.", "answer": 3085771999, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54951 * 58202.", "answer": 3198258102, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58735 * 56271.", "answer": 3305077185, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59602 * 55045.", "answer": 3280792090, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56743 * 51456.", "answer": 2919767808, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51790 * 59381.", "answer": 3075341990, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55642 * 52338.", "answer": 2912190996, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54407 * 53432.", "answer": 2907074824, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56520 * 55047.", "answer": 3111256440, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50105 * 52759.", "answer": 2643489695, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58056 * 50025.", "answer": 2904251400, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51587 * 51144.", "answer": 2638365528, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56845 * 58600.", "answer": 3331117000, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56829 * 54724.", "answer": 3109910196, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57060 * 52795.", "answer": 3012482700, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52890 * 56138.", "answer": 2969138820, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53053 * 52200.", "answer": 2769366600, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53244 * 57970.", "answer": 3086554680, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52981 * 58234.", "answer": 3085295554, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51806 * 57383.", "answer": 2972783698, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59291 * 53482.", "answer": 3171001262, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53041 * 53292.", "answer": 2826660972, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50966 * 52993.", "answer": 2700841238, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53143 * 54249.", "answer": 2882954607, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56697 * 57220.", "answer": 3244202340, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51789 * 52721.", "answer": 2730367869, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51307 * 54802.", "answer": 2811726214, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51404 * 56188.", "answer": 2888287952, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52042 * 54534.", "answer": 2838058428, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51052 * 55605.", "answer": 2838746460, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50486 * 59595.", "answer": 3008713170, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53846 * 57829.", "answer": 3113860334, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57949 * 51651.", "answer": 2993123799, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50155 * 51000.", "answer": 2557905000, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54359 * 50118.", "answer": 2724364362, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59542 * 50685.", "answer": 3017886270, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51586 * 53458.", "answer": 2757684388, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58557 * 50118.", "answer": 2934759726, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56154 * 59879.", "answer": 3362445366, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58520 * 54355.", "answer": 3180854600, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57961 * 57753.", "answer": 3347421633, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55521 * 59902.", "answer": 3325818942, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57036 * 55514.", "answer": 3166296504, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56074 * 55620.", "answer": 3118835880, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55164 * 53925.", "answer": 2974718700, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55918 * 56528.", "answer": 3160932704, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56200 * 50937.", "answer": 2862659400, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55833 * 55410.", "answer": 3093706530, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51641 * 50050.", "answer": 2584632050, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57486 * 56583.", "answer": 3252730338, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52275 * 50420.", "answer": 2635705500, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59861 * 52013.", "answer": 3113550193, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58693 * 54578.", "answer": 3203346554, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54072 * 56036.", "answer": 3029978592, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57404 * 57785.", "answer": 3317090140, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58436 * 56768.", "answer": 3317294848, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53079 * 50051.", "answer": 2656657029, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55278 * 50272.", "answer": 2778935616, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55901 * 50749.", "answer": 2836919849, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55333 * 57279.", "answer": 3169418907, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53826 * 59941.", "answer": 3226384266, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57938 * 56556.", "answer": 3276741528, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51333 * 55707.", "answer": 2859607431, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57010 * 57800.", "answer": 3295178000, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51645 * 56305.", "answer": 2907871725, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54814 * 59947.", "answer": 3285934858, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53196 * 52345.", "answer": 2784544620, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58520 * 59369.", "answer": 3474273880, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58267 * 50520.", "answer": 2943648840, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52094 * 58158.", "answer": 3029682852, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51426 * 54937.", "answer": 2825190162, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58990 * 57648.", "answer": 3400655520, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52753 * 57311.", "answer": 3023327183, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51895 * 57899.", "answer": 3004668605, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58858 * 53946.", "answer": 3175153668, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53987 * 53467.", "answer": 2886522929, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52792 * 51465.", "answer": 2716940280, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51728 * 57125.", "answer": 2954962000, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50478 * 52625.", "answer": 2656404750, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55349 * 56283.", "answer": 3115207767, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54593 * 53610.", "answer": 2926730730, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54220 * 57803.", "answer": 3134078660, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52016 * 52224.", "answer": 2716483584, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58757 * 58060.", "answer": 3411431420, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51481 * 55452.", "answer": 2854724412, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53666 * 59436.", "answer": 3189692376, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59841 * 51059.", "answer": 3055421619, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55623 * 56176.", "answer": 3124677648, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56252 * 59206.", "answer": 3330455912, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57159 * 53823.", "answer": 3076468857, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53662 * 54244.", "answer": 2910841528, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51895 * 54767.", "answer": 2842133465, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51436 * 51824.", "answer": 2665619264, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51460 * 55574.", "answer": 2859838040, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59702 * 53082.", "answer": 3169101564, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51902 * 59385.", "answer": 3082200270, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56025 * 52087.", "answer": 2918174175, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55134 * 56229.", "answer": 3100129686, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59452 * 50027.", "answer": 2974205204, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55092 * 51013.", "answer": 2810408196, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59667 * 58775.", "answer": 3506927925, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53110 * 56359.", "answer": 2993226490, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56941 * 55237.", "answer": 3145250017, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55980 * 52069.", "answer": 2914822620, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58515 * 59856.", "answer": 3502473840, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59679 * 53639.", "answer": 3201121881, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51746 * 56476.", "answer": 2922407096, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50150 * 58819.", "answer": 2949772850, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57546 * 55176.", "answer": 3175158096, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52370 * 54863.", "answer": 2873175310, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53586 * 58189.", "answer": 3118115754, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57467 * 52415.", "answer": 3012132805, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59854 * 54643.", "answer": 3270602122, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52389 * 50562.", "answer": 2648892618, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59812 * 55245.", "answer": 3304313940, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55060 * 58230.", "answer": 3206143800, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52022 * 54480.", "answer": 2834158560, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59403 * 57836.", "answer": 3435631908, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53534 * 58110.", "answer": 3110860740, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54775 * 56171.", "answer": 3076766525, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50963 * 55458.", "answer": 2826306054, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52501 * 53450.", "answer": 2806178450, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53687 * 50861.", "answer": 2730574507, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52933 * 57987.", "answer": 3069425871, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56419 * 54900.", "answer": 3097403100, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52608 * 50353.", "answer": 2648970624, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58977 * 56427.", "answer": 3327895179, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55528 * 56921.", "answer": 3160709288, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57756 * 55706.", "answer": 3217355736, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56412 * 56407.", "answer": 3182031684, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51176 * 58648.", "answer": 3001370048, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54637 * 54626.", "answer": 2984600762, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53196 * 58978.", "answer": 3137393688, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56451 * 51594.", "answer": 2912532894, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52144 * 55298.", "answer": 2883458912, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59509 * 50886.", "answer": 3028174974, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54981 * 57496.", "answer": 3161187576, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52681 * 59456.", "answer": 3132201536, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52253 * 57239.", "answer": 2990909467, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57904 * 54769.", "answer": 3171344176, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52372 * 53436.", "answer": 2798550192, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53573 * 53205.", "answer": 2850351465, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50149 * 55934.", "answer": 2805034166, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59431 * 51670.", "answer": 3070799770, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52418 * 56169.", "answer": 2944266642, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56997 * 52756.", "answer": 3006933732, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50922 * 51573.", "answer": 2626200306, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55825 * 57763.", "answer": 3224619475, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52943 * 50859.", "answer": 2692628037, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51922 * 58444.", "answer": 3034529368, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55545 * 59722.", "answer": 3317258490, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57107 * 52434.", "answer": 2994348438, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56619 * 54014.", "answer": 3058218666, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50556 * 51946.", "answer": 2626181976, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53946 * 56498.", "answer": 3047841108, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58005 * 54959.", "answer": 3187896795, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59767 * 52826.", "answer": 3157251542, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56150 * 51468.", "answer": 2889928200, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57596 * 56260.", "answer": 3240350960, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54509 * 57292.", "answer": 3122929628, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56018 * 50190.", "answer": 2811543420, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51966 * 51910.", "answer": 2697555060, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51353 * 51999.", "answer": 2670304647, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58015 * 58351.", "answer": 3385233265, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53685 * 50377.", "answer": 2704489245, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59614 * 59387.", "answer": 3540296618, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59381 * 57856.", "answer": 3435547136, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54484 * 51549.", "answer": 2808595716, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59713 * 52967.", "answer": 3162818471, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56290 * 57932.", "answer": 3260992280, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57105 * 54888.", "answer": 3134379240, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59362 * 52051.", "answer": 3089851462, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51629 * 55328.", "answer": 2856529312, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51040 * 58806.", "answer": 3001458240, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53029 * 56640.", "answer": 3003562560, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50323 * 56451.", "answer": 2840783673, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59110 * 58788.", "answer": 3474958680, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58684 * 58004.", "answer": 3403906736, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51047 * 58501.", "answer": 2986300547, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59580 * 58830.", "answer": 3505091400, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52033 * 53399.", "answer": 2778510167, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51922 * 52960.", "answer": 2749789120, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59815 * 52948.", "answer": 3167084620, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50087 * 59088.", "answer": 2959540656, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57327 * 55149.", "answer": 3161526723, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52015 * 50641.", "answer": 2634091615, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52110 * 59422.", "answer": 3096480420, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53378 * 52641.", "answer": 2809871298, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51438 * 59215.", "answer": 3045901170, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54206 * 50573.", "answer": 2741360038, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51386 * 52043.", "answer": 2674281598, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58292 * 54891.", "answer": 3199706172, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55956 * 58919.", "answer": 3296871564, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52811 * 56931.", "answer": 3006583041, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50001 * 54068.", "answer": 2703454068, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54925 * 50756.", "answer": 2787773300, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58510 * 54807.", "answer": 3206757570, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58750 * 57289.", "answer": 3365728750, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52291 * 59454.", "answer": 3108909114, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58035 * 55127.", "answer": 3199295445, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58563 * 55769.", "answer": 3265999947, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59931 * 58818.", "answer": 3525021558, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58365 * 53438.", "answer": 3118908870, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51622 * 50732.", "answer": 2618887304, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53884 * 50601.", "answer": 2726584284, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53081 * 52321.", "answer": 2777251001, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54910 * 53526.", "answer": 2939112660, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52198 * 59865.", "answer": 3124833270, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59045 * 53539.", "answer": 3161210255, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59695 * 55882.", "answer": 3335875990, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54544 * 52105.", "answer": 2842015120, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56914 * 51218.", "answer": 2915021252, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59008 * 54177.", "answer": 3196876416, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54270 * 56255.", "answer": 3052958850, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52675 * 56554.", "answer": 2978981950, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57472 * 51364.", "answer": 2951991808, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54164 * 56968.", "answer": 3085614752, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52346 * 58780.", "answer": 3076897880, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53338 * 51156.", "answer": 2728558728, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54413 * 53156.", "answer": 2892377428, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56097 * 59234.", "answer": 3322849698, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58379 * 59911.", "answer": 3497544269, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52687 * 56876.", "answer": 2996625812, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52514 * 55183.", "answer": 2897880062, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57104 * 56208.", "answer": 3209701632, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50424 * 59889.", "answer": 3019842936, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54055 * 51270.", "answer": 2771399850, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54425 * 52041.", "answer": 2832331425, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58707 * 51802.", "answer": 3041140014, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58984 * 56664.", "answer": 3342269376, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51080 * 55396.", "answer": 2829627680, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51457 * 55944.", "answer": 2878710408, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55464 * 54476.", "answer": 3021456864, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52397 * 53698.", "answer": 2813614106, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54483 * 50161.", "answer": 2732921763, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51604 * 56179.", "answer": 2899061116, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53640 * 56203.", "answer": 3014728920, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51720 * 52023.", "answer": 2690629560, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52879 * 58625.", "answer": 3100031375, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55022 * 59647.", "answer": 3281897234, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58021 * 51565.", "answer": 2991852865, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58666 * 55716.", "answer": 3268634856, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59374 * 54620.", "answer": 3243007880, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59036 * 54440.", "answer": 3213919840, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59952 * 51623.", "answer": 3094902096, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50785 * 52797.", "answer": 2681295645, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55210 * 56382.", "answer": 3112850220, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52960 * 55655.", "answer": 2947488800, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58711 * 59038.", "answer": 3466180018, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59742 * 56597.", "answer": 3381217974, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57812 * 59704.", "answer": 3451607648, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52090 * 54244.", "answer": 2825569960, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50155 * 58414.", "answer": 2929754170, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52547 * 52070.", "answer": 2736122290, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52337 * 56206.", "answer": 2941653422, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59298 * 54380.", "answer": 3224625240, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50866 * 56064.", "answer": 2851751424, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54081 * 59972.", "answer": 3243345732, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56852 * 57500.", "answer": 3268990000, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52999 * 57191.", "answer": 3031065809, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55799 * 57678.", "answer": 3218374722, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58228 * 54699.", "answer": 3185013372, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54519 * 57008.", "answer": 3108019152, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58529 * 53748.", "answer": 3145816692, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55000 * 51424.", "answer": 2828320000, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55007 * 56660.", "answer": 3116696620, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55123 * 51476.", "answer": 2837511548, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51302 * 51256.", "answer": 2629535312, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53932 * 51534.", "answer": 2779331688, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52705 * 59425.", "answer": 3131994625, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50940 * 51385.", "answer": 2617551900, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54683 * 59079.", "answer": 3230616957, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58074 * 50175.", "answer": 2913862950, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56946 * 58334.", "answer": 3321887964, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52235 * 57858.", "answer": 3022212630, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58156 * 58437.", "answer": 3398462172, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58722 * 52042.", "answer": 3056010324, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56643 * 50227.", "answer": 2845007961, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53115 * 50119.", "answer": 2662070685, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56962 * 58754.", "answer": 3346745348, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55653 * 54001.", "answer": 3005317653, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58652 * 59981.", "answer": 3518005612, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50693 * 59951.", "answer": 3039096043, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57350 * 52761.", "answer": 3025843350, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58577 * 53687.", "answer": 3144823399, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52864 * 51230.", "answer": 2708222720, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56013 * 52184.", "answer": 2922982392, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58416 * 55788.", "answer": 3258911808, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50834 * 56925.", "answer": 2893725450, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58118 * 56211.", "answer": 3266870898, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52793 * 56115.", "answer": 2962479195, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51855 * 55537.", "answer": 2879871135, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54092 * 58832.", "answer": 3182340544, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51931 * 54752.", "answer": 2843326112, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54901 * 57915.", "answer": 3179591415, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54809 * 54337.", "answer": 2978156633, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53490 * 50036.", "answer": 2676425640, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59319 * 56449.", "answer": 3348498231, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53562 * 54994.", "answer": 2945588628, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58446 * 50580.", "answer": 2956198680, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57586 * 57999.", "answer": 3339930414, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50942 * 55828.", "answer": 2843989976, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50096 * 57542.", "answer": 2882624032, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55382 * 54888.", "answer": 3039807216, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55798 * 51755.", "answer": 2887825490, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50084 * 55729.", "answer": 2791131236, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53050 * 56587.", "answer": 3001940350, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55808 * 50145.", "answer": 2798492160, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51660 * 57058.", "answer": 2947616280, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58061 * 53236.", "answer": 3090935396, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51388 * 58668.", "answer": 3014831184, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58426 * 52518.", "answer": 3068416668, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56729 * 52029.", "answer": 2951553141, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57985 * 50113.", "answer": 2905802305, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52549 * 54098.", "answer": 2842795802, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53704 * 57711.", "answer": 3099311544, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56477 * 56132.", "answer": 3170166964, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54903 * 55971.", "answer": 3072975813, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57017 * 52984.", "answer": 3020988728, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58788 * 54415.", "answer": 3198949020, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51780 * 57185.", "answer": 2961039300, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57198 * 52651.", "answer": 3011531898, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52291 * 55795.", "answer": 2917576345, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57110 * 50095.", "answer": 2860925450, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55885 * 53251.", "answer": 2975932135, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51813 * 53105.", "answer": 2751529365, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54667 * 50659.", "answer": 2769375553, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52190 * 56464.", "answer": 2946856160, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56898 * 55426.", "answer": 3153628548, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50517 * 52626.", "answer": 2658507642, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53260 * 57852.", "answer": 3081197520, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54354 * 51946.", "answer": 2823472884, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56899 * 58012.", "answer": 3300824788, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59013 * 58119.", "answer": 3429776547, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52087 * 55322.", "answer": 2881557014, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56551 * 58222.", "answer": 3292512322, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56370 * 52153.", "answer": 2939864610, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51797 * 51767.", "answer": 2681375299, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50346 * 52066.", "answer": 2621314836, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52548 * 55638.", "answer": 2923665624, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58192 * 50223.", "answer": 2922576816, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53874 * 50852.", "answer": 2739600648, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55605 * 57039.", "answer": 3171653595, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59782 * 50131.", "answer": 2996931442, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57116 * 57867.", "answer": 3305131572, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54742 * 54623.", "answer": 2990172266, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57961 * 51353.", "answer": 2976471233, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57027 * 54059.", "answer": 3082822593, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52498 * 58376.", "answer": 3064623248, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53061 * 54087.", "answer": 2869910307, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54606 * 51884.", "answer": 2833177704, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54317 * 54052.", "answer": 2935942484, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57031 * 53250.", "answer": 3036900750, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57764 * 51688.", "answer": 2985705632, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58230 * 52968.", "answer": 3084326640, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53091 * 59686.", "answer": 3168789426, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52436 * 53758.", "answer": 2818854488, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51973 * 52167.", "answer": 2711275491, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56574 * 50628.", "answer": 2864228472, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54486 * 53148.", "answer": 2895821928, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52395 * 56984.", "answer": 2985676680, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50289 * 53270.", "answer": 2678895030, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51489 * 50834.", "answer": 2617391826, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56231 * 56673.", "answer": 3186779463, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58601 * 55020.", "answer": 3224227020, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53791 * 53633.", "answer": 2884972703, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55507 * 56980.", "answer": 3162788860, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57851 * 51005.", "answer": 2950690255, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58353 * 56997.", "answer": 3325945941, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50846 * 54985.", "answer": 2795767310, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51803 * 54411.", "answer": 2818653033, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55956 * 54596.", "answer": 3054973776, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55751 * 56849.", "answer": 3169388599, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54046 * 55240.", "answer": 2985501040, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50779 * 52977.", "answer": 2690119083, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50669 * 50008.", "answer": 2533855352, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50854 * 55269.", "answer": 2810649726, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53473 * 54674.", "answer": 2923582802, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57734 * 54590.", "answer": 3151699060, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59937 * 51650.", "answer": 3095746050, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57059 * 53028.", "answer": 3025724652, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54133 * 58049.", "answer": 3142366517, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55956 * 55476.", "answer": 3104215056, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54986 * 51827.", "answer": 2849759422, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51587 * 50223.", "answer": 2590853901, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59040 * 52134.", "answer": 3077991360, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55426 * 55907.", "answer": 3098701382, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55920 * 59648.", "answer": 3335516160, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58664 * 59907.", "answer": 3514384248, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56088 * 53903.", "answer": 3023311464, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54521 * 53441.", "answer": 2913656761, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59573 * 56292.", "answer": 3353483316, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51429 * 51742.", "answer": 2661039318, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52137 * 59860.", "answer": 3120920820, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51971 * 50672.", "answer": 2633474512, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59610 * 53120.", "answer": 3166483200, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53160 * 57303.", "answer": 3046227480, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51616 * 51226.", "answer": 2644081216, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58955 * 55618.", "answer": 3278959190, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54939 * 57769.", "answer": 3173771091, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53309 * 58741.", "answer": 3131423969, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52517 * 50717.", "answer": 2663504689, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52094 * 53140.", "answer": 2768275160, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56851 * 59019.", "answer": 3355289169, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54137 * 59180.", "answer": 3203827660, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55690 * 55996.", "answer": 3118417240, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57347 * 51923.", "answer": 2977628281, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57145 * 51109.", "answer": 2920623805, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57910 * 56864.", "answer": 3292994240, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58581 * 58255.", "answer": 3412636155, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50358 * 52735.", "answer": 2655629130, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59816 * 54491.", "answer": 3259433656, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52112 * 54745.", "answer": 2852871440, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50744 * 59276.", "answer": 3007901344, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50996 * 53116.", "answer": 2708703536, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56512 * 58110.", "answer": 3283912320, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58723 * 58412.", "answer": 3430127876, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51228 * 52711.", "answer": 2700279108, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 57172 * 58344.", "answer": 3335643168, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56293 * 59215.", "answer": 3333389995, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56393 * 56567.", "answer": 3189982831, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59948 * 54448.", "answer": 3264048704, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53390 * 53015.", "answer": 2830470850, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50058 * 52621.", "answer": 2634102018, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59369 * 53568.", "answer": 3180278592, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59701 * 50145.", "answer": 2993706645, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58401 * 57461.", "answer": 3355779861, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58254 * 58602.", "answer": 3413800908, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54240 * 54971.", "answer": 2981627040, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53609 * 54855.", "answer": 2940721695, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54399 * 59046.", "answer": 3212043354, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51951 * 52803.", "answer": 2743168653, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53668 * 50747.", "answer": 2723489996, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 58741 * 53902.", "answer": 3166257382, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54781 * 50640.", "answer": 2774109840, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52427 * 54550.", "answer": 2859892850, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52178 * 54430.", "answer": 2840048540, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50844 * 54079.", "answer": 2749592676, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53440 * 58758.", "answer": 3140027520, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51903 * 50022.", "answer": 2596291866, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55692 * 59914.", "answer": 3336730488, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56047 * 55317.", "answer": 3100351899, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 51363 * 58999.", "answer": 3030365637, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 54326 * 52189.", "answer": 2835219614, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 56690 * 54831.", "answer": 3108369390, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 55318 * 50938.", "answer": 2817788284, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50170 * 55824.", "answer": 2800690080, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 53592 * 54582.", "answer": 2925158544, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 52895 * 54194.", "answer": 2866591630, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 50256 * 58804.", "answer": 2955253824, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 59556 * 51743.", "answer": 3081606108, "range": "[50000, 59999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66258 * 64216.", "answer": 4254823728, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69901 * 69025.", "answer": 4824916525, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63377 * 67244.", "answer": 4261722988, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63614 * 65312.", "answer": 4154757568, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64403 * 63341.", "answer": 4079350423, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69529 * 66479.", "answer": 4622218391, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62550 * 67308.", "answer": 4210115400, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63796 * 67109.", "answer": 4281285764, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66039 * 62430.", "answer": 4122814770, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67848 * 61535.", "answer": 4175026680, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68125 * 62973.", "answer": 4290035625, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67526 * 63031.", "answer": 4256231306, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62885 * 63094.", "answer": 3967666190, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69333 * 68036.", "answer": 4717139988, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62955 * 64621.", "answer": 4068215055, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60344 * 65081.", "answer": 3927247864, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62669 * 62911.", "answer": 3942569459, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66458 * 69958.", "answer": 4649268764, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63077 * 61137.", "answer": 3856338549, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62351 * 61180.", "answer": 3814634180, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66986 * 64018.", "answer": 4288309748, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67455 * 66594.", "answer": 4492098270, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61642 * 68630.", "answer": 4230490460, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62249 * 60193.", "answer": 3746954057, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69884 * 61633.", "answer": 4307160572, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66191 * 66291.", "answer": 4387867581, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60339 * 61802.", "answer": 3729070878, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60222 * 60716.", "answer": 3656438952, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62165 * 64068.", "answer": 3982787220, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61369 * 64385.", "answer": 3951243065, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62336 * 69824.", "answer": 4352548864, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60221 * 60153.", "answer": 3622473813, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61742 * 68886.", "answer": 4253159412, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65544 * 61392.", "answer": 4023877248, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63314 * 62281.", "answer": 3943259234, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67871 * 69221.", "answer": 4698098491, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67279 * 62672.", "answer": 4216509488, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65036 * 65435.", "answer": 4255630660, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67846 * 62531.", "answer": 4242478226, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63994 * 60915.", "answer": 3898194510, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68905 * 64382.", "answer": 4436241710, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68906 * 62016.", "answer": 4273274496, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60347 * 60729.", "answer": 3664812963, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61684 * 68923.", "answer": 4251446332, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64861 * 61680.", "answer": 4000626480, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68381 * 66804.", "answer": 4568124324, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62323 * 60019.", "answer": 3740564137, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63675 * 60393.", "answer": 3845524275, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63713 * 66998.", "answer": 4268643574, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66314 * 62414.", "answer": 4138921996, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65788 * 64699.", "answer": 4256417812, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63700 * 66303.", "answer": 4223501100, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61841 * 68057.", "answer": 4208712937, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62778 * 61804.", "answer": 3879931512, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63678 * 61666.", "answer": 3926767548, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64617 * 65854.", "answer": 4255287918, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61249 * 65467.", "answer": 4009788283, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61939 * 65906.", "answer": 4082151734, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61389 * 60710.", "answer": 3726926190, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69904 * 62475.", "answer": 4367252400, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62917 * 67022.", "answer": 4216823174, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68691 * 65486.", "answer": 4498298826, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69824 * 62971.", "answer": 4396887104, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66967 * 62461.", "answer": 4182825787, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64940 * 64702.", "answer": 4201747880, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65707 * 61702.", "answer": 4054253314, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64441 * 68179.", "answer": 4393522939, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66047 * 64348.", "answer": 4249992356, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61251 * 60035.", "answer": 3677203785, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62435 * 62401.", "answer": 3896006435, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65247 * 62421.", "answer": 4072782987, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66399 * 67318.", "answer": 4469847882, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67838 * 61102.", "answer": 4145037476, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61854 * 69467.", "answer": 4296811818, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67003 * 64562.", "answer": 4325847686, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62370 * 61481.", "answer": 3834569970, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65292 * 62089.", "answer": 4053914988, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62979 * 66308.", "answer": 4176011532, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65777 * 65231.", "answer": 4290699487, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68097 * 66944.", "answer": 4558685568, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67885 * 66782.", "answer": 4533496070, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69858 * 65463.", "answer": 4573114254, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62264 * 64028.", "answer": 3986639392, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66278 * 66859.", "answer": 4431280802, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69000 * 68144.", "answer": 4701936000, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68826 * 68745.", "answer": 4731443370, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68070 * 68724.", "answer": 4678042680, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68785 * 63770.", "answer": 4386419450, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66301 * 61369.", "answer": 4068826069, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69518 * 66911.", "answer": 4651518898, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68633 * 69467.", "answer": 4767728611, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63593 * 61429.", "answer": 3906454397, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63853 * 65926.", "answer": 4209572878, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60046 * 63330.", "answer": 3802713180, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60281 * 65937.", "answer": 3974748297, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69148 * 67764.", "answer": 4685745072, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62188 * 61804.", "answer": 3843467152, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60976 * 65723.", "answer": 4007525648, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65912 * 62283.", "answer": 4105197096, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64828 * 67543.", "answer": 4378677604, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62361 * 69035.", "answer": 4305091635, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66898 * 63973.", "answer": 4279665754, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63452 * 63679.", "answer": 4040559908, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60915 * 62257.", "answer": 3792385155, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61920 * 62344.", "answer": 3860340480, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66184 * 60431.", "answer": 3999565304, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66958 * 66089.", "answer": 4425187262, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60886 * 61736.", "answer": 3758858096, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69529 * 61208.", "answer": 4255731032, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67812 * 69730.", "answer": 4728530760, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62591 * 60494.", "answer": 3786379954, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62406 * 65984.", "answer": 4117797504, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62314 * 61294.", "answer": 3819474316, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64014 * 61262.", "answer": 3921625668, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60204 * 69325.", "answer": 4173642300, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66823 * 62452.", "answer": 4173229996, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62988 * 67696.", "answer": 4264035648, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62295 * 68641.", "answer": 4275991095, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64907 * 67703.", "answer": 4394398621, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66742 * 65526.", "answer": 4373336292, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67274 * 60216.", "answer": 4050971184, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64698 * 61822.", "answer": 3999759756, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62554 * 60983.", "answer": 3814730582, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60526 * 69898.", "answer": 4230646348, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62843 * 68245.", "answer": 4288720535, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62627 * 60178.", "answer": 3768767606, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66494 * 66940.", "answer": 4451108360, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67443 * 69079.", "answer": 4658894997, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64227 * 69372.", "answer": 4455555444, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68222 * 65014.", "answer": 4435385108, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63724 * 66941.", "answer": 4265748284, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62569 * 64453.", "answer": 4032759757, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61506 * 68544.", "answer": 4215867264, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66185 * 62050.", "answer": 4106779250, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63471 * 66560.", "answer": 4224629760, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60917 * 63586.", "answer": 3873468362, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66427 * 63009.", "answer": 4185498843, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69163 * 69913.", "answer": 4835392819, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61264 * 67674.", "answer": 4145979936, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67821 * 65131.", "answer": 4417249551, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66637 * 66233.", "answer": 4413568421, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62700 * 60895.", "answer": 3818116500, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66086 * 66950.", "answer": 4424457700, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63190 * 64422.", "answer": 4070826180, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61776 * 61710.", "answer": 3812196960, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61274 * 65942.", "answer": 4040530108, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69882 * 65496.", "answer": 4576991472, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60459 * 63924.", "answer": 3864781116, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64623 * 62666.", "answer": 4049664918, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68873 * 61744.", "answer": 4252494512, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61070 * 63471.", "answer": 3876173970, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69783 * 60179.", "answer": 4199471157, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65064 * 63075.", "answer": 4103911800, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69038 * 63305.", "answer": 4370450590, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60530 * 63937.", "answer": 3870106610, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64410 * 61393.", "answer": 3954323130, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69340 * 69253.", "answer": 4802003020, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60735 * 69236.", "answer": 4205048460, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67926 * 60748.", "answer": 4126368648, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60787 * 65154.", "answer": 3960516198, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61527 * 65056.", "answer": 4002700512, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60138 * 65843.", "answer": 3959666334, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64626 * 66523.", "answer": 4299115398, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68195 * 63192.", "answer": 4309378440, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65152 * 66400.", "answer": 4326092800, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65830 * 62122.", "answer": 4089491260, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61595 * 65428.", "answer": 4030037660, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66672 * 68250.", "answer": 4550364000, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61654 * 68227.", "answer": 4206467458, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62460 * 60388.", "answer": 3771834480, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69620 * 66260.", "answer": 4613021200, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67814 * 69606.", "answer": 4720261284, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60612 * 64753.", "answer": 3924808836, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62641 * 62482.", "answer": 3913934962, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67587 * 61290.", "answer": 4142407230, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61528 * 63794.", "answer": 3925117232, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63533 * 62307.", "answer": 3958550631, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62638 * 68218.", "answer": 4273039084, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68459 * 69973.", "answer": 4790281607, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68573 * 65593.", "answer": 4497908789, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67331 * 62149.", "answer": 4184554319, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65554 * 64765.", "answer": 4245604810, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65903 * 67059.", "answer": 4419389277, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60655 * 66350.", "answer": 4024459250, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63917 * 63421.", "answer": 4053680057, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69943 * 61228.", "answer": 4282470004, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62496 * 69288.", "answer": 4330222848, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68151 * 61595.", "answer": 4197760845, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60244 * 62336.", "answer": 3755369984, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65071 * 68964.", "answer": 4487556444, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61428 * 68174.", "answer": 4187792472, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61541 * 67451.", "answer": 4151001991, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65139 * 62780.", "answer": 4089426420, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64843 * 62645.", "answer": 4062089735, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61116 * 64589.", "answer": 3947421324, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69445 * 65952.", "answer": 4580036640, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65789 * 61461.", "answer": 4043457729, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61165 * 62935.", "answer": 3849419275, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67548 * 64226.", "answer": 4338337848, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67753 * 64194.", "answer": 4349336082, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67242 * 62301.", "answer": 4189243842, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62031 * 69318.", "answer": 4299864858, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67999 * 60648.", "answer": 4124003352, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65955 * 64696.", "answer": 4267024680, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66568 * 66701.", "answer": 4440152168, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62113 * 67222.", "answer": 4175360086, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66008 * 68396.", "answer": 4514683168, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65138 * 66122.", "answer": 4307054836, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61367 * 66769.", "answer": 4097413223, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68289 * 67374.", "answer": 4600903086, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64306 * 60699.", "answer": 3903309894, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60934 * 64011.", "answer": 3900446274, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69188 * 60130.", "answer": 4160274440, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62532 * 61725.", "answer": 3859787700, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64762 * 66157.", "answer": 4284459634, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62592 * 69341.", "answer": 4340191872, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66541 * 61195.", "answer": 4071976495, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63654 * 66360.", "answer": 4224079440, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67573 * 61531.", "answer": 4157834263, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65716 * 67632.", "answer": 4444504512, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67675 * 68767.", "answer": 4653806725, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67616 * 61787.", "answer": 4177789792, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61406 * 62953.", "answer": 3865691918, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61775 * 66503.", "answer": 4108222825, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67096 * 63268.", "answer": 4245029728, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66578 * 65385.", "answer": 4353202530, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61056 * 65198.", "answer": 3980729088, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65610 * 69901.", "answer": 4586204610, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67967 * 63483.", "answer": 4314749061, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67802 * 61873.", "answer": 4195113146, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64560 * 67447.", "answer": 4354378320, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60627 * 68930.", "answer": 4179019110, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62551 * 67699.", "answer": 4234640149, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62384 * 63497.", "answer": 3961196848, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65245 * 69309.", "answer": 4522065705, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60513 * 69848.", "answer": 4226712024, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66230 * 61022.", "answer": 4041487060, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65922 * 67046.", "answer": 4419806412, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67756 * 63496.", "answer": 4302234976, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60886 * 63465.", "answer": 3864129990, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60375 * 66929.", "answer": 4040838375, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64421 * 64129.", "answer": 4131254309, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62885 * 61369.", "answer": 3859189565, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62322 * 61134.", "answer": 3809993148, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64487 * 66636.", "answer": 4297155732, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61338 * 64887.", "answer": 3980038806, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67396 * 66876.", "answer": 4507174896, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68597 * 63507.", "answer": 4356389679, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64250 * 63015.", "answer": 4048713750, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60880 * 61514.", "answer": 3744972320, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67021 * 65603.", "answer": 4396778663, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64864 * 62695.", "answer": 4066648480, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63253 * 65722.", "answer": 4157113666, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66866 * 67890.", "answer": 4539532740, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67790 * 68773.", "answer": 4662121670, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62632 * 67156.", "answer": 4206114592, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65811 * 69344.", "answer": 4563597984, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66375 * 60162.", "answer": 3993252750, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69189 * 69783.", "answer": 4828215987, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63253 * 61274.", "answer": 3875764322, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69477 * 62369.", "answer": 4333211013, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65304 * 65185.", "answer": 4256841240, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60232 * 62465.", "answer": 3762391880, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67514 * 62416.", "answer": 4213953824, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68182 * 65184.", "answer": 4444375488, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61861 * 66658.", "answer": 4123530538, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64305 * 68531.", "answer": 4406885955, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60060 * 67381.", "answer": 4046902860, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62059 * 67361.", "answer": 4180356299, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69476 * 61596.", "answer": 4279443696, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60597 * 63581.", "answer": 3852817857, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63074 * 66884.", "answer": 4218641416, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68947 * 62721.", "answer": 4324424787, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69845 * 66185.", "answer": 4622691325, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63541 * 65703.", "answer": 4174834323, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63436 * 63131.", "answer": 4004778116, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69450 * 60235.", "answer": 4183320750, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66066 * 65960.", "answer": 4357713360, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60265 * 64947.", "answer": 3914030955, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65029 * 68226.", "answer": 4436668554, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62043 * 68177.", "answer": 4229905611, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67471 * 66783.", "answer": 4505915793, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66723 * 65762.", "answer": 4387837926, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65770 * 68887.", "answer": 4530697990, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66977 * 68571.", "answer": 4592679867, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65502 * 61857.", "answer": 4051757214, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62880 * 67517.", "answer": 4245468960, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67018 * 66113.", "answer": 4430761034, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62898 * 69056.", "answer": 4343484288, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69746 * 62664.", "answer": 4370563344, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68892 * 67141.", "answer": 4625477772, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66251 * 64669.", "answer": 4284385919, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67167 * 64640.", "answer": 4341674880, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61625 * 61435.", "answer": 3785931875, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61700 * 61468.", "answer": 3792575600, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60269 * 66738.", "answer": 4022232522, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61698 * 68133.", "answer": 4203669834, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68924 * 61633.", "answer": 4247992892, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67276 * 68247.", "answer": 4591385172, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69522 * 60534.", "answer": 4208444748, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64749 * 66891.", "answer": 4331125359, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63471 * 63651.", "answer": 4039992621, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67448 * 69037.", "answer": 4656407576, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66243 * 61875.", "answer": 4098785625, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63204 * 67693.", "answer": 4278468372, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62038 * 65744.", "answer": 4078626272, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67601 * 66765.", "answer": 4513380765, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66484 * 60124.", "answer": 3997284016, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66138 * 63668.", "answer": 4210874184, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68315 * 64646.", "answer": 4416291490, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64384 * 64333.", "answer": 4142015872, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65036 * 66794.", "answer": 4344014584, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63957 * 60068.", "answer": 3841769076, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66792 * 60535.", "answer": 4043253720, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60254 * 60430.", "answer": 3641149220, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62512 * 66134.", "answer": 4134168608, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68502 * 69829.", "answer": 4783426158, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65201 * 65490.", "answer": 4270013490, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62792 * 69374.", "answer": 4356132208, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67045 * 63962.", "answer": 4288332290, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69105 * 66412.", "answer": 4589401260, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63156 * 66444.", "answer": 4196337264, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60845 * 69467.", "answer": 4226719615, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67030 * 62111.", "answer": 4163300330, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66396 * 62846.", "answer": 4172723016, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66604 * 65212.", "answer": 4343380048, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68475 * 62595.", "answer": 4286192625, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67166 * 63784.", "answer": 4284116144, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61631 * 62069.", "answer": 3825374539, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68261 * 61939.", "answer": 4228018079, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69452 * 66422.", "answer": 4613140744, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64263 * 69058.", "answer": 4437874254, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62605 * 65282.", "answer": 4086979610, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63338 * 61527.", "answer": 3896997126, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61528 * 60420.", "answer": 3717521760, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67166 * 60189.", "answer": 4042654374, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69720 * 62507.", "answer": 4357988040, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60455 * 68907.", "answer": 4165772685, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61290 * 69368.", "answer": 4251564720, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66265 * 60414.", "answer": 4003333710, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62138 * 67433.", "answer": 4190151754, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65867 * 63056.", "answer": 4153309552, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63927 * 63633.", "answer": 4067866791, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64864 * 63175.", "answer": 4097783200, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68772 * 64018.", "answer": 4402645896, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66194 * 64267.", "answer": 4254089798, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60847 * 64505.", "answer": 3924935735, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61359 * 62355.", "answer": 3826040445, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60379 * 69492.", "answer": 4195857468, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61694 * 61817.", "answer": 3813737998, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67522 * 69763.", "answer": 4710537286, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62010 * 61754.", "answer": 3829365540, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62323 * 64627.", "answer": 4027748521, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64292 * 62959.", "answer": 4047760028, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61520 * 61267.", "answer": 3769145840, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68097 * 65921.", "answer": 4489022337, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63407 * 66402.", "answer": 4210351614, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61649 * 68045.", "answer": 4194906205, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60359 * 66778.", "answer": 4030653302, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61205 * 67971.", "answer": 4160165055, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61250 * 63445.", "answer": 3886006250, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66879 * 66148.", "answer": 4423912092, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65137 * 67387.", "answer": 4389387019, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62639 * 62945.", "answer": 3942811855, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64894 * 60166.", "answer": 3904412404, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62927 * 69294.", "answer": 4360463538, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69939 * 60515.", "answer": 4232358585, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61920 * 65616.", "answer": 4062942720, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65681 * 67928.", "answer": 4461578968, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69830 * 68953.", "answer": 4814987990, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60082 * 62595.", "answer": 3760832790, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68548 * 64169.", "answer": 4398656612, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61992 * 63159.", "answer": 3915352728, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69930 * 60484.", "answer": 4229646120, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68781 * 60377.", "answer": 4152790437, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68486 * 68384.", "answer": 4683346624, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62496 * 63543.", "answer": 3971183328, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65978 * 61880.", "answer": 4082718640, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63554 * 60483.", "answer": 3843936582, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65366 * 62270.", "answer": 4070340820, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63600 * 61367.", "answer": 3902941200, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62073 * 64384.", "answer": 3996508032, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64483 * 67890.", "answer": 4377750870, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63264 * 61506.", "answer": 3891115584, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65710 * 69035.", "answer": 4536289850, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64822 * 67652.", "answer": 4385337944, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68123 * 67144.", "answer": 4574050712, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68399 * 66552.", "answer": 4552090248, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63163 * 64097.", "answer": 4048558811, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62833 * 63242.", "answer": 3973684586, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64605 * 66436.", "answer": 4292097780, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61685 * 69562.", "answer": 4290931970, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69626 * 65105.", "answer": 4533000730, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62714 * 63372.", "answer": 3974311608, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67992 * 67101.", "answer": 4562331192, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67309 * 66942.", "answer": 4505799078, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69770 * 64451.", "answer": 4496746270, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65222 * 61762.", "answer": 4028241164, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69949 * 66275.", "answer": 4635869975, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67033 * 63272.", "answer": 4241311976, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69292 * 65782.", "answer": 4558166344, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66126 * 61052.", "answer": 4037124552, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67363 * 62740.", "answer": 4226354620, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60553 * 68378.", "answer": 4140493034, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64146 * 69615.", "answer": 4465523790, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66714 * 64808.", "answer": 4323600912, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69894 * 68691.", "answer": 4801088754, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65771 * 66525.", "answer": 4375415775, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60490 * 61878.", "answer": 3743000220, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62947 * 65286.", "answer": 4109557842, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67035 * 63046.", "answer": 4226288610, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65861 * 64019.", "answer": 4216355359, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61190 * 63525.", "answer": 3887094750, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66089 * 66094.", "answer": 4368086366, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62376 * 65151.", "answer": 4063858776, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62003 * 60157.", "answer": 3729914471, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65219 * 60178.", "answer": 3924748982, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65388 * 63502.", "answer": 4152268776, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67624 * 69297.", "answer": 4686140328, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65268 * 63811.", "answer": 4164816348, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69201 * 61085.", "answer": 4227143085, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66317 * 64646.", "answer": 4287128782, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69859 * 63476.", "answer": 4434369884, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68638 * 63562.", "answer": 4362768556, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61686 * 69190.", "answer": 4268054340, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64555 * 69959.", "answer": 4516203245, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61225 * 69403.", "answer": 4249198675, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66909 * 67130.", "answer": 4491601170, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65206 * 65244.", "answer": 4254300264, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63246 * 63229.", "answer": 3998981334, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60813 * 68092.", "answer": 4140878796, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68169 * 60766.", "answer": 4142357454, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64496 * 66901.", "answer": 4314846896, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61953 * 62033.", "answer": 3843130449, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67418 * 62803.", "answer": 4234052654, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69853 * 65355.", "answer": 4565242815, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69685 * 66272.", "answer": 4618164320, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63873 * 69443.", "answer": 4435532739, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60348 * 64670.", "answer": 3902705160, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60292 * 69433.", "answer": 4186254436, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60076 * 67565.", "answer": 4059034940, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64659 * 62147.", "answer": 4018362873, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66599 * 60606.", "answer": 4036298994, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68740 * 68642.", "answer": 4718451080, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60640 * 65527.", "answer": 3973557280, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60266 * 61137.", "answer": 3684482442, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67698 * 61558.", "answer": 4167353484, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66800 * 64931.", "answer": 4337390800, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64500 * 65196.", "answer": 4205142000, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65665 * 66559.", "answer": 4370596735, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61306 * 69116.", "answer": 4237225496, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65131 * 68090.", "answer": 4434769790, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60771 * 66444.", "answer": 4037868324, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64889 * 67447.", "answer": 4376568383, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68082 * 61989.", "answer": 4220335098, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66126 * 61683.", "answer": 4078850058, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60479 * 63670.", "answer": 3850697930, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60783 * 60170.", "answer": 3657313110, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62273 * 61722.", "answer": 3843614106, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65289 * 67138.", "answer": 4383372882, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63708 * 62788.", "answer": 4000097904, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61442 * 63131.", "answer": 3878894902, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66043 * 68807.", "answer": 4544220701, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 60080 * 60860.", "answer": 3656468800, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64254 * 60705.", "answer": 3900539070, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61815 * 60786.", "answer": 3757486590, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64985 * 61229.", "answer": 3978966565, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64320 * 65395.", "answer": 4206206400, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66218 * 64422.", "answer": 4265895996, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62790 * 62257.", "answer": 3909117030, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69559 * 67548.", "answer": 4698571332, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61964 * 62069.", "answer": 3846043516, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65231 * 62424.", "answer": 4071979944, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69570 * 66771.", "answer": 4645258470, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67320 * 62004.", "answer": 4174109280, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68548 * 68644.", "answer": 4705408912, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63940 * 69468.", "answer": 4441783920, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67830 * 68029.", "answer": 4614407070, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64596 * 65274.", "answer": 4216439304, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67908 * 63700.", "answer": 4325739600, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61504 * 64322.", "answer": 3956060288, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 64853 * 61356.", "answer": 3979120668, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65783 * 69150.", "answer": 4548894450, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63971 * 63373.", "answer": 4054034183, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61278 * 61231.", "answer": 3752113218, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68103 * 60987.", "answer": 4153397661, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63481 * 60215.", "answer": 3822508415, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63541 * 67670.", "answer": 4299819470, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66308 * 63078.", "answer": 4182576024, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 67989 * 61712.", "answer": 4195737168, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65577 * 63418.", "answer": 4158762186, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 69675 * 68644.", "answer": 4782770700, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68420 * 65134.", "answer": 4456468280, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 65108 * 67438.", "answer": 4390753304, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 62523 * 68265.", "answer": 4268132595, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 61731 * 62130.", "answer": 3835347030, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 63584 * 65957.", "answer": 4193809888, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66317 * 67412.", "answer": 4470561604, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 68412 * 63326.", "answer": 4332258312, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 66556 * 63079.", "answer": 4198285924, "range": "[60000, 69999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71124 * 74552.", "answer": 5302436448, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76931 * 72690.", "answer": 5592114390, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75032 * 79457.", "answer": 5961817624, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71672 * 72413.", "answer": 5189984536, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77552 * 71755.", "answer": 5564743760, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71805 * 73941.", "answer": 5309333505, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70271 * 77550.", "answer": 5449516050, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73064 * 74370.", "answer": 5433769680, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70468 * 77802.", "answer": 5482551336, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78698 * 77416.", "answer": 6092484368, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75766 * 74351.", "answer": 5633277866, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71938 * 79016.", "answer": 5684253008, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71377 * 75806.", "answer": 5410804862, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77069 * 73474.", "answer": 5662567706, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72467 * 76503.", "answer": 5543942901, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78227 * 77059.", "answer": 6028094393, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78321 * 75467.", "answer": 5910650907, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70870 * 77230.", "answer": 5473290100, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74466 * 76058.", "answer": 5663735028, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71602 * 70805.", "answer": 5069779610, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76267 * 76923.", "answer": 5866686441, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73177 * 74816.", "answer": 5474810432, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73103 * 76597.", "answer": 5599470491, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72894 * 79732.", "answer": 5811984408, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74520 * 78676.", "answer": 5862935520, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79952 * 78087.", "answer": 6243211824, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78497 * 77103.", "answer": 6052354191, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71788 * 70817.", "answer": 5083810796, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74078 * 71819.", "answer": 5320207882, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73597 * 71887.", "answer": 5290667539, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70870 * 70584.", "answer": 5002288080, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79424 * 74361.", "answer": 5906048064, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73911 * 71078.", "answer": 5253446058, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78718 * 71655.", "answer": 5640538290, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74513 * 73710.", "answer": 5492353230, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76628 * 76421.", "answer": 5855988388, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76437 * 71659.", "answer": 5477398983, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73602 * 74395.", "answer": 5475620790, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78112 * 73370.", "answer": 5731077440, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72802 * 73335.", "answer": 5338934670, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75695 * 74718.", "answer": 5655779010, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79769 * 74718.", "answer": 5960180142, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70050 * 71544.", "answer": 5011657200, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73032 * 78245.", "answer": 5714388840, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77811 * 75002.", "answer": 5835980622, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73909 * 72789.", "answer": 5379762201, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75162 * 71137.", "answer": 5346799194, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72730 * 73069.", "answer": 5314308370, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75442 * 77458.", "answer": 5843586436, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72323 * 70208.", "answer": 5077653184, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77775 * 77011.", "answer": 5989530525, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75473 * 70341.", "answer": 5308846293, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72908 * 74322.", "answer": 5418668376, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71261 * 72797.", "answer": 5187587017, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70159 * 79732.", "answer": 5593917388, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75769 * 77763.", "answer": 5892024747, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79554 * 70016.", "answer": 5570052864, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78000 * 74055.", "answer": 5776290000, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77742 * 71792.", "answer": 5581253664, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70740 * 70284.", "answer": 4971890160, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79294 * 74762.", "answer": 5928178028, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73740 * 78606.", "answer": 5796406440, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78243 * 72741.", "answer": 5691474063, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72401 * 71538.", "answer": 5179422738, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71638 * 74990.", "answer": 5372133620, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75499 * 77415.", "answer": 5844755085, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78039 * 75747.", "answer": 5911220133, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78940 * 74216.", "answer": 5858611040, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77970 * 74153.", "answer": 5781709410, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75968 * 77516.", "answer": 5888735488, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70222 * 75777.", "answer": 5321212494, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74933 * 75467.", "answer": 5654968711, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78484 * 79760.", "answer": 6259883840, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77935 * 71847.", "answer": 5599395945, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74422 * 78508.", "answer": 5842722376, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70339 * 72423.", "answer": 5094161397, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76722 * 73608.", "answer": 5647352976, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72320 * 75852.", "answer": 5485616640, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78156 * 70506.", "answer": 5510466936, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74003 * 79463.", "answer": 5880500389, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77056 * 75888.", "answer": 5847625728, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73380 * 71462.", "answer": 5243881560, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73175 * 76189.", "answer": 5575130075, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71768 * 74487.", "answer": 5345783016, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78927 * 77360.", "answer": 6105792720, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78632 * 72866.", "answer": 5729599312, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74346 * 75715.", "answer": 5629107390, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75426 * 76406.", "answer": 5762998956, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79652 * 76836.", "answer": 6120141072, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74526 * 75067.", "answer": 5594443242, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73122 * 70673.", "answer": 5167751106, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79494 * 78520.", "answer": 6241868880, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75624 * 72014.", "answer": 5445986736, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77101 * 77455.", "answer": 5971857955, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79284 * 75685.", "answer": 6000609540, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74725 * 71805.", "answer": 5365628625, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70136 * 78174.", "answer": 5482811664, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72410 * 77640.", "answer": 5621912400, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72461 * 78571.", "answer": 5693333231, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74747 * 79144.", "answer": 5915776568, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72664 * 74974.", "answer": 5447910736, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77976 * 74722.", "answer": 5826522672, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71058 * 74828.", "answer": 5317128024, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70255 * 77436.", "answer": 5440266180, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70670 * 73560.", "answer": 5198485200, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74636 * 79716.", "answer": 5949683376, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72022 * 70871.", "answer": 5104271162, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78001 * 75010.", "answer": 5850855010, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70083 * 77050.", "answer": 5399895150, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75771 * 70010.", "answer": 5304727710, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70817 * 74119.", "answer": 5248885223, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72256 * 75737.", "answer": 5472452672, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74641 * 78224.", "answer": 5838717584, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79187 * 72540.", "answer": 5744224980, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71409 * 74434.", "answer": 5315257506, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72337 * 73223.", "answer": 5296732151, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77078 * 79588.", "answer": 6134483864, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71322 * 74764.", "answer": 5332318008, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73585 * 70526.", "answer": 5189655710, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77752 * 75810.", "answer": 5894379120, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74075 * 76328.", "answer": 5653996600, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76923 * 76539.", "answer": 5887609497, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71607 * 74280.", "answer": 5318967960, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74948 * 79781.", "answer": 5979426388, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75091 * 72839.", "answer": 5469553349, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79239 * 77140.", "answer": 6112496460, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75283 * 79472.", "answer": 5982890576, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72280 * 73268.", "answer": 5295811040, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74096 * 72223.", "answer": 5351435408, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76820 * 79081.", "answer": 6075002420, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73268 * 74932.", "answer": 5490117776, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74997 * 71402.", "answer": 5354935794, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74871 * 79284.", "answer": 5936072364, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77555 * 78942.", "answer": 6122346810, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73004 * 76159.", "answer": 5559911636, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77158 * 71573.", "answer": 5522429534, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72270 * 78627.", "answer": 5682373290, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77240 * 75132.", "answer": 5803195680, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78254 * 75858.", "answer": 5936191932, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77673 * 75803.", "answer": 5887846419, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77006 * 77643.", "answer": 5978976858, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76889 * 76721.", "answer": 5899000969, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77557 * 70453.", "answer": 5464123321, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79157 * 70432.", "answer": 5575185824, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76896 * 71448.", "answer": 5494065408, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72303 * 74954.", "answer": 5419399062, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73975 * 79508.", "answer": 5881604300, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78391 * 76113.", "answer": 5966574183, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72085 * 78900.", "answer": 5687506500, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79266 * 74806.", "answer": 5929572396, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70877 * 76433.", "answer": 5417341741, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72063 * 76601.", "answer": 5520097863, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70097 * 77582.", "answer": 5438265454, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78487 * 77540.", "answer": 6085881980, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70890 * 71387.", "answer": 5060624430, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70896 * 74426.", "answer": 5276505696, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71753 * 75463.", "answer": 5414696639, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79737 * 71595.", "answer": 5708770515, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74760 * 79264.", "answer": 5925776640, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77888 * 75428.", "answer": 5874936064, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70997 * 71989.", "answer": 5111003033, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79578 * 78369.", "answer": 6236448282, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70868 * 73359.", "answer": 5198805612, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78458 * 72361.", "answer": 5677299338, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79208 * 78115.", "answer": 6187332920, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72234 * 73662.", "answer": 5320900908, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72535 * 74929.", "answer": 5434975015, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75093 * 70105.", "answer": 5264394765, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77945 * 73288.", "answer": 5712433160, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71879 * 71100.", "answer": 5110596900, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70000 * 72507.", "answer": 5075490000, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79892 * 71983.", "answer": 5750865836, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78516 * 71587.", "answer": 5620724892, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74050 * 73347.", "answer": 5431345350, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71697 * 77761.", "answer": 5575230417, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70403 * 78287.", "answer": 5511639661, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77271 * 76401.", "answer": 5903581671, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70911 * 71995.", "answer": 5105237445, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74913 * 76628.", "answer": 5740433364, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77925 * 73015.", "answer": 5689693875, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73849 * 78957.", "answer": 5830895493, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74264 * 77194.", "answer": 5732735216, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72018 * 77083.", "answer": 5551363494, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72396 * 70354.", "answer": 5093348184, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73027 * 72321.", "answer": 5281385667, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73943 * 72797.", "answer": 5382828571, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78380 * 78956.", "answer": 6188571280, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73282 * 77801.", "answer": 5701412882, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77871 * 74751.", "answer": 5820935121, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74742 * 71638.", "answer": 5354367396, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79646 * 78076.", "answer": 6218441096, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76018 * 74508.", "answer": 5663949144, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76409 * 76321.", "answer": 5831611289, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71758 * 77601.", "answer": 5568492558, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76830 * 76960.", "answer": 5912836800, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72427 * 70458.", "answer": 5103061566, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74643 * 77488.", "answer": 5783936784, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71968 * 79244.", "answer": 5703032192, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76380 * 70180.", "answer": 5360348400, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79511 * 74960.", "answer": 5960144560, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70558 * 77282.", "answer": 5452863356, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70698 * 75811.", "answer": 5359686078, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72282 * 77666.", "answer": 5613853812, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77509 * 74536.", "answer": 5777210824, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70149 * 72593.", "answer": 5092326357, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75861 * 78202.", "answer": 5932481922, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78244 * 73453.", "answer": 5747256532, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75715 * 78602.", "answer": 5951350430, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76399 * 78405.", "answer": 5990063595, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71028 * 72858.", "answer": 5174958024, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72480 * 75764.", "answer": 5491374720, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79226 * 75558.", "answer": 5986158108, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77528 * 72294.", "answer": 5604809232, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74560 * 74963.", "answer": 5589241280, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76454 * 71117.", "answer": 5437179118, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77925 * 76168.", "answer": 5935391400, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77729 * 79926.", "answer": 6212568054, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72955 * 79437.", "answer": 5795326335, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78306 * 78608.", "answer": 6155478048, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74247 * 72120.", "answer": 5354693640, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75309 * 79647.", "answer": 5998135923, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79514 * 75703.", "answer": 6019448342, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79576 * 76615.", "answer": 6096715240, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71107 * 70736.", "answer": 5029824752, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70483 * 72607.", "answer": 5117559181, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73796 * 71581.", "answer": 5282391476, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71740 * 78182.", "answer": 5608776680, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77805 * 75302.", "answer": 5858872110, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73793 * 73876.", "answer": 5451531668, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71727 * 72850.", "answer": 5225311950, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76292 * 76882.", "answer": 5865481544, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71054 * 71014.", "answer": 5045828756, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74103 * 71875.", "answer": 5326153125, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70613 * 71194.", "answer": 5027221922, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77234 * 76132.", "answer": 5879978888, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79937 * 70482.", "answer": 5634119634, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72851 * 75261.", "answer": 5482839111, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71763 * 77364.", "answer": 5551872732, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76187 * 72182.", "answer": 5499330034, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79400 * 79117.", "answer": 6281889800, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73272 * 73206.", "answer": 5363950032, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74136 * 78046.", "answer": 5786018256, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77168 * 74687.", "answer": 5763446416, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73694 * 73296.", "answer": 5401475424, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72655 * 77111.", "answer": 5602499705, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78659 * 73150.", "answer": 5753905850, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71409 * 79537.", "answer": 5679657633, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70397 * 71576.", "answer": 5038735672, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73334 * 70544.", "answer": 5173273696, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72302 * 70085.", "answer": 5067285670, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75891 * 76685.", "answer": 5819701335, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79310 * 78955.", "answer": 6261921050, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71179 * 75582.", "answer": 5379851178, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73036 * 78653.", "answer": 5744500508, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78129 * 73115.", "answer": 5712401835, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73399 * 79344.", "answer": 5823770256, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77761 * 78205.", "answer": 6081299005, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75768 * 75840.", "answer": 5746245120, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79153 * 72258.", "answer": 5719437474, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71100 * 77190.", "answer": 5488209000, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77004 * 76162.", "answer": 5864778648, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71161 * 79324.", "answer": 5644775164, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71280 * 72083.", "answer": 5138076240, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78474 * 74886.", "answer": 5876603964, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71653 * 71932.", "answer": 5154143596, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78170 * 73777.", "answer": 5767148090, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70843 * 79854.", "answer": 5657096922, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78856 * 75421.", "answer": 5947398376, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70369 * 73670.", "answer": 5184084230, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74749 * 74118.", "answer": 5540246382, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76396 * 75863.", "answer": 5795629748, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71113 * 72586.", "answer": 5161808218, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74719 * 71225.", "answer": 5321860775, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78755 * 79426.", "answer": 6255194630, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73955 * 78482.", "answer": 5804136310, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78192 * 75115.", "answer": 5873392080, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76540 * 70928.", "answer": 5428829120, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78944 * 71816.", "answer": 5669442304, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79548 * 77716.", "answer": 6182152368, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74309 * 70491.", "answer": 5238115719, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70528 * 75538.", "answer": 5327544064, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76904 * 74274.", "answer": 5711967696, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73285 * 75481.", "answer": 5531625085, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70973 * 72282.", "answer": 5130070386, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73346 * 78963.", "answer": 5791620198, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75400 * 71021.", "answer": 5354983400, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73860 * 78086.", "answer": 5767431960, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71194 * 79238.", "answer": 5641270172, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79994 * 70579.", "answer": 5645896526, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75666 * 71159.", "answer": 5384316894, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76819 * 79800.", "answer": 6130156200, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71320 * 79034.", "answer": 5636704880, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77844 * 72121.", "answer": 5614187124, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74432 * 70683.", "answer": 5261077056, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71704 * 70583.", "answer": 5061083432, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78136 * 78316.", "answer": 6119298976, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73690 * 75738.", "answer": 5581133220, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77069 * 77824.", "answer": 5997817856, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74971 * 73731.", "answer": 5527686801, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70351 * 70906.", "answer": 4988308006, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70431 * 73214.", "answer": 5156535234, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78752 * 79963.", "answer": 6297246176, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76215 * 70296.", "answer": 5357609640, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79052 * 77899.", "answer": 6158071748, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70854 * 76342.", "answer": 5409136068, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76180 * 72051.", "answer": 5488845180, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77040 * 76993.", "answer": 5931540720, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79003 * 72257.", "answer": 5708519771, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71893 * 77175.", "answer": 5548342275, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71933 * 76024.", "answer": 5468634392, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75763 * 73172.", "answer": 5543730236, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75621 * 77152.", "answer": 5834311392, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70949 * 73902.", "answer": 5243272998, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73801 * 71507.", "answer": 5277288107, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79643 * 70164.", "answer": 5588071452, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73721 * 76767.", "answer": 5659340007, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78785 * 79306.", "answer": 6248123210, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70750 * 70244.", "answer": 4969763000, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74094 * 70931.", "answer": 5255561514, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71255 * 70928.", "answer": 5053974640, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72076 * 77185.", "answer": 5563186060, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72958 * 74630.", "answer": 5444855540, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70716 * 75146.", "answer": 5314024536, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75728 * 79869.", "answer": 6048319632, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74001 * 74790.", "answer": 5534534790, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72125 * 79930.", "answer": 5764951250, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76517 * 77843.", "answer": 5956312831, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72005 * 71258.", "answer": 5130932290, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71251 * 74099.", "answer": 5279627849, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78907 * 73372.", "answer": 5789564404, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78108 * 75848.", "answer": 5924335584, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73609 * 77266.", "answer": 5687472994, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74959 * 76011.", "answer": 5697708549, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79034 * 74795.", "answer": 5911348030, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74001 * 78631.", "answer": 5818772631, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74383 * 75224.", "answer": 5595386792, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78870 * 78248.", "answer": 6171419760, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71710 * 70884.", "answer": 5083091640, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75679 * 76731.", "answer": 5806925349, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77966 * 74583.", "answer": 5814938178, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71285 * 73335.", "answer": 5227685475, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72246 * 78535.", "answer": 5673839610, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73777 * 74996.", "answer": 5532979892, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79059 * 73453.", "answer": 5807120727, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72011 * 76101.", "answer": 5480109111, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72325 * 70587.", "answer": 5105204775, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73851 * 77213.", "answer": 5702257263, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77434 * 71871.", "answer": 5565259014, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70348 * 78174.", "answer": 5499384552, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70553 * 74428.", "answer": 5251118684, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74554 * 79637.", "answer": 5937256898, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76294 * 74921.", "answer": 5716022774, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71384 * 70978.", "answer": 5066693552, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74572 * 79990.", "answer": 5965014280, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76290 * 78115.", "answer": 5959393350, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70308 * 76268.", "answer": 5362250544, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76302 * 77274.", "answer": 5896160748, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70727 * 73677.", "answer": 5210953179, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73370 * 76214.", "answer": 5591821180, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73021 * 77062.", "answer": 5627144302, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78724 * 70856.", "answer": 5578067744, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74999 * 70512.", "answer": 5288329488, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78872 * 75698.", "answer": 5970452656, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70425 * 79973.", "answer": 5632098525, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75508 * 74301.", "answer": 5610319908, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79682 * 73547.", "answer": 5860372054, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70448 * 75586.", "answer": 5324882528, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77111 * 77004.", "answer": 5937855444, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70935 * 71789.", "answer": 5092352715, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79065 * 76358.", "answer": 6037245270, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74709 * 78761.", "answer": 5884155549, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77594 * 76944.", "answer": 5970392736, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79381 * 79311.", "answer": 6295786491, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78501 * 74261.", "answer": 5829562761, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72663 * 76247.", "answer": 5540335761, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77656 * 73903.", "answer": 5739011368, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72160 * 70248.", "answer": 5069095680, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74598 * 74495.", "answer": 5557178010, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71401 * 74094.", "answer": 5290385694, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78893 * 74846.", "answer": 5904825478, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75530 * 79356.", "answer": 5993758680, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76465 * 70632.", "answer": 5400875880, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74493 * 75926.", "answer": 5655955518, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74403 * 74104.", "answer": 5513559912, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79961 * 70202.", "answer": 5613422122, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72036 * 75028.", "answer": 5404717008, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79313 * 75259.", "answer": 5969017067, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74333 * 72929.", "answer": 5421031357, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77271 * 77581.", "answer": 5994761451, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70282 * 77207.", "answer": 5426262374, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70145 * 77642.", "answer": 5446198090, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70606 * 75877.", "answer": 5357371462, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77867 * 79119.", "answer": 6160759173, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73569 * 76694.", "answer": 5642300886, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70959 * 79495.", "answer": 5640885705, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71303 * 74529.", "answer": 5314141287, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79999 * 79034.", "answer": 6322640966, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75145 * 71049.", "answer": 5338977105, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77216 * 72945.", "answer": 5632521120, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74227 * 74524.", "answer": 5531692948, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74252 * 78108.", "answer": 5799675216, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72084 * 73726.", "answer": 5314464984, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72858 * 72406.", "answer": 5275356348, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70812 * 73812.", "answer": 5226775344, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71875 * 70630.", "answer": 5076531250, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73018 * 78302.", "answer": 5717455436, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77214 * 79500.", "answer": 6138513000, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75199 * 70687.", "answer": 5315591713, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79067 * 73734.", "answer": 5829926178, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70996 * 74244.", "answer": 5271027024, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74217 * 70264.", "answer": 5214783288, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75789 * 78854.", "answer": 5976265806, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70732 * 79839.", "answer": 5647172148, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73845 * 75729.", "answer": 5592208005, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71788 * 71269.", "answer": 5116258972, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78305 * 77271.", "answer": 6050705655, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71854 * 78372.", "answer": 5631341688, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71268 * 73882.", "answer": 5265422376, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73343 * 75337.", "answer": 5525441591, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79344 * 76084.", "answer": 6036808896, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76815 * 71169.", "answer": 5466846735, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76987 * 74638.", "answer": 5746155706, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72344 * 70404.", "answer": 5093306976, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75350 * 79944.", "answer": 6023780400, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75902 * 75488.", "answer": 5729690176, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76686 * 76139.", "answer": 5838795354, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77711 * 74817.", "answer": 5814103887, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70510 * 72626.", "answer": 5120859260, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76034 * 70730.", "answer": 5377884820, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74765 * 72458.", "answer": 5417322370, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79686 * 70418.", "answer": 5611328748, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71740 * 79978.", "answer": 5737621720, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73464 * 75129.", "answer": 5519276856, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78368 * 78326.", "answer": 6138251968, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79527 * 75636.", "answer": 6015104172, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73520 * 76206.", "answer": 5602665120, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79546 * 70534.", "answer": 5610697564, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72458 * 76243.", "answer": 5524415294, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71285 * 71266.", "answer": 5080196810, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73679 * 79263.", "answer": 5840018577, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78249 * 79411.", "answer": 6213831339, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78982 * 76849.", "answer": 6069687718, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78830 * 71986.", "answer": 5674656380, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78646 * 70842.", "answer": 5571439932, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79946 * 77738.", "answer": 6214842148, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78592 * 78525.", "answer": 6171436800, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77225 * 75192.", "answer": 5806702200, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74410 * 73195.", "answer": 5446439950, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79424 * 74801.", "answer": 5940994624, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73998 * 75385.", "answer": 5578339230, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73982 * 75930.", "answer": 5617453260, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73782 * 77468.", "answer": 5715743976, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75157 * 71890.", "answer": 5403036730, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73949 * 77291.", "answer": 5715592159, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76716 * 75929.", "answer": 5824969164, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71305 * 75766.", "answer": 5402494630, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79182 * 78284.", "answer": 6198683688, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71252 * 75935.", "answer": 5410520620, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77932 * 79915.", "answer": 6227935780, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73774 * 77355.", "answer": 5706787770, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76862 * 73764.", "answer": 5669648568, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79328 * 72052.", "answer": 5715741056, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78808 * 74013.", "answer": 5832816504, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76678 * 79580.", "answer": 6102035240, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72263 * 79921.", "answer": 5775331223, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 74264 * 74700.", "answer": 5547520800, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75596 * 75142.", "answer": 5680434632, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71932 * 71335.", "answer": 5131269220, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76692 * 76898.", "answer": 5897461416, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78274 * 72431.", "answer": 5669464094, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79437 * 78096.", "answer": 6203711952, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73245 * 72947.", "answer": 5343003015, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77439 * 70254.", "answer": 5440399506, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72732 * 71979.", "answer": 5235176628, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76858 * 74315.", "answer": 5711702270, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79086 * 77698.", "answer": 6144824028, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71654 * 72070.", "answer": 5164103780, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70558 * 77068.", "answer": 5437763944, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70392 * 72735.", "answer": 5119962120, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71196 * 72168.", "answer": 5138072928, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78436 * 78672.", "answer": 6170716992, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76358 * 76919.", "answer": 5873381002, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75805 * 72088.", "answer": 5464630840, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76591 * 79124.", "answer": 6060186284, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73955 * 74806.", "answer": 5532277730, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 71950 * 75518.", "answer": 5433520100, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75515 * 79690.", "answer": 6017790350, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79973 * 71765.", "answer": 5739262345, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 70741 * 71208.", "answer": 5037325128, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 75815 * 77354.", "answer": 5864593510, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76699 * 77368.", "answer": 5934048232, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77138 * 74739.", "answer": 5765216982, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77816 * 72205.", "answer": 5618704280, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 73005 * 79659.", "answer": 5815505295, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 78345 * 71372.", "answer": 5591639340, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 72494 * 70127.", "answer": 5083786738, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 79724 * 79716.", "answer": 6355278384, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76060 * 77430.", "answer": 5889325800, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 76215 * 75250.", "answer": 5735178750, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 77185 * 72895.", "answer": 5626400575, "range": "[70000, 79999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88334 * 89635.", "answer": 7917818090, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84576 * 81587.", "answer": 6900302112, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83805 * 84871.", "answer": 7112614155, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88082 * 85588.", "answer": 7538762216, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80791 * 89242.", "answer": 7209950422, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88481 * 88604.", "answer": 7839770524, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89499 * 88326.", "answer": 7905088674, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86990 * 84673.", "answer": 7365704270, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85288 * 86292.", "answer": 7359672096, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85219 * 82923.", "answer": 7066615137, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82346 * 80687.", "answer": 6644251702, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83451 * 87053.", "answer": 7264659903, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88505 * 84558.", "answer": 7483805790, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89423 * 85150.", "answer": 7614368450, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81629 * 85690.", "answer": 6994789010, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84666 * 82713.", "answer": 7002978858, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81942 * 84716.", "answer": 6941798472, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84486 * 87973.", "answer": 7432486878, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87191 * 83664.", "answer": 7294747824, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82774 * 84726.", "answer": 7013109924, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84250 * 89931.", "answer": 7576686750, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81738 * 83795.", "answer": 6849235710, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84565 * 82310.", "answer": 6960545150, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81572 * 83388.", "answer": 6802125936, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89046 * 88334.", "answer": 7865789364, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82766 * 80448.", "answer": 6658359168, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89804 * 80651.", "answer": 7242782404, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88844 * 88813.", "answer": 7890502172, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83197 * 80109.", "answer": 6664828473, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88001 * 80422.", "answer": 7077216422, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86054 * 83328.", "answer": 7170707712, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84617 * 89357.", "answer": 7561121269, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86987 * 87288.", "answer": 7592921256, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88534 * 82067.", "answer": 7265719778, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87435 * 84832.", "answer": 7417285920, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81795 * 81965.", "answer": 6704327175, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87281 * 87082.", "answer": 7600604042, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88081 * 84309.", "answer": 7426021029, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81423 * 82241.", "answer": 6696308943, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84562 * 81908.", "answer": 6926304296, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85795 * 81295.", "answer": 6974704525, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83644 * 81218.", "answer": 6793398392, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85359 * 82567.", "answer": 7047836553, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88307 * 85494.", "answer": 7549718658, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84523 * 87429.", "answer": 7389761367, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88402 * 81213.", "answer": 7179391626, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85157 * 80628.", "answer": 6866038596, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87100 * 81645.", "answer": 7111279500, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88540 * 85202.", "answer": 7543785080, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83119 * 89145.", "answer": 7409643255, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80583 * 80130.", "answer": 6457115790, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84029 * 82242.", "answer": 6910713018, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89606 * 86163.", "answer": 7720721778, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83607 * 83205.", "answer": 6956520435, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84346 * 87702.", "answer": 7397312892, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82481 * 87938.", "answer": 7253214178, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83065 * 88138.", "answer": 7321182970, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84630 * 82159.", "answer": 6953116170, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83253 * 81453.", "answer": 6781206609, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88459 * 83509.", "answer": 7387122631, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80052 * 87115.", "answer": 6973729980, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81102 * 88039.", "answer": 7140138978, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89137 * 83416.", "answer": 7435451992, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82918 * 80635.", "answer": 6686092930, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86851 * 84310.", "answer": 7322407810, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86230 * 89566.", "answer": 7723276180, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83845 * 85713.", "answer": 7186606485, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87933 * 88691.", "answer": 7798865703, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82950 * 84916.", "answer": 7043782200, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83799 * 84786.", "answer": 7104982014, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87947 * 88031.", "answer": 7742062357, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86425 * 89795.", "answer": 7760532875, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85851 * 88903.", "answer": 7632411453, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87880 * 84840.", "answer": 7455739200, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81581 * 83586.", "answer": 6819029466, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81841 * 84706.", "answer": 6932423746, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86874 * 87326.", "answer": 7586358924, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85331 * 84053.", "answer": 7172326543, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86960 * 81897.", "answer": 7121763120, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82886 * 87614.", "answer": 7261974004, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85224 * 81860.", "answer": 6976436640, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85694 * 86522.", "answer": 7414416268, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82098 * 87925.", "answer": 7218466650, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88014 * 89847.", "answer": 7907793858, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86750 * 83847.", "answer": 7273727250, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80474 * 84766.", "answer": 6821459084, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84389 * 88314.", "answer": 7452730146, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83524 * 86701.", "answer": 7241614324, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80996 * 89212.", "answer": 7225815152, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85295 * 84286.", "answer": 7189174370, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85203 * 86737.", "answer": 7390252611, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86412 * 87240.", "answer": 7538582880, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86966 * 86531.", "answer": 7525254946, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84271 * 80895.", "answer": 6817102545, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84396 * 87954.", "answer": 7422965784, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83587 * 85567.", "answer": 7152288829, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80747 * 85054.", "answer": 6867855338, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87334 * 86714.", "answer": 7573080476, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83625 * 89379.", "answer": 7474318875, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82728 * 88782.", "answer": 7344757296, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83378 * 81807.", "answer": 6820904046, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85401 * 82117.", "answer": 7012873917, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89911 * 88843.", "answer": 7987962973, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80326 * 80345.", "answer": 6453792470, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86212 * 81478.", "answer": 7024381336, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85460 * 85778.", "answer": 7330587880, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89058 * 81039.", "answer": 7217171262, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80806 * 88497.", "answer": 7151088582, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83448 * 85932.", "answer": 7170853536, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88773 * 83251.", "answer": 7390441023, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82572 * 88776.", "answer": 7330411872, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86480 * 83757.", "answer": 7243305360, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84754 * 82644.", "answer": 7004409576, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86125 * 85431.", "answer": 7357744875, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86773 * 83532.", "answer": 7248322236, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89059 * 84074.", "answer": 7487546366, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80223 * 80591.", "answer": 6465251793, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80328 * 88627.", "answer": 7119229656, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81679 * 88216.", "answer": 7205394664, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86519 * 87944.", "answer": 7608826936, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80692 * 82571.", "answer": 6662819132, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84638 * 84939.", "answer": 7189067082, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80397 * 83768.", "answer": 6734695896, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84051 * 80553.", "answer": 6770560203, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84463 * 82025.", "answer": 6928077575, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86190 * 86565.", "answer": 7461037350, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82149 * 84423.", "answer": 6935265027, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81391 * 81253.", "answer": 6613262923, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81210 * 88265.", "answer": 7168000650, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86805 * 80330.", "answer": 6973045650, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80241 * 88875.", "answer": 7131418875, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89910 * 82487.", "answer": 7416406170, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81565 * 89636.", "answer": 7311160340, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86408 * 83183.", "answer": 7187676664, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89923 * 85114.", "answer": 7653706222, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85303 * 86965.", "answer": 7418375395, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88394 * 80383.", "answer": 7105374902, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84950 * 84490.", "answer": 7177425500, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87518 * 83320.", "answer": 7291999760, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81633 * 84329.", "answer": 6884029257, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89440 * 87723.", "answer": 7845945120, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86169 * 84771.", "answer": 7304632299, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87037 * 81524.", "answer": 7095604388, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83641 * 86657.", "answer": 7248078137, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89191 * 84563.", "answer": 7542258533, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87919 * 84659.", "answer": 7443134621, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88736 * 88300.", "answer": 7835388800, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84007 * 86265.", "answer": 7246863855, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80282 * 88143.", "answer": 7076296326, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86449 * 86106.", "answer": 7443777594, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88955 * 81774.", "answer": 7274206170, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87409 * 83671.", "answer": 7313598439, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89467 * 80407.", "answer": 7193773069, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86510 * 83802.", "answer": 7249711020, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87325 * 86059.", "answer": 7515102175, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87811 * 89226.", "answer": 7835024286, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81785 * 85089.", "answer": 6959003865, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85446 * 82355.", "answer": 7036905330, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81370 * 81562.", "answer": 6636699940, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89189 * 82773.", "answer": 7382441097, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83402 * 88025.", "answer": 7341461050, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89722 * 84095.", "answer": 7545171590, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81374 * 82315.", "answer": 6698300810, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86605 * 87758.", "answer": 7600281590, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88575 * 89283.", "answer": 7908241725, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83808 * 80965.", "answer": 6785514720, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88084 * 84129.", "answer": 7410418836, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86747 * 85102.", "answer": 7382343194, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85535 * 82467.", "answer": 7053814845, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80598 * 85266.", "answer": 6872269068, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89262 * 89809.", "answer": 8016530958, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86660 * 80091.", "answer": 6940686060, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84393 * 83427.", "answer": 7040654811, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89214 * 88007.", "answer": 7851456498, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88938 * 88188.", "answer": 7843264344, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85128 * 83862.", "answer": 7139004336, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85272 * 87559.", "answer": 7466331048, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87913 * 88428.", "answer": 7773970764, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89089 * 81334.", "answer": 7245964726, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81721 * 86974.", "answer": 7107602254, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81269 * 86155.", "answer": 7001730695, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82085 * 80223.", "answer": 6585104955, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82655 * 88518.", "answer": 7316455290, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81990 * 82722.", "answer": 6782376780, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83233 * 87169.", "answer": 7255337377, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81862 * 80639.", "answer": 6601269818, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86949 * 88113.", "answer": 7661337237, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82797 * 88594.", "answer": 7335317418, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87982 * 82291.", "answer": 7240126762, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88963 * 86850.", "answer": 7726436550, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86543 * 80151.", "answer": 6936507993, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84861 * 81926.", "answer": 6952322286, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87134 * 84820.", "answer": 7390705880, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84441 * 88560.", "answer": 7478094960, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85281 * 86088.", "answer": 7341670728, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89237 * 82718.", "answer": 7381506166, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82318 * 84754.", "answer": 6976779772, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88572 * 83349.", "answer": 7382387628, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86082 * 88509.", "answer": 7619031738, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89904 * 84116.", "answer": 7562364864, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87735 * 87583.", "answer": 7684094505, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83450 * 85409.", "answer": 7127381050, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82217 * 82690.", "answer": 6798523730, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88591 * 87763.", "answer": 7775011933, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80160 * 85205.", "answer": 6830032800, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86820 * 82936.", "answer": 7200503520, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82463 * 87708.", "answer": 7232664804, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81098 * 80091.", "answer": 6495219918, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85109 * 83074.", "answer": 7070345066, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83264 * 81537.", "answer": 6789096768, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88810 * 87513.", "answer": 7772029530, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85423 * 81551.", "answer": 6966331073, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81001 * 87679.", "answer": 7102086679, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89739 * 82563.", "answer": 7409121057, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81093 * 85741.", "answer": 6952994913, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89161 * 83703.", "answer": 7463043183, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85651 * 80231.", "answer": 6871865381, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83156 * 84498.", "answer": 7026515688, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84656 * 86982.", "answer": 7363548192, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89575 * 85009.", "answer": 7614681175, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86017 * 86607.", "answer": 7449674319, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84173 * 89193.", "answer": 7507642389, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88864 * 83319.", "answer": 7404059616, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81269 * 89709.", "answer": 7290560721, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82497 * 81687.", "answer": 6738932439, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83546 * 84587.", "answer": 7066905502, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82921 * 84307.", "answer": 6990820747, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89235 * 81676.", "answer": 7288357860, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82075 * 88557.", "answer": 7268315775, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89622 * 86274.", "answer": 7732048428, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85409 * 89431.", "answer": 7638212279, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89702 * 89908.", "answer": 8064927416, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84542 * 87756.", "answer": 7419067752, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83429 * 82754.", "answer": 6904083466, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80043 * 83798.", "answer": 6707443314, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83546 * 81496.", "answer": 6808664816, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82400 * 82348.", "answer": 6785475200, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82700 * 87790.", "answer": 7260233000, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80004 * 85297.", "answer": 6824101188, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81274 * 80855.", "answer": 6571409270, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82244 * 88383.", "answer": 7268971452, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87203 * 86969.", "answer": 7583957707, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87728 * 85359.", "answer": 7488374352, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84957 * 88198.", "answer": 7493037486, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81921 * 83944.", "answer": 6876776424, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89177 * 86442.", "answer": 7708638234, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86181 * 86316.", "answer": 7438799196, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87773 * 85816.", "answer": 7532327768, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85107 * 88552.", "answer": 7536395064, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85193 * 88694.", "answer": 7556107942, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81281 * 89918.", "answer": 7308624958, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83504 * 82721.", "answer": 6907534384, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84550 * 82341.", "answer": 6961931550, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87163 * 89183.", "answer": 7773457829, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87235 * 88029.", "answer": 7679209815, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84104 * 81970.", "answer": 6894004880, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89140 * 87133.", "answer": 7767035620, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85704 * 82916.", "answer": 7106232864, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80414 * 85991.", "answer": 6914880274, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87636 * 85668.", "answer": 7507600848, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86948 * 83502.", "answer": 7260331896, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89171 * 83129.", "answer": 7412696059, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86266 * 86130.", "answer": 7430090580, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82932 * 80174.", "answer": 6648990168, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83208 * 87243.", "answer": 7259315544, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85914 * 88618.", "answer": 7613526852, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83193 * 80091.", "answer": 6663010563, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89604 * 85085.", "answer": 7623956340, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85381 * 81541.", "answer": 6962052121, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86043 * 84157.", "answer": 7241120751, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88237 * 80212.", "answer": 7077666244, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89941 * 84473.", "answer": 7597586093, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80549 * 84504.", "answer": 6806712696, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87843 * 86525.", "answer": 7600615575, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80719 * 84145.", "answer": 6792100255, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84492 * 80937.", "answer": 6838529004, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89374 * 80498.", "answer": 7194428252, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87713 * 89954.", "answer": 7890135202, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87446 * 88033.", "answer": 7698133718, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82847 * 87756.", "answer": 7270321332, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88938 * 81702.", "answer": 7266412476, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80625 * 86054.", "answer": 6938103750, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80472 * 82509.", "answer": 6639664248, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82898 * 82156.", "answer": 6810568088, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81356 * 86874.", "answer": 7067721144, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81956 * 80918.", "answer": 6631715608, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87264 * 81021.", "answer": 7070216544, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85148 * 81597.", "answer": 6947821356, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88914 * 84546.", "answer": 7517323044, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83181 * 80273.", "answer": 6677188413, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85450 * 85185.", "answer": 7279058250, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82772 * 89614.", "answer": 7417530008, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86000 * 88459.", "answer": 7607474000, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80232 * 86605.", "answer": 6948492360, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86821 * 81007.", "answer": 7033108747, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81064 * 83161.", "answer": 6741363304, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88216 * 82416.", "answer": 7270409856, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84368 * 81375.", "answer": 6865446000, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82827 * 87264.", "answer": 7227815328, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80729 * 84514.", "answer": 6822730706, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89970 * 83255.", "answer": 7490452350, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88281 * 86705.", "answer": 7654404105, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82833 * 80052.", "answer": 6630947316, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85098 * 84485.", "answer": 7189504530, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89184 * 85745.", "answer": 7647082080, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81928 * 85594.", "answer": 7012545232, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87639 * 89308.", "answer": 7826863812, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81410 * 89276.", "answer": 7267959160, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87585 * 81444.", "answer": 7133272740, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81904 * 81483.", "answer": 6673783632, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82990 * 81415.", "answer": 6756630850, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83041 * 85201.", "answer": 7075176241, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89685 * 80329.", "answer": 7204306365, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82774 * 80171.", "answer": 6636074354, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83563 * 86136.", "answer": 7197782568, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87542 * 81331.", "answer": 7119878402, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84042 * 85042.", "answer": 7147099764, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83130 * 82174.", "answer": 6831124620, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85087 * 80873.", "answer": 6881240951, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86214 * 84703.", "answer": 7302584442, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82916 * 84570.", "answer": 7012206120, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82300 * 89257.", "answer": 7345851100, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85169 * 86782.", "answer": 7391136158, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83702 * 83084.", "answer": 6954296968, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84469 * 83264.", "answer": 7033226816, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82901 * 84832.", "answer": 7032657632, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84249 * 87202.", "answer": 7346681298, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84334 * 81514.", "answer": 6874401676, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88026 * 85818.", "answer": 7554215268, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89481 * 85957.", "answer": 7691518317, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85715 * 88569.", "answer": 7591691835, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87367 * 82793.", "answer": 7233376031, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80601 * 89588.", "answer": 7220882388, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86318 * 82551.", "answer": 7125637218, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88813 * 89317.", "answer": 7932510721, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83451 * 87108.", "answer": 7269249708, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85683 * 84729.", "answer": 7259834907, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83398 * 85606.", "answer": 7139369188, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88253 * 89037.", "answer": 7857782361, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84406 * 81486.", "answer": 6877907316, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88409 * 83452.", "answer": 7377907868, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84230 * 83575.", "answer": 7039522250, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87662 * 84273.", "answer": 7387539726, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80515 * 81889.", "answer": 6593292835, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88471 * 83054.", "answer": 7347870434, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87785 * 82290.", "answer": 7223827650, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87655 * 89614.", "answer": 7855115170, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85291 * 86099.", "answer": 7343469809, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89236 * 86191.", "answer": 7691340076, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89640 * 80554.", "answer": 7220860560, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85281 * 81713.", "answer": 6968566353, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85879 * 80129.", "answer": 6881398391, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82600 * 86904.", "answer": 7178270400, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87790 * 85483.", "answer": 7504552570, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85516 * 81641.", "answer": 6981611756, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83065 * 85865.", "answer": 7132376225, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85018 * 82666.", "answer": 7028097988, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87648 * 88958.", "answer": 7796990784, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83050 * 80356.", "answer": 6673565800, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87192 * 87478.", "answer": 7627381776, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89725 * 89436.", "answer": 8024645100, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87126 * 86542.", "answer": 7540058292, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87759 * 83990.", "answer": 7370878410, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84138 * 86114.", "answer": 7245459732, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89845 * 85535.", "answer": 7684892075, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87906 * 86572.", "answer": 7610198232, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84918 * 80657.", "answer": 6849231126, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83838 * 88306.", "answer": 7403398428, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81767 * 86897.", "answer": 7105306999, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86977 * 84413.", "answer": 7341989501, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89461 * 86565.", "answer": 7744191465, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89716 * 80467.", "answer": 7219177372, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82687 * 88391.", "answer": 7308786617, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82726 * 84924.", "answer": 7025422824, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89778 * 88586.", "answer": 7953073908, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83251 * 89305.", "answer": 7434730555, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82286 * 82128.", "answer": 6757984608, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85458 * 80881.", "answer": 6911928498, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81481 * 85067.", "answer": 6931344227, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82317 * 85670.", "answer": 7052097390, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87515 * 86487.", "answer": 7568909805, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82708 * 87546.", "answer": 7240754568, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80013 * 82416.", "answer": 6594351408, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83283 * 82819.", "answer": 6897414777, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84936 * 85038.", "answer": 7222787568, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81316 * 83024.", "answer": 6751179584, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83869 * 83331.", "answer": 6988887639, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87152 * 81477.", "answer": 7100883504, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84009 * 82525.", "answer": 6932842725, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89098 * 86131.", "answer": 7674099838, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80081 * 87820.", "answer": 7032713420, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82610 * 85647.", "answer": 7075298670, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81636 * 87713.", "answer": 7160538468, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89008 * 86456.", "answer": 7695275648, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83481 * 87738.", "answer": 7324455978, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86165 * 87593.", "answer": 7547450845, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83977 * 81569.", "answer": 6849919913, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86350 * 82105.", "answer": 7089766750, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85215 * 82187.", "answer": 7003565205, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86551 * 85359.", "answer": 7387906809, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84639 * 86956.", "answer": 7359868884, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89780 * 86452.", "answer": 7761660560, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88750 * 81174.", "answer": 7204192500, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85683 * 88000.", "answer": 7540104000, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89608 * 80440.", "answer": 7208067520, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83632 * 89970.", "answer": 7524371040, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82918 * 83852.", "answer": 6952840136, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86047 * 85935.", "answer": 7394448945, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85568 * 88215.", "answer": 7548381120, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80026 * 89816.", "answer": 7187615216, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86523 * 81265.", "answer": 7031291595, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83769 * 82262.", "answer": 6891005478, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88191 * 83079.", "answer": 7326820089, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80724 * 83460.", "answer": 6737225040, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84946 * 87133.", "answer": 7401599818, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81521 * 85563.", "answer": 6975181323, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86292 * 82947.", "answer": 7157662524, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86974 * 82469.", "answer": 7172658806, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84668 * 85096.", "answer": 7204908128, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86337 * 87875.", "answer": 7586863875, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80570 * 84276.", "answer": 6790117320, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86909 * 82941.", "answer": 7208319369, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82679 * 86524.", "answer": 7153717796, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88476 * 81743.", "answer": 7232293668, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87617 * 81353.", "answer": 7127905801, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85673 * 81661.", "answer": 6996142853, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86626 * 80200.", "answer": 6947405200, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82635 * 85226.", "answer": 7042650510, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82109 * 89415.", "answer": 7341776235, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88306 * 86291.", "answer": 7620013046, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87449 * 80189.", "answer": 7012447861, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87964 * 86581.", "answer": 7616011084, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86921 * 80893.", "answer": 7031300453, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84963 * 86962.", "answer": 7388552406, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84237 * 81899.", "answer": 6898926063, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89889 * 87377.", "answer": 7854231153, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88225 * 86108.", "answer": 7596878300, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87758 * 85489.", "answer": 7502343662, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88765 * 85977.", "answer": 7631748405, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81829 * 82930.", "answer": 6786078970, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86947 * 88711.", "answer": 7713155317, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86282 * 81310.", "answer": 7015589420, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82463 * 80113.", "answer": 6606358319, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85523 * 89669.", "answer": 7668761887, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84224 * 83237.", "answer": 7010553088, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88436 * 87454.", "answer": 7734081944, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87125 * 80795.", "answer": 7039264375, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87614 * 84615.", "answer": 7413458610, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80652 * 81991.", "answer": 6612738132, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88021 * 87540.", "answer": 7705358340, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86014 * 80820.", "answer": 6951651480, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89819 * 86050.", "answer": 7728924950, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84134 * 86974.", "answer": 7317470516, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85528 * 84852.", "answer": 7257221856, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80385 * 88892.", "answer": 7145583420, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84378 * 82928.", "answer": 6997298784, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84804 * 85847.", "answer": 7280168988, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86833 * 80287.", "answer": 6971561071, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87319 * 85318.", "answer": 7449882442, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84877 * 80583.", "answer": 6839643291, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89761 * 81829.", "answer": 7345052869, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85853 * 80599.", "answer": 6919665947, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88704 * 86491.", "answer": 7672097664, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84073 * 82871.", "answer": 6967213583, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81377 * 88765.", "answer": 7223429405, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81549 * 82065.", "answer": 6692318685, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 82369 * 88084.", "answer": 7255390996, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87063 * 84500.", "answer": 7356823500, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85658 * 87504.", "answer": 7495417632, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83999 * 88577.", "answer": 7440379423, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89323 * 87510.", "answer": 7816655730, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80665 * 81253.", "answer": 6554273245, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85350 * 86107.", "answer": 7349232450, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80627 * 82404.", "answer": 6643987308, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89983 * 81656.", "answer": 7347651848, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86257 * 88398.", "answer": 7624946286, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81290 * 85534.", "answer": 6953058860, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84947 * 86922.", "answer": 7383763134, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86565 * 80366.", "answer": 6956882790, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83013 * 84208.", "answer": 6990358704, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81298 * 87101.", "answer": 7081137098, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 81907 * 83139.", "answer": 6809666073, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89353 * 84275.", "answer": 7530224075, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84967 * 88422.", "answer": 7512952074, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 88833 * 83993.", "answer": 7461350169, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80800 * 86131.", "answer": 6959384800, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 89393 * 87748.", "answer": 7844056964, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83525 * 87158.", "answer": 7279871950, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84502 * 83042.", "answer": 7017215084, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84535 * 88217.", "answer": 7457424095, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80749 * 89906.", "answer": 7259819594, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86531 * 82969.", "answer": 7179390539, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84668 * 84467.", "answer": 7151651956, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 80082 * 86671.", "answer": 6940787022, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83393 * 80306.", "answer": 6696958258, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 86788 * 82126.", "answer": 7127551288, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 84501 * 84375.", "answer": 7129771875, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 87576 * 89815.", "answer": 7865638440, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 85212 * 81591.", "answer": 6952532292, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 83626 * 83683.", "answer": 6998074558, "range": "[80000, 89999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90296 * 95318.", "answer": 8606834128, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93621 * 91044.", "answer": 8523630324, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94715 * 99983.", "answer": 9469889845, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97547 * 99632.", "answer": 9718802704, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96893 * 99752.", "answer": 9665270536, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95386 * 98871.", "answer": 9430909206, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96374 * 97792.", "answer": 9424606208, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99136 * 90205.", "answer": 8942562880, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95618 * 95580.", "answer": 9139168440, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95237 * 95674.", "answer": 9111704738, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97280 * 92486.", "answer": 8997038080, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97568 * 98175.", "answer": 9578738400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93451 * 98720.", "answer": 9225482720, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92785 * 96390.", "answer": 8943546150, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94189 * 96601.", "answer": 9098751589, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90528 * 99360.", "answer": 8994862080, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91287 * 97971.", "answer": 8943478677, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99196 * 95657.", "answer": 9488791772, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91361 * 93400.", "answer": 8533117400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98676 * 96048.", "answer": 9477632448, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94981 * 94781.", "answer": 9002394161, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95166 * 97397.", "answer": 9268882902, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97657 * 90484.", "answer": 8836395988, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92554 * 99583.", "answer": 9216804982, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92731 * 95761.", "answer": 8880013291, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99255 * 97070.", "answer": 9634682850, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96805 * 90383.", "answer": 8749526315, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94651 * 99116.", "answer": 9381428516, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98040 * 93845.", "answer": 9200563800, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96148 * 98807.", "answer": 9500095436, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92157 * 96200.", "answer": 8865503400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99947 * 92023.", "answer": 9197422781, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91588 * 96483.", "answer": 8836685004, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93576 * 93462.", "answer": 8745800112, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91812 * 99351.", "answer": 9121614012, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94740 * 92926.", "answer": 8803809240, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92606 * 96571.", "answer": 8943054026, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99012 * 96693.", "answer": 9573767316, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95767 * 93567.", "answer": 8960630889, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96851 * 99818.", "answer": 9667473118, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94569 * 95233.", "answer": 9006089577, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95950 * 91730.", "answer": 8801493500, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95206 * 98229.", "answer": 9351990174, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98775 * 98724.", "answer": 9751463100, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96425 * 93688.", "answer": 9033865400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96618 * 98107.", "answer": 9478902126, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97600 * 94690.", "answer": 9241744000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97363 * 92571.", "answer": 9012990273, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92910 * 96554.", "answer": 8970832140, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94725 * 90054.", "answer": 8530365150, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98727 * 95473.", "answer": 9425762871, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97602 * 92822.", "answer": 9059612844, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91610 * 96280.", "answer": 8820210800, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99505 * 96850.", "answer": 9637059250, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96852 * 96722.", "answer": 9367719144, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93094 * 90475.", "answer": 8422679650, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93673 * 92270.", "answer": 8643207710, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99989 * 98247.", "answer": 9823619283, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91319 * 99823.", "answer": 9115736537, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99348 * 96697.", "answer": 9606653556, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90374 * 95325.", "answer": 8614901550, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99991 * 94095.", "answer": 9408653145, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92727 * 99327.", "answer": 9210294729, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97731 * 91490.", "answer": 8941409190, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96066 * 90372.", "answer": 8681676552, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99852 * 96378.", "answer": 9623536056, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99044 * 98377.", "answer": 9743651588, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93162 * 92644.", "answer": 8630900328, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97500 * 96046.", "answer": 9364485000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93920 * 92870.", "answer": 8722350400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97736 * 93273.", "answer": 9116129928, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95287 * 92173.", "answer": 8782888651, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94800 * 91061.", "answer": 8632582800, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90506 * 93391.", "answer": 8452445846, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99463 * 97555.", "answer": 9703112965, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97523 * 94014.", "answer": 9168527322, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99883 * 97268.", "answer": 9715419644, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93963 * 92897.", "answer": 8728880811, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97559 * 98195.", "answer": 9579806005, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91821 * 99896.", "answer": 9172550616, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95427 * 92609.", "answer": 8837399043, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94011 * 97572.", "answer": 9172841292, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91144 * 90112.", "answer": 8213168128, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90529 * 96657.", "answer": 8750261553, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98515 * 97703.", "answer": 9625211045, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96313 * 91152.", "answer": 8779122576, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96833 * 94260.", "answer": 9127478580, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98803 * 91982.", "answer": 9088097546, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99944 * 98751.", "answer": 9869569944, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90388 * 97184.", "answer": 8784267392, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97877 * 90979.", "answer": 8904751583, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94799 * 96527.", "answer": 9150663073, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90653 * 95953.", "answer": 8698427309, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96544 * 98381.", "answer": 9498095264, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97209 * 97021.", "answer": 9431314389, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92032 * 91697.", "answer": 8439058304, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92391 * 94300.", "answer": 8712471300, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99499 * 91831.", "answer": 9137092669, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92768 * 96004.", "answer": 8906099072, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96764 * 95567.", "answer": 9247445188, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92325 * 93982.", "answer": 8676888150, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97906 * 93442.", "answer": 9148532452, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94333 * 91591.", "answer": 8640053803, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95407 * 91213.", "answer": 8702358691, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97507 * 98053.", "answer": 9560853871, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94009 * 94259.", "answer": 8861194331, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95610 * 94838.", "answer": 9067461180, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97285 * 95417.", "answer": 9282642845, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97378 * 94225.", "answer": 9175442050, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99309 * 94510.", "answer": 9385693590, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99739 * 90585.", "answer": 9034857315, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92294 * 92425.", "answer": 8530272950, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98548 * 94725.", "answer": 9334959300, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90425 * 93621.", "answer": 8465678925, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96076 * 99233.", "answer": 9533909708, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95942 * 94771.", "answer": 9092519282, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95024 * 92593.", "answer": 8798557232, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99300 * 94992.", "answer": 9432705600, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97787 * 97206.", "answer": 9505483122, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94831 * 92530.", "answer": 8774712430, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92106 * 92400.", "answer": 8510594400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99952 * 94789.", "answer": 9474350128, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96295 * 94215.", "answer": 9072433425, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93734 * 90458.", "answer": 8478990172, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93467 * 99555.", "answer": 9305107185, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94963 * 92430.", "answer": 8777430090, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99572 * 90197.", "answer": 8981095684, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94250 * 95966.", "answer": 9044795500, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98332 * 98467.", "answer": 9682457044, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96649 * 97814.", "answer": 9453625286, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92791 * 95639.", "answer": 8874438449, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92553 * 99619.", "answer": 9220037307, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98209 * 95149.", "answer": 9344488141, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98574 * 96133.", "answer": 9476214342, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96192 * 97950.", "answer": 9422006400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92770 * 98605.", "answer": 9147585850, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97897 * 92873.", "answer": 9091988081, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97929 * 96223.", "answer": 9423022167, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90233 * 91060.", "answer": 8216616980, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95609 * 93683.", "answer": 8956937947, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95067 * 93382.", "answer": 8877546594, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93675 * 92459.", "answer": 8661096825, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94559 * 99971.", "answer": 9453157789, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91959 * 93226.", "answer": 8572969734, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95840 * 98172.", "answer": 9408804480, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97525 * 99329.", "answer": 9687060725, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90199 * 98587.", "answer": 8892448813, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93741 * 93318.", "answer": 8747722638, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95956 * 90538.", "answer": 8687664328, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96528 * 91619.", "answer": 8843798832, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95398 * 98313.", "answer": 9378863574, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91100 * 94447.", "answer": 8604121700, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99065 * 98761.", "answer": 9783758465, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98810 * 91301.", "answer": 9021451810, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90917 * 97317.", "answer": 8847769689, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99284 * 98567.", "answer": 9786126028, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94062 * 94009.", "answer": 8842674558, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94195 * 92993.", "answer": 8759475635, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94015 * 93741.", "answer": 8813060115, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97472 * 92907.", "answer": 9055831104, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90659 * 99980.", "answer": 9064086820, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94354 * 99043.", "answer": 9345103222, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94546 * 91496.", "answer": 8650580816, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93113 * 91043.", "answer": 8477286859, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92171 * 98561.", "answer": 9084465931, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94960 * 90997.", "answer": 8641075120, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93403 * 93728.", "answer": 8754476384, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93996 * 99595.", "answer": 9361531620, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99523 * 97819.", "answer": 9735240337, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97606 * 91610.", "answer": 8941685660, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98797 * 90836.", "answer": 8974324292, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95224 * 91196.", "answer": 8684047904, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93218 * 97836.", "answer": 9120076248, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91907 * 97240.", "answer": 8937036680, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91366 * 97799.", "answer": 8935503434, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93234 * 91636.", "answer": 8543590824, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98886 * 99656.", "answer": 9854583216, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93522 * 99802.", "answer": 9333682644, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97982 * 94914.", "answer": 9299863548, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99327 * 90157.", "answer": 8955024339, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99530 * 97041.", "answer": 9658490730, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91827 * 97252.", "answer": 8930359404, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93191 * 99649.", "answer": 9286389959, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97475 * 90008.", "answer": 8773529800, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94124 * 96671.", "answer": 9099061204, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99852 * 94435.", "answer": 9429523620, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98070 * 92892.", "answer": 9109918440, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95384 * 98311.", "answer": 9377296424, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97918 * 98424.", "answer": 9637481232, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94649 * 94909.", "answer": 8983041941, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94328 * 98719.", "answer": 9311965832, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94079 * 95589.", "answer": 8992917531, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94510 * 99195.", "answer": 9374919450, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98242 * 95059.", "answer": 9338786278, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97209 * 91826.", "answer": 8926313634, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92984 * 97988.", "answer": 9111316192, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90106 * 95229.", "answer": 8580704274, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98348 * 97708.", "answer": 9609386384, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98122 * 92672.", "answer": 9093161984, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92929 * 91074.", "answer": 8463415746, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97078 * 94991.", "answer": 9221536298, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91549 * 97261.", "answer": 8904147289, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95610 * 98824.", "answer": 9448562640, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92992 * 93171.", "answer": 8664157632, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91781 * 93797.", "answer": 8608782457, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93493 * 95033.", "answer": 8884920269, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98221 * 95003.", "answer": 9331289663, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95243 * 98690.", "answer": 9399531670, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97731 * 91686.", "answer": 8960564466, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94916 * 99986.", "answer": 9490271176, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93445 * 99355.", "answer": 9284227975, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92532 * 95304.", "answer": 8818669728, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92562 * 93144.", "answer": 8621594928, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96491 * 92814.", "answer": 8955715674, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92587 * 99996.", "answer": 9258329652, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92574 * 95335.", "answer": 8825542290, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98461 * 97762.", "answer": 9625744282, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99752 * 96830.", "answer": 9658986160, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94413 * 93747.", "answer": 8850935511, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94306 * 97732.", "answer": 9216713992, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94974 * 96075.", "answer": 9124627050, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92375 * 95017.", "answer": 8777195375, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95467 * 95798.", "answer": 9145547666, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95166 * 97368.", "answer": 9266123088, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95046 * 96968.", "answer": 9216420528, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99228 * 96447.", "answer": 9570242916, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96834 * 90092.", "answer": 8723968728, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96620 * 90906.", "answer": 8783337720, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96697 * 95793.", "answer": 9262895721, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92292 * 97485.", "answer": 8997085620, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94492 * 90319.", "answer": 8534422948, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93313 * 93417.", "answer": 8717020521, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94193 * 94829.", "answer": 8932227997, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96119 * 90387.", "answer": 8687908053, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95273 * 97004.", "answer": 9241862092, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96265 * 95336.", "answer": 9177520040, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99143 * 99174.", "answer": 9832407882, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93267 * 93522.", "answer": 8722516374, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98240 * 97210.", "answer": 9549910400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94488 * 91750.", "answer": 8669274000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91219 * 93983.", "answer": 8573035277, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92628 * 95332.", "answer": 8830412496, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97859 * 99714.", "answer": 9757912326, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97698 * 90753.", "answer": 8866386594, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96390 * 97979.", "answer": 9444195810, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94093 * 94589.", "answer": 8900162777, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99940 * 99602.", "answer": 9954223880, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96144 * 90971.", "answer": 8746315824, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91661 * 90919.", "answer": 8333726459, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95614 * 94522.", "answer": 9037626508, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98812 * 96053.", "answer": 9491189036, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97178 * 94656.", "answer": 9198480768, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91819 * 97730.", "answer": 8973470870, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92200 * 91212.", "answer": 8409746400, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95317 * 96779.", "answer": 9224683943, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92486 * 92464.", "answer": 8551625504, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99663 * 94896.", "answer": 9457620048, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99405 * 93276.", "answer": 9272100780, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99205 * 91441.", "answer": 9071404405, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97180 * 94017.", "answer": 9136572060, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95371 * 99383.", "answer": 9478256093, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98955 * 94271.", "answer": 9328586805, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99120 * 98700.", "answer": 9783144000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94774 * 90358.", "answer": 8563589092, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92301 * 91114.", "answer": 8409913314, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95143 * 95918.", "answer": 9125926274, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97304 * 93519.", "answer": 9099772776, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93016 * 95263.", "answer": 8860983208, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97673 * 93730.", "answer": 9154890290, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97549 * 95934.", "answer": 9358265766, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95456 * 93260.", "answer": 8902226560, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94243 * 94183.", "answer": 8876088469, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99889 * 90379.", "answer": 9027867931, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92298 * 91952.", "answer": 8486985696, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96730 * 97001.", "answer": 9382906730, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96493 * 97968.", "answer": 9453226224, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90786 * 98657.", "answer": 8956674402, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90987 * 98392.", "answer": 8952392904, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96119 * 90265.", "answer": 8676181535, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99268 * 97163.", "answer": 9645176684, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90525 * 98261.", "answer": 8895077025, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95358 * 98827.", "answer": 9423945066, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98061 * 94630.", "answer": 9279512430, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99417 * 95468.", "answer": 9491142156, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91099 * 91237.", "answer": 8311599463, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99261 * 91509.", "answer": 9083274849, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99147 * 91840.", "answer": 9105660480, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98712 * 92592.", "answer": 9139941504, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98413 * 91437.", "answer": 8998589481, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99403 * 97675.", "answer": 9709188025, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99994 * 93127.", "answer": 9312141238, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91197 * 97060.", "answer": 8851580820, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94536 * 97630.", "answer": 9229549680, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97393 * 92493.", "answer": 9008170749, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95413 * 91196.", "answer": 8701283948, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92976 * 99424.", "answer": 9244045824, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95567 * 97439.", "answer": 9311952913, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98646 * 97084.", "answer": 9576948264, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90351 * 96577.", "answer": 8725828527, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99416 * 94813.", "answer": 9425929208, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90104 * 96388.", "answer": 8684944352, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90309 * 90139.", "answer": 8140362951, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93690 * 95281.", "answer": 8926876890, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96998 * 92465.", "answer": 8968920070, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94241 * 93651.", "answer": 8825763891, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99574 * 95351.", "answer": 9494480474, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98722 * 97499.", "answer": 9625296278, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93282 * 99411.", "answer": 9273256902, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95810 * 99451.", "answer": 9528400310, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92500 * 93094.", "answer": 8611195000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92429 * 93377.", "answer": 8630742733, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95054 * 92975.", "answer": 8837645650, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91653 * 90429.", "answer": 8288089137, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98739 * 99861.", "answer": 9860175279, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90646 * 92086.", "answer": 8347227556, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98848 * 95710.", "answer": 9460742080, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91134 * 95365.", "answer": 8690993910, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95166 * 93770.", "answer": 8923715820, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93421 * 93304.", "answer": 8716552984, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94963 * 92675.", "answer": 8800696025, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96951 * 94441.", "answer": 9156149391, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93817 * 93559.", "answer": 8777424703, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95821 * 90447.", "answer": 8666721987, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92249 * 97203.", "answer": 8966879547, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92017 * 96145.", "answer": 8846974465, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90416 * 97273.", "answer": 8795035568, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93417 * 96232.", "answer": 8989704744, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90806 * 97320.", "answer": 8837239920, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97185 * 96540.", "answer": 9382239900, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93254 * 93369.", "answer": 8707032726, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96234 * 99670.", "answer": 9591642780, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92042 * 91521.", "answer": 8423775882, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92868 * 98301.", "answer": 9129017268, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99474 * 98462.", "answer": 9794408988, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91993 * 92668.", "answer": 8524807324, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93434 * 91971.", "answer": 8593218414, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98013 * 99909.", "answer": 9792380817, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95871 * 95191.", "answer": 9126056361, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96801 * 93129.", "answer": 9014980329, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93446 * 91487.", "answer": 8549094202, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98305 * 95895.", "answer": 9426957975, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97831 * 94182.", "answer": 9213919242, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98335 * 91834.", "answer": 9030496390, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97486 * 90264.", "answer": 8799476304, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90118 * 96226.", "answer": 8671694668, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96881 * 96558.", "answer": 9354635598, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91639 * 95811.", "answer": 8780024229, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95904 * 95078.", "answer": 9118360512, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91069 * 97113.", "answer": 8843983797, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94926 * 93757.", "answer": 8899976982, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91383 * 96384.", "answer": 8807859072, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97722 * 90259.", "answer": 8820289998, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94500 * 95296.", "answer": 9005472000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90743 * 92305.", "answer": 8376032615, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94079 * 92905.", "answer": 8740409495, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99250 * 90151.", "answer": 8947486750, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92096 * 98497.", "answer": 9071179712, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92551 * 92297.", "answer": 8542179647, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97697 * 90638.", "answer": 8855060686, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91002 * 99768.", "answer": 9079087536, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93437 * 94801.", "answer": 8857921037, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96089 * 96797.", "answer": 9301126933, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92580 * 96868.", "answer": 8968039440, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92824 * 92861.", "answer": 8619729464, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98496 * 92480.", "answer": 9108910080, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92975 * 95981.", "answer": 8923833475, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91792 * 92660.", "answer": 8505446720, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90491 * 98151.", "answer": 8881782141, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93343 * 95014.", "answer": 8868891802, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96613 * 96114.", "answer": 9285861882, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94344 * 95260.", "answer": 8987209440, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90466 * 90423.", "answer": 8180207118, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95432 * 90466.", "answer": 8633351312, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97708 * 90560.", "answer": 8848436480, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92364 * 96679.", "answer": 8929659156, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90761 * 98838.", "answer": 8970635718, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96177 * 99805.", "answer": 9598945485, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98604 * 92781.", "answer": 9148577724, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92591 * 91640.", "answer": 8485039240, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90244 * 95712.", "answer": 8637433728, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93648 * 91509.", "answer": 8569634832, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96879 * 91086.", "answer": 8824320594, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91841 * 97793.", "answer": 8981406913, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97609 * 96800.", "answer": 9448551200, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98793 * 97215.", "answer": 9604161495, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92202 * 99883.", "answer": 9209412366, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90011 * 95102.", "answer": 8560226122, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97802 * 97692.", "answer": 9554472984, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94208 * 92100.", "answer": 8676556800, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95290 * 98847.", "answer": 9419130630, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95989 * 91579.", "answer": 8790576631, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97828 * 98074.", "answer": 9594383272, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99359 * 93215.", "answer": 9261749185, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92061 * 93593.", "answer": 8616265173, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98433 * 92126.", "answer": 9068238558, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92336 * 93695.", "answer": 8651421520, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91346 * 91553.", "answer": 8363000338, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96616 * 94625.", "answer": 9142289000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91724 * 94092.", "answer": 8630494608, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93706 * 94106.", "answer": 8818296836, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93024 * 94933.", "answer": 8831047392, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95384 * 97571.", "answer": 9306712264, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99679 * 98518.", "answer": 9820175722, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98468 * 99456.", "answer": 9793233408, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94370 * 92157.", "answer": 8696856090, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95373 * 96914.", "answer": 9242978922, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96140 * 92379.", "answer": 8881317060, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99492 * 90560.", "answer": 9009995520, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96308 * 90786.", "answer": 8743418088, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93242 * 92984.", "answer": 8670014128, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90234 * 92342.", "answer": 8332388028, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90558 * 93896.", "answer": 8503033968, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92652 * 96500.", "answer": 8940918000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95284 * 90191.", "answer": 8593759244, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99373 * 97877.", "answer": 9726331121, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97927 * 95634.", "answer": 9365150718, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93076 * 99456.", "answer": 9256966656, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96646 * 97407.", "answer": 9413996922, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93519 * 97425.", "answer": 9111088575, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94305 * 98943.", "answer": 9330819615, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97206 * 91930.", "answer": 8936147580, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94576 * 98429.", "answer": 9309021104, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95527 * 95525.", "answer": 9125216675, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93052 * 94182.", "answer": 8763823464, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95586 * 97984.", "answer": 9365898624, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98993 * 97476.", "answer": 9649441668, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91581 * 95609.", "answer": 8755967829, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98504 * 94306.", "answer": 9289518224, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91034 * 95987.", "answer": 8738080558, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96988 * 90416.", "answer": 8769267008, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98901 * 92068.", "answer": 9105617268, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91549 * 93721.", "answer": 8580063829, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97494 * 91820.", "answer": 8951899080, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91970 * 99018.", "answer": 9106685460, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94844 * 92069.", "answer": 8732192236, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95695 * 95030.", "answer": 9093895850, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97414 * 97146.", "answer": 9463380444, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99065 * 91359.", "answer": 9050479335, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98269 * 92991.", "answer": 9138132579, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96513 * 98370.", "answer": 9493983810, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93192 * 92321.", "answer": 8603578632, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93634 * 90273.", "answer": 8452622082, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93255 * 95798.", "answer": 8933642490, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98611 * 99845.", "answer": 9845815295, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92486 * 99222.", "answer": 9176645892, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98692 * 98602.", "answer": 9731228584, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90769 * 98735.", "answer": 8962077215, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95941 * 98838.", "answer": 9482616558, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93775 * 98697.", "answer": 9255311175, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92732 * 96135.", "answer": 8914790820, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92600 * 91640.", "answer": 8485864000, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92713 * 93707.", "answer": 8687857091, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92491 * 98860.", "answer": 9143660260, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99988 * 96947.", "answer": 9693536636, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93312 * 94561.", "answer": 8823676032, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90801 * 96567.", "answer": 8768380167, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94857 * 96386.", "answer": 9142886802, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98548 * 96901.", "answer": 9549399748, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97807 * 97667.", "answer": 9552516269, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95274 * 92230.", "answer": 8787121020, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94915 * 90005.", "answer": 8542824575, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91226 * 94117.", "answer": 8585917442, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99105 * 95105.", "answer": 9425381025, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93420 * 99731.", "answer": 9316870020, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91094 * 90970.", "answer": 8286821180, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96723 * 92298.", "answer": 8927339454, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92355 * 97879.", "answer": 9039615045, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92625 * 93972.", "answer": 8704156500, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96410 * 92612.", "answer": 8928722920, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96865 * 96406.", "answer": 9338367190, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99689 * 93168.", "answer": 9287824752, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94072 * 95741.", "answer": 9006547352, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91155 * 93707.", "answer": 8541861585, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94525 * 92300.", "answer": 8724657500, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96577 * 92022.", "answer": 8887208694, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99599 * 92487.", "answer": 9211612713, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93372 * 97264.", "answer": 9081734208, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92333 * 94513.", "answer": 8726668829, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95365 * 90176.", "answer": 8599634240, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91921 * 98529.", "answer": 9056884209, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95098 * 98589.", "answer": 9375616722, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91681 * 99804.", "answer": 9150130524, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97718 * 93804.", "answer": 9166339272, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97180 * 94895.", "answer": 9221896100, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92045 * 98867.", "answer": 9100213015, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99994 * 97444.", "answer": 9743815336, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 92517 * 91153.", "answer": 8433202101, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95593 * 94458.", "answer": 9029523594, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 90671 * 96250.", "answer": 8727083750, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 94185 * 91848.", "answer": 8650703880, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97643 * 96978.", "answer": 9469222854, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99584 * 92759.", "answer": 9237312256, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 97983 * 94769.", "answer": 9285750927, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 93680 * 98566.", "answer": 9233662880, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91688 * 91451.", "answer": 8384959288, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 99884 * 99814.", "answer": 9969821576, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 95940 * 93953.", "answer": 9013850820, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 98102 * 97085.", "answer": 9524232670, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 96908 * 90928.", "answer": 8811650624, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
{"question": "Calculate the following question: 91723 * 94590.", "answer": 8676078570, "range": "[90000, 99999]"}
